<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>building-materials on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/building-materials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in building-materials on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/building-materials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portland cement materials and specifications</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/portland-cement-materials-and-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/portland-cement-materials-and-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Portland cement, the most common of modern cement, is made by carefully blending selected raw materials to produce a finished material meeting the requirements of ASTM C150 for one of eight specific cement types. Four major compounds [lime (CaO), iron (Fe2O3), silica (SiO2), and alumina (Al2O3)] and two minor compounds [gypsum (CaSO4 2H2O) and magnesia (MgO)] constitute the raw materials. The calcareous (CaO) materials typically come from limestone, calcite, marl, or shale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building guide</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/docs/installation/building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 22:42:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/docs/installation/building/</guid>
      <description>Step by step installation process of a building. This guide of installation of a building will help us to know how to build small to large scale category building by self.
PRINCIPLES OF ARCHITECTURE A building is an assemblage that is firmly attached to the ground and that provides
SYSTEMS DESIGN AND ANALYSIS Systems design comprises a logical series of steps that leads to the best
TRADITIONAL CONSTRUCTION PROCEDURES Systems design of buildings requires a different approach to design and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building stones and it&#39;s properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</guid>
      <description>Principal building stones generally used in the United States are limestones, marbles, granites, and sandstones. Other stones such as serpentine and quartzite are used locally but to a much lesser extent. Stone, in general, makes an excellent
building material, if properly selected on the basis of experience; but the cost may be relatively high.
The properties of stone depend on what nature has provided. Therefore, the designer does not have the choice of properties and colors available in some of the manufactured building units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Sustainable Building or Green Building</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</guid>
      <description>What is a sustainable building? For your building to be sustainable, many factors need to be considered. These include air quality, energy
efficiency, and the use of ‘green’ materials among others. This document focuses on 1) building a sustainable building 2) retrofitting and 3) certification.
Why should I make my buildings sustainable? Apart from the environmental benefits, a sustainable building can reduce your operational costs by as much as 30-50% on your energy usage and 40-50% on your water usage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
