<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>corona on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/corona/</link>
    <description>Recent content in corona on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/corona/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corona vaccination: No expectations to stop Corona in 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>WHO said &amp;ldquo;There is no hope to stop Corona virus in 2021. Vaccine program ongoing but human need to aware to maintain all preventive actions to stop spread.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy of Bangladesh in  2020: Rising from the ruins</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-bangladesh-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-bangladesh-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</guid>
      <description>The year 2020 started with a haze of vulnerability looming into the great beyond. The tale Covid was spreading in Europe, the objective of more than 60% fares from Bangladesh, subsequent to unleashing ruin in China, its biggest exchanging accomplice.
Source: The daily Star
Bangladesh felt the warmth of an approaching worldwide emergency however the infection had not at this point advanced into the nation.
The awful news came two or after three months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy of United States in  2020: Rising from the ruins</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</guid>
      <description>The year 2020 started with a haze of vulnerability looming into the great beyond. The tale Covid was spreading in Europe, the objective of more than 60% fares from Bangladesh, subsequent to unleashing ruin in China, its biggest exchanging accomplice.
Source: The daily Star
Bangladesh felt the warmth of an approaching worldwide emergency however the infection had not at this point advanced into the nation.
The awful news came two or after three months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing one more point extension of leave: BD News</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</guid>
      <description>The country has announced to extend the holiday once again till January 16. According to the Ministry of Education on Friday, all educational institutions, schools, colleges, universities and national universities will remain closed till January 16. Until December 17, all educational institutions in the country were closed except Qawmi Madrasa.
To curb the spread of corona virus in Bangladesh, all educational institutions were closed from March 17 and all educational institutions were closed till December 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House has threatened Hane with approving the vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</guid>
      <description>White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine later in the day, two administration officials said. The vaccine, developed by Pfizer and its German partner Bioentech, was endorsed by an FDA panel on Thursday and reached the public.
White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine by the end of the day, two administration officials said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. experts call for Pfizer vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-us-scientist-pfizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-us-scientist-pfizer/</guid>
      <description>U.S. experts on Thursday called on a panel of U.S. government advisers to decide whether to support the large-scale use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 vaccine to combat the outbreak of nearly 300,000 American corona deaths.
Pfizer vaccine for corona prevention The meeting of Food and Drug Administration advisers will present the potential hurdles from the beginning to the end of the largest immunization program in U.S. history. Vaccination activities could begin in a few days, depending on how quickly the FDA signs the panel&amp;rsquo;s recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19: United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</guid>
      <description>According to the World Health Organisation (WHO), for the first wave of COVID-19 to be over, the number of people testing positive for COVID-19 has to drop below 5%. Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s present data says the infection rate is still above 10%. So the first wave of COVID-19 in Bangladesh is continuing and the rate of infection is increasing to some extent.
Why is the infection rate still increasing? The answer probably is we have become relaxed, or exhausted, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without delay posterior Bangladesh look forward to a Covid-19 protection?</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-without-delay-posterior-bangladesh-look-forward-to-a-covid-19-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-without-delay-posterior-bangladesh-look-forward-to-a-covid-19-protection/</guid>
      <description>The surprising saving exotic Covid-19 hindering trials by Pfizer-BioNTech and Moderna elevated perspective beating the planet in the deportment compete relative to the nefarious failing, but experts curb beamy challenges for Bangladesh to as well moderate foreign the pair vaccines suited to to its current tainted nude strand. They word-of-mouth the mRNA technology-based vaccines qualified by Moderna and Pfizer address to be stored at at large of pocket 70-80 degrees Celsius temperature, but the wilderness has a unveil mooring having the talent of preserving life-saving drugs and progeny&amp;rsquo;s vaccines at temperatures as inferior as missing 20 degrees Celsius less than the Inflated Proclaim on Immunisation (EPI) background .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
