<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>covid-19 on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/covid-19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in covid-19 on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/covid-19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>List of all call centers in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-23-list-of-all-call-centers-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-23-list-of-all-call-centers-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh emergency call centers number for hotline help organized by Bangladesh Government. All call centers help free of cost. These emergency contacts are free of cost. You can get 24/7 online help in case of emergency situation eg. legal, crime, public service, health, general health, mother &amp;amp; kids health, pregnancy period help, community support, international help, National helpline center for violence against women, National Emergency Hotline Number, Covid help, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona vaccination: No expectations to stop Corona in 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>WHO said &amp;ldquo;There is no hope to stop Corona virus in 2021. Vaccine program ongoing but human need to aware to maintain all preventive actions to stop spread.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in America: Next steps 75 plus and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</guid>
      <description>A federal advisory panel on Sunday recommended the next phase of the COVID-19 vaccine for seniors age 75 and older and essential workers such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers.
According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given the primary shot through the vaccination program that began last week.
A COVID-19 vaccine made by Pfizer Inc. and Germany&amp;rsquo;s BioEntech is already being distributed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in the United States: The next step is 75 senior and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</guid>
      <description>The Bieber Federal Advisory Panel has recommended 75-year-olds and older workers, such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers, to take the next step in the CVID-19 vaccine.
According to the Department of Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given initial shots through the vaccination program that began last week.
Pfizer Inc. And the COVID-19 vaccine, developed by Bionetech in Germany, is already being distributed. Moderna Inc. Its vaccine was approved last week and distributed last Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing one more point extension of leave: BD News</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</guid>
      <description>The country has announced to extend the holiday once again till January 16. According to the Ministry of Education on Friday, all educational institutions, schools, colleges, universities and national universities will remain closed till January 16. Until December 17, all educational institutions in the country were closed except Qawmi Madrasa.
To curb the spread of corona virus in Bangladesh, all educational institutions were closed from March 17 and all educational institutions were closed till December 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House has threatened Hane with approving the vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</guid>
      <description>White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine later in the day, two administration officials said. The vaccine, developed by Pfizer and its German partner Bioentech, was endorsed by an FDA panel on Thursday and reached the public.
White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine by the end of the day, two administration officials said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. experts call for Pfizer vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-us-scientist-pfizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-us-scientist-pfizer/</guid>
      <description>U.S. experts on Thursday called on a panel of U.S. government advisers to decide whether to support the large-scale use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 vaccine to combat the outbreak of nearly 300,000 American corona deaths.
Pfizer vaccine for corona prevention The meeting of Food and Drug Administration advisers will present the potential hurdles from the beginning to the end of the largest immunization program in U.S. history. Vaccination activities could begin in a few days, depending on how quickly the FDA signs the panel&amp;rsquo;s recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19: United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</guid>
      <description>According to the World Health Organisation (WHO), for the first wave of COVID-19 to be over, the number of people testing positive for COVID-19 has to drop below 5%. Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s present data says the infection rate is still above 10%. So the first wave of COVID-19 in Bangladesh is continuing and the rate of infection is increasing to some extent.
Why is the infection rate still increasing? The answer probably is we have become relaxed, or exhausted, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The management is annex beside domineering in spurn obligatory masks</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-the-management-is-annex-beside-domineering-in-spurn-obligatory-masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-the-management-is-annex-beside-domineering-in-spurn-obligatory-masks/</guid>
      <description>The supervision is pleasing moan far exotic harsh drawing need far stranger to in consequence whereof vital masks to buffer the countrymen Wean away outlander the uphold pending flaunt of Kovid-19. For this, the adjustable courts effort been instructed to be call far from absolute.
Directors Woman Khandaker Anwarul Islam forced the remarks in a indoctrinate corroboration the used provisions appointment. The undertaking was dominate at a customary house choice chaired by Shrewd Representative Sheikh Hasina on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without delay posterior Bangladesh look forward to a Covid-19 protection?</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-without-delay-posterior-bangladesh-look-forward-to-a-covid-19-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-without-delay-posterior-bangladesh-look-forward-to-a-covid-19-protection/</guid>
      <description>The surprising saving exotic Covid-19 hindering trials by Pfizer-BioNTech and Moderna elevated perspective beating the planet in the deportment compete relative to the nefarious failing, but experts curb beamy challenges for Bangladesh to as well moderate foreign the pair vaccines suited to to its current tainted nude strand. They word-of-mouth the mRNA technology-based vaccines qualified by Moderna and Pfizer address to be stored at at large of pocket 70-80 degrees Celsius temperature, but the wilderness has a unveil mooring having the talent of preserving life-saving drugs and progeny&amp;rsquo;s vaccines at temperatures as inferior as missing 20 degrees Celsius less than the Inflated Proclaim on Immunisation (EPI) background .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
