<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sop-document on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/sop-document/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sop-document on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/sop-document/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn How To Create an SOP of Claim And Complain Of QC</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we got a quality complaint and claim, we need to provide a reasonable explanation to the buyer how and why it happened. To provide this explanation, we need to make a thorough investigation to find out the possible root cause as well as provide the correct action plan to avoid future happening. During the investigation, we need to involve a lot of data and questions. In our past experiences, we spent a lot of time back and forth emails to collect the data and find out the root cause because either we forgot to check this or that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Operating Procedure of A Small Business</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</guid>
      <description>Standard operating procedures (SOP) of a garment idustry A Standard Operating Procedure or SOP means is structured documentation that provides step-by-step guidelines and instructions on how to do a particular business activity, such as production or record keeping. We need SOP in a company with different operations in different areas.
Example of business operating procedure manual: Standard operating procedures or SOP needs to develop as a structured documented office word or pdf file and manual printed copy for management approval.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
