<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>compliance on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/compliance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in compliance on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/compliance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Fire Safety Management System</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-fire-safety-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-fire-safety-management-system/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you to learn about industrial fire safety management system implementation, analysis, and inspection systems to install fire safety management systems in your own industrial premises.
We have completed our fire safety project implementation in an Indonesian Apparel manufacturer industry location is &amp;ldquo;Jl. Raya Wantilan RT.07/03, Ds. Wantilan, Kec. Wantilan, Kab. Subang, Jawa Barat&amp;rdquo;
In this fire safety project implementation, a total of 1164 Employees attended and, contributed their efforts to make this project successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance and Sustainability: Conflict Minerals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</guid>
      <description>Learn About Conflict Minerals US guidelines for vendor compliance and sustainability
Index:
What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals in Products US Conflict Minerals Laws Auditing and Reporting Requirements Customer’s expectations Continuous Tracking Tracing workflow Reporting – CFSI Beyond USA What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals refer to raw materials that come from a particular part of the world where conflict is occurring and trading of those materials, perpetuates the fighting. Conflict minerals are mined in conditions of armed conflict and human rights abuses, notably in the Democratic Republic of Congo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Supplier Safety And Product Quality Specifications</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-garment-supplier-safety-and-product-quality-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-garment-supplier-safety-and-product-quality-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Suppliers of private brand products to Fashion Retail (the “Suppliers”) and its subsidiaries undertake to
comply with the following requirements.
Product safety and quality 1.1. The Suppliers must assure: 1.1.1. The safety and the compliance of the products with the laws and standards in force in the countries
of sale at the time of purchase
1.1.2. A level of aesthetic quality, performance, and minimum product life that is usual for the kind of goods</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
