<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphics Design on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/graphics-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphics Design on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/graphics-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D classic logo design</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-classic-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-classic-logo/</guid>
      <description>3D classic logo design using adobe cc 2020 3D classic logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020. Learn online Adobe Illustrator by Channel 365. All content created by a skilled graphics designer from India and content authority verified. This content will help you to learn about Adobe Illustrator 3D classic logo design using Adobe Illustrator cc 2020. Adobe illustrator 2020 cc is almost the same as Adobe illustrator 2021 latest update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D colorful logo design</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-colorful-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-colorful-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>3D colorful logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020 Welcome to Adobe illustrator course cc 2020. And in this video I will be teaching you how you can create colorful logo. Now it’s super easy to do and let’s see how that’s done.
The first thing we have to do is to create on your document. So the document that I wouldn’t be using for district auditor is this custom sized document which is called in by a thousand pixels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract animal logo design</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/animal-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/animal-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>Abstract animal logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020 Abstract animal logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020. Learn online Adobe Illustrator by Channel 365. All content created by a skilled graphics designer from India and content authority verified. This content will help you to learn about Adobe Illustrator Abstract animal logo design using Adobe Illustrator cc 2020. Adobe illustrator 2020 cc is almost the same as Adobe illustrator 2021 latest update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create Rectangle, Circle and Straigt line using Inkscape</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/-create-rectangle-circle-and-straigt-line-using-inkscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/-create-rectangle-circle-and-straigt-line-using-inkscape/</guid>
      <description>Create Rectangle, Circle and Straigt line using Inkscape Today we will learn how to create Rectangle, Circle and Straigt line using Inkscape.
Inkscape is a great design tool to create SVG images. Using Inkscape you can learn different designs very easily.
First you have to open Inkscape and follow below steps:
Select File –&amp;gt; New from Template –&amp;gt; Select your required template.
Then For straight line, select Draw Baizer curve and Straight lines tool.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
