<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>weather on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/weather/</link>
    <description>Recent content in weather on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Crisis: Understanding the Alarming Decline in Lake Mead Water Levels</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/navigating-the-crisis-understanding-the-alarming-decline-in-lake-mead-water-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/navigating-the-crisis-understanding-the-alarming-decline-in-lake-mead-water-levels/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Lake Mead, located on the Colorado River, is the largest reservoir in the United States, providing water and power to millions of people in the Southwest. It has long been a vital resource for agricultural, industrial, and municipal needs, supporting cities such as Las Vegas, Phoenix, and Los Angeles. However, in recent years, the water levels of Lake Mead have been steadily declining, raising concerns about the sustainability of water resources in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determination of Moist Air Properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</guid>
      <description>An air-water mixture is found from the heat and mass balance to be at 60°C (333 K) and 0.025 kg/kg (25 g/kg) absolute humidity. Calculate the other main parameters for the mixture. Take atmospheric pressure as 101,325 Pa.
Method: Consult item (vi) in Table 12-5 for the calculation methodology.
From the initial terminology section, specific humidity YW = 0.02439 kg/kg, mole ratio z = 0.0402 kmol/kmol, mole fraction y = 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to protect your building against wind, storm, or tornado</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</guid>
      <description>For practical design, wind and earthquakes may be treated as horizontal, or lateral, loads. Although wind and seismic loads may have vertical components, these generally are small and readily resisted by columns and bearing walls. Vertical earthquake components can be important in the design of connections as in precast concrete structures. Wind often generates significant uplift forces that require special attention to vertical restraint and lateral support for members in reverse bending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greenhouse Gases and Renewable Energy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</guid>
      <description>Effect greenhouse What are greenhouse gases (GHG)? Greenhouse gases (GHGs) trap heat within the earth’s atmosphere, contributing to the ‘greenhouse’ effect and causing global warming. These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide, and water vapor. Industry, including manufacturing, is the second largest global emitter of human-created GHGs. Much of industrial GHG emissions are due to the burning of fossil fuels for heat and power generation.
Why should I care about GHGs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best economical structures of building construction</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</guid>
      <description>STRUCTURAL STEEL CONSTRUCTION Structural steel is the economical construction material for building applications. It offers high ratios of strength to weight and strength to volume. Thus, structural steel has the advantage of permitting long clear spans for horizontal members and requiring less floor space for columns than other common construction materials. It also can be used in combination with reinforced concrete to provide cost-effective building components. For large industrial buildings, where the structural frame can be exposed, it is often the material of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different types of Steel Grades</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</guid>
      <description>Structural steel grades are referred to by their corresponding ASTM designation. For example, the most commonly used grade of structural steel is A36, which is produced to meet the requirements of the ASTM A36 specification. This grade offers a good mix of strength, weldability, and cost. In many designs, this specification alone will satisfy designers’ needs. Other specifications, such as A53 for pipe, provide an equivalent grade of steel for that type of product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Design Your Building Against Earthquake</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</guid>
      <description>Buildings should be designed to withstand minor earthquakes without damage, because they may occur almost everywhere. For major earthquakes, it may not be economical to prevent all damage but collapse should be precluded. Because an earthquake and a high wind are not likely to occur simultaneously, building codes usually do not require that buildings be designed for a combination of large seismic and wind loads. Thus, designers may assume that the full strength of wind bracing is also available to resist drift caused by earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is COP26 And Why Its Matter</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</guid>
      <description>UK hosts a summit amongst United Nations countries to talk about global climate changes, how to tackle this situation and what necessary steps should take in immediate action is called COP26.
It was a plan to host in Glasgow, in a city of Scotland in November 2020 last year and attend more than 200 world countries leader, but due to Coronavirus Pandemic, the COP26 program delayed more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Of Making An Easy 5K A Month Within The Next 22 Days</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days/</guid>
      <description>Making money is the big secret of life, it&amp;rsquo;s not so easy to make money. Many many people is trying to earn money, they are doing lots of things but money is not so easy to get much within short time.
I have tried lots of things last couple of years. Amazon affiliate, digital marketing, learning programming, social media marketing, Upwork, Fiverr and more. But money is not easy to make online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>খুলনার সেহরি এবং ইফতারের সময়</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/04/2021-04-26-sehri-and-iftar-time-in-khulna-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/04/2021-04-26-sehri-and-iftar-time-in-khulna-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>আমরা এখানে খুব সহজেই খুলনা এবং তার পার্শ্ববর্তী অঞ্চলের সেহরি এবং ইফতারের সময়সূচি।
All times based on local calenders updated by government of Bangladesh. Requested to follow your local Prayer time for Ramadan sehri and iftar.
[prayer_time]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sello oil in Altoona PA on 12 Feb 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-12-sello-oil-in-altoona/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-12-sello-oil-in-altoona/</guid>
      <description>Sello Oil price update on 12 Feb 2021 What is sello oil? Sello oil (Sel-Lo Oil) is a fuel supplier and distributor in Altoona, PA, United States of America. They deliver different kinds of fuel like Ultra-low-sulfur diesel oil (Dyed ULSD), blended fuel, kerosene fuel, and heating oil. Sello Oil company established in 1988 has been operated by a family in central Pennsylvania. Sello oil company is one of the largest heating oil distributors in central Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need a strong global climate alliance to save our planet: Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina has said that a strong global climate alliance is urgently needed to save future generations and the planet from the adverse effects of climate change by reducing carbon emissions.
She said he would like to emphasize the importance of a positive and strong international climate alliance to move towards achieving carbon balance by effectively reducing global carbon emissions before the middle of the century.
This was stated by the Prime Minister in a pre-recorded speech at a virtual conference titled &amp;lsquo;Thimphu Ambition Summit&amp;rsquo; aimed at accelerating the pace of globalization by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA&#39;s Joe Biden urges world pioneers to be intense to handle environmental change</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</guid>
      <description>US President Joe Biden has encouraged the world chiefs to assume a striking part in decreasing carbon emanations to guarantee the assurance of life and property.
He made the allure while tending to the High-Level Panel Closing Session of the UNFCCC Race to Zero Dialogs by means of a video message.
States in the current year confronted intermittent flooding alongside two typhoons that harmed harvests and living spaces and influenced individuals&amp;rsquo; occupation in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
