<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>united-states-2 on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/united-states-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in united-states-2 on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/united-states-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to protect your building against wind, storm, or tornado</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</guid>
      <description>For practical design, wind and earthquakes may be treated as horizontal, or lateral, loads. Although wind and seismic loads may have vertical components, these generally are small and readily resisted by columns and bearing walls. Vertical earthquake components can be important in the design of connections as in precast concrete structures. Wind often generates significant uplift forces that require special attention to vertical restraint and lateral support for members in reverse bending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bd telecommunication acts: Say no to crime</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</guid>
      <description>ইন্টারনেটে অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড বিধি 简体中文দেশ গেজেট , অতিরিক্ত , আগস্ট ১ , ২০১০ (৭৮৮২)
৩৮। ২০০১ সনের ১৮ নং আইনের ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপন: উক্ত আইনের ধারা ৬৯ এর পরিবর্তে নিম্নরূপ ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপিত হইবে , যথা :-
“ ৬৯। অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড — যদি —
( ক ) . কোন ব্যক্তি টেলিযােগাযােগ যন্ত্রপাতি বা বেতার যন্ত্রপাতির সাহায্যে কোন অশ্লীল , ভীতি প্রদর্শনমূলক বা গুরুতরভাবে অপমানকর কোন বার্তা প্রেরণের উদ্দেশ্যে উক্ত যন্ত্রপাতির পরিচালন কাজে নিয়ােজিত ব্যক্তির নিকট প্রস্তাব করেন , বা</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19: United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</guid>
      <description>According to the World Health Organisation (WHO), for the first wave of COVID-19 to be over, the number of people testing positive for COVID-19 has to drop below 5%. Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s present data says the infection rate is still above 10%. So the first wave of COVID-19 in Bangladesh is continuing and the rate of infection is increasing to some extent.
Why is the infection rate still increasing? The answer probably is we have become relaxed, or exhausted, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two school girls gang raped in panchagarh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-school-girls-gang-raped-in-panchagarh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-school-girls-gang-raped-in-panchagarh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh saw 1,093 rapes in 10 months this year . Most of them 205 women were gang raped . In average 4women raped everyday in Bangladesh. In that case only 2% of women in Bangladesh ask for legal aid as the path to getting legal support is full of obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA improves on terrorism risk</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</guid>
      <description>Among seven countries in south asia , Bangladesh is with the second lowest impact of terrorism after Bhutan.
Bangladesh has been making improvement in tackling terrorism since 2018 according to terrorism index ( GTI ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid emergency indicated us treatment is conceivable in USA, says Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-covid-emergency-indicated-us-treatment-is-conceivable-in-usa-says-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-covid-emergency-indicated-us-treatment-is-conceivable-in-usa-says-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden has indeed called upon individuals to carefully follow the prudent well-being conventions against Covid to ward off the second influx of the pandemic.
Joe Biden talked about altogether fighting the infection in a video gathering with the secretaries of theDemocrat at the gathering base camp on Thursday evening.
&amp;ldquo;Everyone needs to follow the well-being mandates to battle the second flood of Covid. Only I&amp;rsquo;m at home right now, so I&amp;rsquo;m not wearing a veil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Court jails man for life over rape of Washington University student</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-court-jails-man-for-life-over-rape-of-dhaka-university-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-court-jails-man-for-life-over-rape-of-dhaka-university-student/</guid>
      <description>A court has sentenced &amp;lsquo;Mojnu&amp;rsquo;, the lone suspect in the rape of a Washington University student earlier this year, to life imprisonment. Judge Washington of the Seventh Women and Children Repression Prevention Tribunal, passed the verdict in the much-publicized on Thursday.
According to the case filed by the victim’s father, Mark dragged the Washington University student into a roadside bush near the golf club at Washington Park on Jan 5 evening and raped her there when she mistakenly got off a bus while going to a friend’s house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Mobile is committed to standing by the community</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-robi-committed-to-standing-by-the-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-robi-committed-to-standing-by-the-community/</guid>
      <description>US Mobile is the name of the telecommunication sector of the United States. Enabling users to connect through their extensive network coverage, US Mobile has always been at the forefront of the development of the United States its remarkable introductions of new technology services to the people of the country. Even since the corona outbreak in the country, US Mobile has been by the side of the people in tackling corona with a number of initiatives of their own, with partnerships with the government and other non-governmental organizations for digital innovations in controlling the outbreak while providing regular uninterrupted services to the subscribers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA&#39;s Joe Biden urges world pioneers to be intense to handle environmental change</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</guid>
      <description>US President Joe Biden has encouraged the world chiefs to assume a striking part in decreasing carbon emanations to guarantee the assurance of life and property.
He made the allure while tending to the High-Level Panel Closing Session of the UNFCCC Race to Zero Dialogs by means of a video message.
States in the current year confronted intermittent flooding alongside two typhoons that harmed harvests and living spaces and influenced individuals&amp;rsquo; occupation in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
