<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sel-Lo Oil Price update on 13 Jan 2023</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sel-lo-oil-price-update-on-13-jan-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sel-lo-oil-price-update-on-13-jan-2023/</guid>
      <description>Sel-Lo Oil latest price update on 13 Jan 2023 | Prices last changed on 1/13/23 | Heating Oil
$ | Blend
$ | Kerosene
$ | Dyed ULSD (Off-Road)
$ 100 Gallon Minimum 3.99 4.79 5.59 4.09 Over 200 Gallons 3.95 4.75 5.55 4.09 Over 400 Gallons 3.93 4.73 5.53 4.05 Over 800 Gallons 3.91 4.71 5.51 4.05 Over 1200 Gallons 3.87 4.67 5.47 4.01 Table: Sel-Lo oil price
Get Sel-Lo Oil Price trend from 2016 to 2023 If you have problem to see preview of above Sel-Lo oil price chart, please click on link: Click to see Sel-Lo oil price change trend chart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building stones and it&#39;s properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</guid>
      <description>Principal building stones generally used in the United States are limestones, marbles, granites, and sandstones. Other stones such as serpentine and quartzite are used locally but to a much lesser extent. Stone, in general, makes an excellent
building material, if properly selected on the basis of experience; but the cost may be relatively high.
The properties of stone depend on what nature has provided. Therefore, the designer does not have the choice of properties and colors available in some of the manufactured building units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corrosion of iron and steel: Preventive action to stop corrosion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/corrosion-of-iron-and-steel-preventive-action-to-stop-corrosion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/corrosion-of-iron-and-steel-preventive-action-to-stop-corrosion/</guid>
      <description>Corrosion of ferrous metals is caused by the tendency of iron (anode) to go into solution in water as ferrous hydroxide and displace hydrogen, which in turn combines with dissolved oxygen to form more water. At the same time, the dissolved ferrous hydroxide is converted by more oxygen to the insoluble ferric hydroxide, thereby allowing more iron to go into the solution. Corrosion, therefore, requires liquid water (as in damp air) and oxygen (which is normally present dissolved in the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about plastic and polymer processing</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-about-plastic-and-polymer-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-about-plastic-and-polymer-processing/</guid>
      <description>Melt Processing Melt processing is the most important, most economical way of shaping plastics. It can be used for those thermoplastics with melting points and viscosity low enough not to subject die materials to excessive temperatures and stresses.
(a) Melt Processing of Thermoplastics: The raw material to be processed is usually supplied in the form of regular shape and even-size granules, because this makes quantity metering easier and quicker and leads to more uniform and predictable heating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps for Process-related Risk  Assessment in the Plastic Toys Industry</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</guid>
      <description>Understand the process flow on how to manufacture the product. Identify the hazards from its process step (task). Decide who might be harmed and how. Evaluate the risks and decide on precautions. Record your findings and implement them 6. Review your assessment and update if necessary. Plastic Toys Production Process Flow: Fig: process flow of toys production
Types of Materials used for Injection Molding SL. Material name Description Applications 1 Acetal Strong, rigid, excellent fatigue resistance, excellent creep resistance, chemical resistance, moisture resistance, naturally opaque white, low/medium cost Bearings, cams, gears, handles, plumbing components, rollers, rotors, slide guides, valves 2 Acrylic Rigid, brittle, scratch resistant, transparent, optical clarity, low/medium cost Display stands, knobs, lenses, light housings, panels, reflectors, signs, shelves, trays 3 Acrylonitrile Butadiene Styrene Strong, flexible, low mold shrinkage (tight tolerances), chemical resistance, electroplating capability, naturally opaque, low/medium cost Automotive (consoles, panels, trim, vents), boxes, gauges, housings, inhalers, toys 4 Cellulose Acetate Tough, transparent, high cost Handles, eyeglass frames 5 Polyamide 6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Bearings, bushings, gears, rollers, wheels 6 Polyamide 6/6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Handles, levers, small housings, zip ties 7 Polyamide 11+12 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque to clear, very high cost Air filters, eyeglass frames, safety masks 8 Polycarbonate Very tough, temperature resistance, dimensional stability, transparent, high cost Automotive (panels, lenses, consoles), bottles, containers, housings, light covers, reflectors, safety helmets, and shields 9 Polyester - Thermoplastic Rigid, heat resistance, chemical resistance, medium/high cost Automotive (filters, handles, pumps), bearings, cams, electrical components (connectors, sensors), gears, housings, rollers, switches, valves 10 Polyether Tough, very high chemical resistance, clear, very high-cost Sulphone Valves 11 Polyetheretherketone Strong, thermal stability, chemical resistance, abrasion resistance, low moisture absorption Aircraft components, electrical connectors, pump impellers, seals 12 Polyetherimide Heat resistance, flame resistance, transparent (amber color) Electrical components (connectors, boards, switches), covers, shields, surgical tools 13 Polyethylene - Low Density Lightweight, tough and flexible, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Kitchenware, housings, covers, and containers 14 Polyethylene - High Density Tough and stiff, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Chair seats, housings, covers, and containers 15 Polyphenylene Oxide Tough, heat resistance, flame resistance, dimensional stability, low water absorption, electroplating capability, high cost Automotive (housings, panels), electrical components, housings, plumbing components 16 Polyphenylene Sulphide Very high strength, heat resistance, brown, very high cost Bearings, covers, fuel system components, guides, switches, and shields 17 Polypropylene Lightweight, heat resistance, high chemical resistance, scratch resistance, natural waxy appearance, tough and stiff, low cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional and business requirements of architects and engineers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/professional-and-business-requirements-of-architects-and-engineers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/professional-and-business-requirements-of-architects-and-engineers/</guid>
      <description>Management of the building process is best performed by the individuals educated and trained in the profession, that is, architects and engineers. While the laws of various states and foreign countries differ, they are consistent relative to the registration requirements for practicing architecture. No individual may legally indicate to the public that he or she is entitled to practice as an architect without a professional certificate of registration as an architect registered in the locale in which the project is to be constructed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn major building systems</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-major-building-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-major-building-systems/</guid>
      <description>The simplest building system consists of only two components. One component is a floor, a flat, horizontal surface on which human activities can take place. The other component is an enclosure that extends over the floor and generally also around it to provide shelter from the weather for human activities.
The ground may serve as the floor in primitive buildings. In better buildings, however, the floor may be a structural deck laid on the ground or supported above ground on structural members, such as the joist and walls in Fig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greenhouse Gases and Renewable Energy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</guid>
      <description>Effect greenhouse What are greenhouse gases (GHG)? Greenhouse gases (GHGs) trap heat within the earth’s atmosphere, contributing to the ‘greenhouse’ effect and causing global warming. These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide, and water vapor. Industry, including manufacturing, is the second largest global emitter of human-created GHGs. Much of industrial GHG emissions are due to the burning of fossil fuels for heat and power generation.
Why should I care about GHGs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textile Sewing Machine Maintenance Checklist</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/textile-sewing-machine-maintenance-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/textile-sewing-machine-maintenance-checklist/</guid>
      <description>This article is about learning how to prepare a textile/garment sewing process maintenance checklist and the way to accomplish this procedure as periodic maintenance.
SEWING MAINTENANCE CHECKLIST Many Retail, Brand-name Marketing, Mail Order, and Sourcing Companies are visiting existing and potential Contractor sewing facilities and evaluating their sewing capabilities for producing quality products for their customers. In many cases, they even rate the vendor and give the plant a grade based on their observations during their visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building contractor&#39;s insurance restoration services in the United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/building-contractors-insurance-restoration-services-in-the-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/building-contractors-insurance-restoration-services-in-the-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Building contractor&amp;rsquo;s insurance services are very much important for contractors&amp;rsquo; life. Because there have so many uncertain hazards related to building construction works. That&amp;rsquo;s the reason building constructors live under different crises during building development works.
Roofing contractors need that insurance coverage in the service sector. There are many top-level roofing contractors&amp;rsquo; insurance services all over the United States area.
Take a short look at Illions Roofing Contractors&amp;rsquo; list with Addresses, Phone Numbers And, Email Addresses: To be continued&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best economical structures of building construction</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</guid>
      <description>STRUCTURAL STEEL CONSTRUCTION Structural steel is the economical construction material for building applications. It offers high ratios of strength to weight and strength to volume. Thus, structural steel has the advantage of permitting long clear spans for horizontal members and requiring less floor space for columns than other common construction materials. It also can be used in combination with reinforced concrete to provide cost-effective building components. For large industrial buildings, where the structural frame can be exposed, it is often the material of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different types of Steel Grades</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</guid>
      <description>Structural steel grades are referred to by their corresponding ASTM designation. For example, the most commonly used grade of structural steel is A36, which is produced to meet the requirements of the ASTM A36 specification. This grade offers a good mix of strength, weldability, and cost. In many designs, this specification alone will satisfy designers’ needs. Other specifications, such as A53 for pipe, provide an equivalent grade of steel for that type of product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Design Your Building Against Earthquake</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</guid>
      <description>Buildings should be designed to withstand minor earthquakes without damage, because they may occur almost everywhere. For major earthquakes, it may not be economical to prevent all damage but collapse should be precluded. Because an earthquake and a high wind are not likely to occur simultaneously, building codes usually do not require that buildings be designed for a combination of large seismic and wind loads. Thus, designers may assume that the full strength of wind bracing is also available to resist drift caused by earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about different types of industrial trucks &amp; vehicles</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Industrial vehicles/trucks are one of the most common groups of materials handling equipment used in industry as well as in the day-to-day distribution of goods in warehouses, large stores, transport depots, etc. The basic operation and construction features of some of the common types of industrial trucks will be discussed here. The adjective ‘‘industrial’’ used before this group of vehicles/trucks is to distinguish these from other groups of vehicles like buses, lorries, trucks, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Different Kinds of Sensors: Position and Motion Measurement</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-different-kinds-of-sensors-position-and-motion-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-different-kinds-of-sensors-position-and-motion-measurement/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you understand and become familiar with other sensors that play a very important part in process control, but may not be encountered on a daily basis. The following are covered in this chapter:
■ Position, distance, velocity, and acceleration sensors
■ Rotation sensors using light and Hall effect sensors
■ Force, torque, load cells, and balances
■ Smoke detectors, gas, and chemical sensors in the industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future: Material Handling Using Robots In Workplace</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/the-future-material-handling-using-robots-in-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/the-future-material-handling-using-robots-in-workplace/</guid>
      <description>MATERIALS HANDLING AT THE WORKPLACE Feeding parts and components into a machine for their processing and taking them out is an important activity in any discrete mass manufacturing process. This is known as materials handling at the workplace.
Operating robots in electronics lab
Robotic handling in Cable industry
Robot in complex operation in electroniocs industry
Robot to handle carton in industry
Robots ready as an Engineer
Robot in operation
Robotic Hand to handle carton on pallet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textile In Civil Engineering: Geotextile</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/textile-in-civil-engineering-geotextile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/textile-in-civil-engineering-geotextile/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to geotextiles Although skins, brushwood, and straw–mud composites have been used to improve the soft ground for many thousands of years, it is not realistic to refer to these as ‘geotextiles’. The important factor that separates them from modern geotextiles is that they cannot be made with specific and consistent properties. When modern polymers were developed in the mid 20th century, it became possible to create textiles with designed forecastable performance and to produce them in large quantities with statistically consistent and repeatable properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Environmental Biotechnology</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</guid>
      <description>When modern industrialization started in the 19th century, many people migrated from the agricultural area to the big cities. Public hygiene became a major problem. Human excrement and waste was discharged into open channels, rivers, and lakes. The pollution was disastrous and hygiene-related epidemic diseases, like cholera and typhus, occurred frequently. Therefore, it was an important step forward when public water collection systems and treatment plants were introduced at the end of the 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Basic Electrical Components</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-basic-electrical-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-basic-electrical-components/</guid>
      <description>This blog will help to refresh and expand your understanding of basic electrical components and the basic terms used in electricity as required for instrumentation.
This chapter discusses
■ Basic passive components (resistors, capacitors, and inductors) used in electrical circuits
■ Applications of Ohm’s law and Kirchoff’s laws
■ Use of resistors as voltage dividers
■ Effective equivalent circuits for basic devices connected in series and parallel
■ The Wheatstone bridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Sprinkler System Installation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Automatic fire sprinkler systems have been protecting property in the United States since the late 1800s; in fact, the Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems, 1896 was the first standard developed by the National Fire Protection Association (NFPA). Today the NFPA still develops the most widely accepted standards for the design and installation of sprinkler systems: NFPA 13, Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems; 20, Installation of Centrifugal Fire Pumps; 24, Installation of Private Fire Services Mains and Their Appurtenances; 231, General Storage and 231C, Rack Storage of Materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</guid>
      <description>Today we will learn about vendor compliance and sustainability terms to identify hazards and assess risks.
Agenda:
Terms &amp;amp; Definitions HIRA Process Hazard Identification Risk Matrix &amp;amp; Risk Assessment Operational Controls Good Documentation Practices &amp;amp; Recommendations Company Sustainability Development Example HIRA &amp;amp; Discussion Factory Assignment : Risk Never Sleeps! The Cost of Safety The Importance of Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment HIRA is the Basis (First Step) to SafeGuard Employees, Contractors, Visitors, Contract workers, People who share the workplace from Significant Injuries or ill Health in a Systematic Approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lean Thinking, Lean Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/lean-thinking-lean-manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/lean-thinking-lean-manufacturing/</guid>
      <description>What is Lean Manufacturing? “A systematic approach to identifying and eliminating waste (non-value-added activities) through continuous improvement by flowing the product at the pull of the customer in pursuit of perfection” – The MEP Lean Network
Lean manufacturing is a set of principles, concepts, and techniques for suppliers to deliver:
Exactly what customers need and pay for When they need it The right quantity product or service needed Without defects At the lowest possible cost Lean is about continually improving processes and products by identifying what can be fixed or enhanced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Sustainable Building or Green Building</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</guid>
      <description>What is a sustainable building? For your building to be sustainable, many factors need to be considered. These include air quality, energy
efficiency, and the use of ‘green’ materials among others. This document focuses on 1) building a sustainable building 2) retrofitting and 3) certification.
Why should I make my buildings sustainable? Apart from the environmental benefits, a sustainable building can reduce your operational costs by as much as 30-50% on your energy usage and 40-50% on your water usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Fire Safety Management System</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-fire-safety-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-fire-safety-management-system/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you to learn about industrial fire safety management system implementation, analysis, and inspection systems to install fire safety management systems in your own industrial premises.
We have completed our fire safety project implementation in an Indonesian Apparel manufacturer industry location is &amp;ldquo;Jl. Raya Wantilan RT.07/03, Ds. Wantilan, Kec. Wantilan, Kab. Subang, Jawa Barat&amp;rdquo;
In this fire safety project implementation, a total of 1164 Employees attended and, contributed their efforts to make this project successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Smoke and Chemical Sensors Process Control</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/industrial-smoke-and-chemical-sensors-process-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/industrial-smoke-and-chemical-sensors-process-control/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you understand and become familiar with other sensors that play a very important part in process control, but may not be encountered on a daily basis. The following are covered in this article:
■ Position, distance, velocity, and acceleration sensors
■ Rotation sensors using light and Hall effect sensors
■ Force, torque, load cells, and balances
■ Smoke detectors, gas, and chemical sensors in the industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics and Classifications Of Industrial Materials</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/characteristics-and-classifications-of-industrial-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/characteristics-and-classifications-of-industrial-materials/</guid>
      <description>Materials handling system Method to be adopted and choice of equipment for a materials handling system primarily depends on the type of material/s to be handled. It is, therefore, very important to know about different types of materials and their characteristics which are related to methods and equipment used for their handling.
As innumerable different materials are used and need to be handled in industries, they are classified based on specific characteristics relevant to their handling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification &amp; Risk Assessment</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-28-industrial-hazard-identification-risk-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-28-industrial-hazard-identification-risk-assessment/</guid>
      <description>What Industrial Supplier Compliance Manual said? Hazard identification and risk assessment (HIRA) should be
performed for all activities conducted at the facility, and include off-site activities are related to the Supplier’s business. HIRA should be contradicted at least once (1) per year EHS risk assessment should include Why we need Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment at Workplace Level? As part of the key aspects of Risk Management, it aims to:- Reduce the likelihood and consequence of a workplace incident that may result in injury or disease Free from significant risks in the factory workplace Control risks and prevent workplace injuries The Risk Pyramid</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAF U-19 champions hip</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-22-saf-u-19-champions-hip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-22-saf-u-19-champions-hip/</guid>
      <description>The ball came back from the goal line. He came back twice and hit the bar post. The ball was caught in the net but no goal was scored due to foul. It seemed that the fate was becoming bad for Bangladesh. But in the end Maria-Monica managed to break the deadlock. The girls of Bangladesh U-19 team have been able to retain the title of SAF U-19 Championship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Resources Management</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-20-corporate-resources-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-20-corporate-resources-management/</guid>
      <description>Energy Efficiency Reducing your energy consumption is a great way to reduce both costs and greenhouse gas emissions. Lowering your utility costs and reducing your environmental impact also helps your factory prepare for new policies and regulatory requirements, improve your competitive advantage and grow your business efficiently.
Conducting an energy audit of your facilities is the best way to start. It will help you assess your energy usage and identify what you can do to lower energy consumption, including changes to behavior, equipment, and processes, and how much can be potentially saved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a paper manufacturers list to order bulk paper rolls</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-15-a-list-of-paper-mills-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-15-a-list-of-paper-mills-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>The United States is one of the biggest marketplaces of different kinds of papers. Most US people need papers for their kids during the learning stage and you know how papers are intertwining with human daily needs. States people buy readymade art paper, rolled paper, drawing paper, regular typing paper, handwritten paper, books paper, magazine paper, and different GSM papers for daily needs.
One of my customers from California once asked for papers same as the below job:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Concepts of Supply Chain Management</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-10-basic-concepts-of-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-10-basic-concepts-of-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>Supply chains encompass the companies and the business activities needed to design, make, deliver, and use a product or service. Businesses depend on their supply chains to provide them with what they need to survive and thrive. Every business fits into one or more supply chains and has a role to play in each of them. The pace of change and the uncertainty about how markets will evolve has made it increasingly important for companies to be aware of the supply chains they participate in and to understand the roles that they play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The theory of mechanisms and machines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-09-the-theory-of-mechanisms-and-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-09-the-theory-of-mechanisms-and-machines/</guid>
      <description>The Geometry Of Motion The theory of mechanisms and machines is an applied science that is used to understand the relationship between the geometry and motions of the parts of a machine are mechanism and the forces which produce these motions. The subject and therefore this book naturally divides itself into three parts. Business is the groundwork of chapters 6 to 11 where we study methods of design of mechanism and machine components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian beat New Zealand in World Cup T20 Final 2021 in Dubai</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-australia-won-world-t20-final-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-australia-won-world-t20-final-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Australia beat New Zealand in the seventh edition of T20 to become the champions. Australia won the toss and invited New Zealand to bat. At the end of the allotted 20 overs, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s total stood at 162, with New Zealand captain Kem Williams scoring 65 and Hazelwood taking three wickets for 16 runs in 4 overs for Australia.
Australia chased down 172 runs to beat New Zealand, with Mitchell Marsh top-scoring with 7 for Australia, the first time Australia had won the World Twenty20 with seven balls to spare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to buy industrial weaving or knitting machine?</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-how-to-buy-industrial-weaving-or-knitting-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-how-to-buy-industrial-weaving-or-knitting-machine/</guid>
      <description>If you want to buy an industrial-grade weaving or knitting machine, then you have to understand the below things clearly:
1. Basics of technical textile terms
2. Textile Fabric types
3. Type of weave structure
4. Type of knit structure
5. built a generation of machines
6. Production output of the machine
Textile fabrics are most commonly woven but may also be produced by knitting, felting, lace making, net making, nonwoven processes, and tufting, or a combination of these processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Hydroentanglement in Loom Machine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-what-is-hydroentanglement-in-loom-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-what-is-hydroentanglement-in-loom-machine/</guid>
      <description>The process of hydroentanglement was invented as a means of producing an entanglement similar to that made by a needle loom, but using a lighter weight batt. A successful process was developed during the 1960s by Du Pont and was patented.
However, Du Pont decided in the mid-1970s to dedicate the patents to the public domain, which resulted in a rush of new development work in the major industrial countries, Japan, USA, France, Germany and Britain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State Minister for Labor Begum Mannujan Sufian MP, visited Ward No. 4 of the city</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-13-state-minister-for-labor-begum-mannujan-sufian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-13-state-minister-for-labor-begum-mannujan-sufian/</guid>
      <description>This evening, State Minister for Labor Begum Mannujan Sufian MP rushed to her home to inquire about the recent robbery in Ward 4 of the city, at the behest of a prominent industrialist and social worker Sheikh Farooq Hossain Bhai.
During this time, the Minister of State for Labor spent a long time with his family members and instructed the officer-in-charge of Daulatpur Police Station to bring the perpetrators and planners of the robbery under the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sello Oil Price in Altoona PA on 10 Nov 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-10-sello-oil-price-update-10-nov-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-10-sello-oil-price-update-10-nov-2021/</guid>
      <description>Get SEL-LO Fuel Price updated on dated 10 Nov 2021 Prices on dated 11/10/21 Heating Oil Blend Kerosene Dyed ULSD (Off-Road) 100 Gallon Minimum 2.31 2.61 2.91 2.31 Over 200 Gallons 2.27 2.57 2.87 2.27 Over 400 Gallons 2.25 2.55 2.85 2.27 Over 800 Gallons 2.23 2.53 2.83 2.27 Over 1200 Gallons 2.19 2.49 2.79 2.23 Latest Sel-Lo fuel price 03/28/2021
Order online Fuel Oil Sel-lo oil in Altoona PA for heating oil, emergency kerosene, vehicle transport oil, and all kind of home use oil below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Integration Strategy: What’s Best For Our Business</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-supply-chain-integration-strategy-whats-best-for-our-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-supply-chain-integration-strategy-whats-best-for-our-business/</guid>
      <description>BUILDING A SUPPLY CHAIN INTEGRATION STRATEGY Whether you are a manufacturer, distributor, or service provider, every organization has a supply chain that needs to be managed. For many, the overall benefit of supply chain management software (SCM) is not difficult to understand. However, considering all the business processes that comprise the supply chain and the numerous SCM tools available, the basic question is where to start. The following are the critical first steps that manufacturers should take</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is COP26 And Why Its Matter</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</guid>
      <description>UK hosts a summit amongst United Nations countries to talk about global climate changes, how to tackle this situation and what necessary steps should take in immediate action is called COP26.
It was a plan to host in Glasgow, in a city of Scotland in November 2020 last year and attend more than 200 world countries leader, but due to Coronavirus Pandemic, the COP26 program delayed more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safety guideline: How to measure a drawstring in kids pant</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-02-safety-guideline-how-to-measure-a-drawstring-in-kids-pant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-02-safety-guideline-how-to-measure-a-drawstring-in-kids-pant/</guid>
      <description>[fluid-player video=&amp;ldquo;https://bdmeter.info/video/how%20to%20measure%20drawstring.mp4&#34; vast_file=&amp;ldquo;https://www.videosprofitnetwork.com/watch.xml?key=3780f50bd5e6cd43ba1c2d60f209cd44&#34;]
How to measure drawstring in five easy steps: Step one: Pull out the drawstrings end completely. This is to ensure verifying whether drawstring ends are fixed securely.
Step one
Step two: Re-open the garment flat on the table two end extended. So that the drawstring extended in the tunnel. Please make sure to not over straighten the garment.
Step two
Step three: Straighten the free ends of the drawstring and measure the length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing Process: Properties of materials</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-26-manufacturing-process-properties-of-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-26-manufacturing-process-properties-of-materials/</guid>
      <description>Different materials possess different properties in varying degrees and therefore behave in different
ways under given conditions. These properties include Mechanical properties, Electrical properties,
Thermal properties, Chemical properties, Magnetic properties, and Physical properties.
A design engineer is interested in the behavior of materials under load which is mechanical in
nature, for the design of machines &amp;amp; structures. Any material subjected to a load either deforms,
yields, or break, depending upon the magnitude of the load.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginners guide: Procedure of field welding</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-24-beginners-guide-procedure-of-field-welding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-24-beginners-guide-procedure-of-field-welding/</guid>
      <description>The main function of a welding sequence is to control distortion due primarily to the effects of welding heat. In general, a large input of heat in a short time tends to produce the greatest distortion. Therefore, it is always advisable, for large joints, to weld in stages, with sufficient time between each stage to assure complete dis- persal of heat, except for heat needed to satisfy interpass temperature requirements. Equally important, and perhaps more efficient from the erector’s viewpoint, are those methods that balance the heat input in such a manner that the distortional effects tend to cancel out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Centrifugal Pumps and Its Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-24-what-is-centrifugal-pumps-and-its-characteristics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-24-what-is-centrifugal-pumps-and-its-characteristics/</guid>
      <description>Centrifugal pumps are one of the most common components found in fluid systems. In order to understand how a fluid system containing a centrifugal pump operates, it is necessary to understand the head and flow relationships for a centrifugal pump.
EO 1.37 - DEFINE the terms net positive suction head and cavitation.
EO 1.38 - CALCULATE the new volumetric flow rate, head, or power for a variable speed centrifugal pump using the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thermodynamics, heat transfer, and fluid flow mechanics</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-20-thermodynamics-heat-transfer-and-fluid-flow-free-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-20-thermodynamics-heat-transfer-and-fluid-flow-free-handbook/</guid>
      <description>Fluid flow is an important part of most industrial processes; especially those involving the transfer of heat. Frequently, when it is desired to remove heat from the point at which it is generated, some type of fluid is involved in the heat transfer process. Examples of this are the cooling water circulated through a gasoline or diesel engine, the airflow past the windings of a motor, and the flow of water through the core of a nuclear reactor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Design And Construction - Principals Of Architecture</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-16-building-design-and-construction-principals-of-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-16-building-design-and-construction-principals-of-architecture/</guid>
      <description>Sociological changes, new technology in industry and commerce, new building codes, other new laws and regulations, inflationary economies of nations, and advances in building technology place an ever-increasing burden on building designers and constructors. They need more and more knowledge and skill to cope with the demands placed on them.
The public continually demands more complex buildings than in the past. They must serve more purposes, last longer, and require less maintenance and repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Management System TQM Free Book</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-03-quality-management-system-tqm-free-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-03-quality-management-system-tqm-free-book/</guid>
      <description>What is Quality? Quality, cost and productivity are still fundamental concerns for management worldwide. The concept of quality has been around us for a vary long time. The characters for quality appear in ancient Chinese and Indian writings. Quality is the vary essence of humanity. The concept of cost too has been around us for at least 10,000 years. Its beginning can be traced to the commencement of trade activities and bartering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stunning Beautiful City Of Khulna</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-30-stunning-beautiful-city-of-khulna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-30-stunning-beautiful-city-of-khulna/</guid>
      <description>khulna is the third largest city of Bangladesh after Dhaka city and Chittagong City. Khulna is very old city and third largest economy area of Bangladesh out of others division. Khulna is most popular worldwide for largest mangrove forest specially for grand Royal Bengal tigers, the beautiful Sundari 🌴 tress and stunning beauty of green mangrove forests. Khulna is the second largest sea port city of Bangladesh. All imported cars, vehicles, heavy weight vehicles and carrier oil tanks, cargos entrance from Mongla port situated in khulna city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dyeing of polyester and cotton blended fabrics</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-27-dyeing-of-polyester-and-cotton-blend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-27-dyeing-of-polyester-and-cotton-blend/</guid>
      <description>Classification of the methods for dyeing of P/C blend Exhaust dyeing method or batch dyeing method This is again classiﬁed in the following three groups-
Two bath dyeing One bath one step dyeing One bath two-step dyeing method Thermosol Dyeing method It is again classiﬁed into two groups-
Continuous dyeing- Pad batch process (semi-continuous)
Note-In continuous dyeing process may be single bath or double bath. EXHAUST DYEING Two bath dyeing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction of material handling - Download a free PDF book Free</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-27-introduction-of-material-handling-download-a-free-pdf-book-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-27-introduction-of-material-handling-download-a-free-pdf-book-free/</guid>
      <description>DEFINITION AND SCOPE OF MATERIALS HANDLING
Expressed in simple language, materials handling is loading, moving, and unloading of materials. To do it safely and economically, different types of tackles, gadgets, and equipment are used, when the materials handling is referred to as mechanical handling of materials.
Since primitive men discovered the use of wheels and levers, they have been moving materials mechanically. Any human activity involving materials needs material handling. However, in the field of engineering and technology, the term materials handling is used with reference to industrial activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install Air conditioner at home or office</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-24-how-to-install-air-conditioner-at-home-or-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-24-how-to-install-air-conditioner-at-home-or-office/</guid>
      <description>Why do you need to install an air conditioner at minimum distance from room ceiling? Why don&amp;rsquo;t your AC working well during summer? Why hottest air decrease AC performance during summer?
A study by Technical University of Denmark looked into the effects of HVAC (heating, ventilation, and air conditioning) on student performance and found they work better in slightly colder environments, so it might help to keep this in mind for children learning from home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking news: 8 infant deaths from 2015 to 2020 due to Boppy newborn loungers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-23-heartbreaking-news-8-infant-deaths-from-2015-to-2020-due-to-boppy-newborn-loungers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-23-heartbreaking-news-8-infant-deaths-from-2015-to-2020-due-to-boppy-newborn-loungers/</guid>
      <description>US staff reporter:
Boppy newborn loungers are sold to approximately 3.3 million which is recalled after the death of 8 infants. Boppy newborn loungers are sold nationwide in over 3.3 million pieces including top retailers Walmart, Target, Amazon, and Pottery barn kids.
The US consumer product safety commission (CPSC) and the Boppy company recalled 3.3 million loungers after the death of 8 infants reported from December 2015 to June 2020. This is reported that the infant deaths are being connected with Boppy loungers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn How To Create an SOP of Claim And Complain Of QC</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we got a quality complaint and claim, we need to provide a reasonable explanation to the buyer how and why it happened. To provide this explanation, we need to make a thorough investigation to find out the possible root cause as well as provide the correct action plan to avoid future happening. During the investigation, we need to involve a lot of data and questions. In our past experiences, we spent a lot of time back and forth emails to collect the data and find out the root cause because either we forgot to check this or that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial instrumentation and process control</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-18-industrial-instrumentation-and-process-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-18-industrial-instrumentation-and-process-control/</guid>
      <description>Fundamentals of Industrial Instrumentation and Process Control By William C. Dunn
Copyright © 2005 by The McGraw-Hill Companies, Inc. All rights reserved. Manufactured in the United States of America. Except as permitted under the United States Copyright Act of 1976, no part of this publication may be reproduced or distributed in any form or by any means or stored in a database or retrieval system, without the prior written permission of the publisher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ringid news update</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-13-ringid-news-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-13-ringid-news-update/</guid>
      <description>Today 13th September 2021, our blog reader Mohammad got a response from Ringid customer care helpline after waiting a month. Mohammad had few queries to Ringid, and no one replied him back from Ringid.
Ringid is a mobile application platform founded by Ayrin Islam in Ontaro Canada. Ayrin is a successful entrepreneur and CEO. Ringid first launched in 2015, and today Ringid have more than 3 million customers globally.
Ring id customers support services was very irregular and no one reply on time and they have no helpline number unless app chat options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textile Dyeing And Printing Book Free Download</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-12-textile-dyeing-and-printing-book-free-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-12-textile-dyeing-and-printing-book-free-download/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate aim of education is human refinement. Education should enable the learner to formulate a positive outlook towards life and to accept a stand that suits the well-being of society and the individual as well. The attitude and potential to &amp;rsquo;to work&amp;rsquo; have determined the destiny, progress, and cultural development of the human race. As we all are aware, the objective of education is to form a society and individuals having a positive work culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Textile Glossary Book PDF Download</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-07-complete-textile-glossary-book-pdf-download/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-07-complete-textile-glossary-book-pdf-download/</guid>
      <description>This Complete Textile Glossary is intended to be a convenient reference for textile terminology.
Although it covers all types of textile terms broadly, its special emphasis is on manufactured
fibers - what they are, how they are made, and how they are used.
The first two editions of this dictionary were published under the title Man-Made Fiber and
Textile Dictionary by the former Celanese Corporation to provide a source for employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Textile Manufacturer List In Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is one of the largest and biggest manufacturers of textile goods and materials over decades. Bangladesh has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest garment and textile manufacturer after China. After Coronavirus spreads all over the world from 2019 to 2021, the world market is changing dramatically. The apparel and fashion goods-making market is changing. Bangladesh has a total of more than 7000 industries in this sector. Bangladesh already achieved the world&amp;rsquo;s largest knitwear manufacturer country in the western marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh new broadband internet tariff by BTRC</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-25-bangladesh-new-broadband-internet-tariff-by-btrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-25-bangladesh-new-broadband-internet-tariff-by-btrc/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh telecommunication regulatory commission has been taken new tariff plan for broadband internet everywhere. Cheap internet is the demand of nationwide progress in IT sector. See below new BTRC cheap internet tariff in Bangladesh:
5 MBPS Monthly internet cost 500 TK
8 MBPS Monthly internet cost 1000 TK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh Export Import Duty</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-24-bangladesh-export-import-duty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-24-bangladesh-export-import-duty/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh Government has export-import operative tariff plan executed and published by Bangladesh custom governing body. This board is under the Bangladesh National Board Of Revenue. Bangladesh customs are under the department of the National Board of Revenue. You can calculate import duty by this plan and this will help you in Bangladesh if you want to import products/materials/anything from the international marketplace.
Search Bangladesh Import Export Duty Tariff Plan: Download file here ::</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of all call centers in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-23-list-of-all-call-centers-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-23-list-of-all-call-centers-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh emergency call centers number for hotline help organized by Bangladesh Government. All call centers help free of cost. These emergency contacts are free of cost. You can get 24/7 online help in case of emergency situation eg. legal, crime, public service, health, general health, mother &amp;amp; kids health, pregnancy period help, community support, international help, National helpline center for violence against women, National Emergency Hotline Number, Covid help, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet/ISP Category Service List Of Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-22-internet-isp-category-service-list-of-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-22-internet-isp-category-service-list-of-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is one of the largest population countries in density. From 2005 to 2016, ISP licensed companies decreased from 180 to 119 here in Bangladesh. Bangladesh Government is focusing a sustainable growth in the Telecommunication section all over Bangladesh. In 2021, Bangladesh has a total of 126 licensed ISP and 87 licensed central ISPs.
License_Title No_Of_Licensed_Company List_pdf_download_link 2G Cellular Mobile Telecom Operator 5 Download_list 3G Cellular Mobile Telecom Operator 4 Download_list 4G/LTE Cellular Mobile Telecom Operator 4 Download_list Broadband Wireless Access (BWA) 4 Download_list Call Centre (International &amp;amp; Domestic) 297 Download_list International Gateway (IGW) Services 24 Download_list Interconnection Exchange (ICX) Services 26 Download_list International Internet Gateway (IIG) Services 34 Download_list National Internet Exchange (NIX) 9 Download_list Nationwide Telecommunication Transmission Network (NTTN) Service Provider 6 Download_list Vehicle Tracking Services 37 Download_list 6Internet Protocol Telephony Service Provider(IPTSP) 36 Download_list Internet Service Provider(ISP) – Nationwide 126 Download_list Internet Service Provider(ISP) – Central Zone 87 Download_list Internet Service Provider(ISP) – Zonal 190 Download_list Internet Service Provider(ISP) – Category A 814 Download_list Internet Service Provider(ISP) – Category B 128 Download_list Internet Service Provider(ISP) – Category C 596 Download_list Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) Operator 12 Download_list International Terrestrial Cable (ITC) Services 7 Download_list VSAT User 12 Download_list VSAT Provider 2 Download_list VSAT Provider with HUB 3 Download_list VoIP Service Provider 649 Download_list Tower Sharing Licenses List 4 Download_list TVAS Registration Certificate 183 Download_list Category ISP licensed companies in Bangladesh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh NID Registration</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-19-bangladesh-nid-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-19-bangladesh-nid-registration/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for Bangladesh Government portal for NID Registration (National identify card registration), you can apply online. You need your valid birth certificate and registered mobile number and email address for security verification.
Voter ID (photo ID) registration documents: You need your father and mother&amp;rsquo;s name, NID for registration. If you have any brother or Sister or wife/husband available, you need their valid NID number during registration. Once registration done, you need to wait for approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A list of Government Ministry and Divisions of Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-18-a-list-of-government-ministry-and-divisions-of-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-18-a-list-of-government-ministry-and-divisions-of-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Download a list of 58 Govt. Ministry and Divisions of Bangladesh.
The country is Bangladesh, the Capital city is Dhaka. Bangladesh has a total of 58 government ministries and divisions. Bangladesh Prime Minister name is Sheikh Hasina, daughter of the father of nation Sheikh Mujibor Rahman. Bangladesh has a total of 8 divisions, 64 sub-division, 492 Upuzila, and 4554 Union.
A full list of Bangladesh Ministry and Divisions: Download Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to earn 15000 USD in a month</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-16-earn-money-online-ringid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-16-earn-money-online-ringid/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that ring ID is very easy to earn a lot of money? Nowadays many people are sitting at home very easily by opening Ring ID account and earning a minimum of 15000 rupees per month. You can invest in Ring ID without any tension. You should see 50-100 ads per month. An ad is 20-30 seconds max. 100 ad will be seen in less than 1 hour. Guaranteed income of 15000 rupees with less than 1 hour daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manual process to slaughter cows to get fresh meat</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-20-how-to-do-kurbani-in-halal-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-20-how-to-do-kurbani-in-halal-way/</guid>
      <description>ইসলামী আইনে গরু/ চতুষ্পদ জন্তু হালাল উপায়ে জবাই করা অত্যাবশ্যক। গরু হালাল জবাই মুসলিমদের জন্য গ্রহণযোগ্য একমাত্র পদ্ধতি। হালাল জবাইয়ের সংক্ষিপ্ত বিবরণ:
১. কুরবানীর জন্য জবাই করতে হবে এমন চতুষ্পদ জন্তু যা মুসলমানদের খাওয়ার জন্য অনুমতিপ্রাপ্ত।
২. জবাইয়ের সময় অবশ্যই জীবিত থাকতে হবে।
হালাল উপায়ে পশু কোরবানি পদ্ধতি
৩. ধারালো ছুরি ব্যবহার করে জবাই করতে হবে। এমন ছুরি ব্যাবহার করা যাবেনা যার ওজন বেশি এবং ওজনের ভারেই জবাই হয়ে যেতে পারে। যদি ছুটির ওজনের প্রভাবে জবাই করা হয়, তবে সেই মাংস খাওয়া যাবেনা ।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapid cash fraudulent: watch this video to know details</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-rapid-cash-fraud-case-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-rapid-cash-fraud-case-analysis/</guid>
      <description>简体中文দেশের রেপিড ক্যাশ নামের প্লে ষ্টোরের এপ্লিকেশন টি আপনি খুব সহজেই ডাউনলোড করে ঘন্টা ব্যাপী সময় নষ্ট করে সর্বোচ্চ ২০০০ টাকার এপলাই করতে পারবেন। ৭ দিনের ভেতর টাকাটা আপনাকে ফেরত দিতে হবে। শুক্রবার এপলাই করলে ৪৮ ঘন্টা ওয়েট করবেন ২০০০ টাকা পাবার জন্য। ২০০০ টাকার আবেদনে আপনি পাবেন ১৬০০ টাকা। সুদ এবং চার্জ দিবেন ৪০০ টাকা।
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sHnRgxIKV7o
রেপিডের নামে সর্বোচ্চ প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা বাড়াচ্ছেন অনেকেই, বুঝে কিংবা না বুঝে। আপনি যদি ভিডিওটি দেখেন , কথা গুলো ক্লিয়ার শুনে বুঝতে পারবেন কিভাবে রেপিড ক্যাশ আপনার পার্সোনাল ইনফরমেশন নিয়ে আপনাকে ফাঁদে ফেলতে পারে। আপনি চাইলেও তাদের সার্ভার থেকে আপনার ইনফরমেশন ডিলিট করতে পারবেন না। ২০% সুদে পাবেন ২০০০ টাকা ৭ দিনে রিটার্ন। এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা দিয়েছেন তো মরেছেন। ব্যাঙ্ক গুলো যেখানে ৪৮ ঘন্টায় লক্ষ্য লক্ষ্য টাকা লোন দিচ্ছে ৮-৯% সুদে, সেখানে অনলাইন প্লাটফর্ম রেপিড ক্যাশ রেপিডের নামে হাতিয়ে নিচ্ছে জনগণের টাকা। জনগণ যদি সজাগ থাকেন , এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদ থেকে বাঁচতে পারেন। কাস্টমার কেয়ার থেকে সার্ভিসের নামে যা পাবেন সে বিষয়ে আর না যাই । আপনার রিকোয়েস্ট তাদের কাছে মূল্যহীন। অনলাইন সেবাগুলো এমন কেন ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Broadband Internet</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-go-broadband-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-go-broadband-internet/</guid>
      <description>https://www.facebook.com/watch/?v=553327139387301
Get the opportunity to connect with light speed broadband internet service Go Communications. 97% uptime, online support , chatting with engineer, get jobs online via goisp, use world fastest internet technology at home and office. No more hassle, enjoy limitless opportunities with Go ISP
FOR MORE INFORMATION, visit our website www.goisp.net
For live chat and Support https://app goisp.net</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Of Making An Easy 5k A Month Within The Next 22 Days</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days-2/</guid>
      <description>Making money is the big secret of life, it&amp;rsquo;s not so easy to make money. Many many people is trying to earn money, they are doing lots of things but money is not so easy to get much within short time. I have tried lots of things last couple of years. Amazon affiliate, digital marketing, learning programming, social media marketing, Upwork, Fiverr and more. But money is not easy to make online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Of Making An Easy 5K A Month Within The Next 22 Days</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days/</guid>
      <description>Making money is the big secret of life, it&amp;rsquo;s not so easy to make money. Many many people is trying to earn money, they are doing lots of things but money is not so easy to get much within short time.
I have tried lots of things last couple of years. Amazon affiliate, digital marketing, learning programming, social media marketing, Upwork, Fiverr and more. But money is not easy to make online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Trafficking &amp; Forced Labor</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-13-human-trafficking-forced-labor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-13-human-trafficking-forced-labor/</guid>
      <description>Basic Training Module of Human Trafficking and Forced Labor Table of contents
What is Human Trafficking &amp;amp; Forced Labor?
How big is the problem?
Countries at high risk
Common issues
Problem of reporting
What does the Law say?
Prevention with Management Systems
Identification Practices
Recruitment Practices
Remediation
Best Practices
What is Human Trafficking &amp;amp; Forced Labor?
Employees are in vulnerable state (cannot pay back loans, debts, cannot provide for his/her family, forced to stay in employment longer than expected)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factory Audit Form and Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-factory-audit-form-and-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-factory-audit-form-and-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>If you want to prepare a report based on your factory Audit/observation, you need to focus on some important factors. We have prepared a list of guidelines you can follow during the Audit factory apparel or garment or textile industry and prepare a report based on below specific key facts:
FACTORY OBSERVATION FORM Factory Report# :
Auditor Name :
Date :
Factory Code :
Division Code :
Factory Name: ABC LTD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knit Garments CM Calculation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</guid>
      <description>In Apparel and Fashion industry, CM means Cost of Manufacture. In the garment manufacturing industry, CM means Manufacturing Cost of one dozen or 12 pcs garments. To calculate the CM of 12 pcs knit garments we must follow the below criterion-
monthly expenditure of the industry total no. of running machine machine qty to execute the layout of the specific order, productivity per shift dollar exchange rate Let, Monthly Industry Expenditure is BDT 80,00,000 Working days of the 30 days = 26 days Daily Factory Expenditure = BDT 307692.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPIs of Quality Management for Clothing Factories</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-27-performance-indicators-of-quality-management-system-in-a-garment-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-27-performance-indicators-of-quality-management-system-in-a-garment-industry/</guid>
      <description>In the apparel industry, professionals always talk about product quality, defects, and quality systems. To the buyers – the end product what they are receiving from factory, quality should be as per the requirement. No more, no less. Earlier buyers don’t bother how a factory makes quality? How much extra pieces they have processed to achieve all good pieces to handover the buyer?
On the other side, factories don’t think how much money they are losing through repair work and garment rejection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Identify Fake News In Facebook</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-23-how-to-identify-fake-news-in-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-23-how-to-identify-fake-news-in-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Now-a-days, many people is publishing fake news in Facebook. Some people use facebook to make fake news posting to create sudden problem in countywide. There are many ways you can identify that news is fake / true.
How to make sure facebook news post quality:
Check any link added to the post written or not. Go to the link (you need internet active connection to browse link) Check the news source If you know the source is reputed newspaper or any government notice from registered government website always have *.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Anti Bribery Policy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-22-what-is-anti-bribery-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-22-what-is-anti-bribery-policy/</guid>
      <description>How to create a company Anti Bribery Policy. Anti Bribery Policy guidelines can be as your Anti Corruption policy for your organization.
1. INTRODUCTION The foundation of company’s culture lies in our history and our values. We believe that we
should always conduct ourselves and our business openly, honestly and in compliance with
all applicable laws.
Our reputation is built by the actions of our people and this is why what you do everyday is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT GUIDELINES</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-17-performance-management-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-17-performance-management-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Goal Setting &amp;amp; Cascading **Purpose
**Goal setting is a powerful tool that is used to align the team and individual goals to
Operating Group objectives and strategies. This strategy keeps all levels of the
organization on the same page. It not only helps improve the attainment of the 3- Year
Plan strategy but also encourages on-going communication between employees and
their managers. As well, each individual can see how their job makes a difference in the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBM Calculation (FedEx Guide)</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-15-cbm-calculation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-15-cbm-calculation/</guid>
      <description>To work at FedEx global shipping, it&amp;rsquo;s important to learn CBM calculation. Why? Because you need to estimate shipping cost to quote price to customers. This is very much important.
Fedex Shipping Job Guide
To calculate CBM, we first need to know the length, width and height of the carton in cm. If carton measurement is in inch, we have to convert measurement in inch. Simply multiply the length, width and height to find cubic centimeter and divide by 1000000 to find cubic meter (CBM).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Printing Capacity Calculation Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-15-garment-printing-capacity-calculation-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-15-garment-printing-capacity-calculation-process/</guid>
      <description>Print Production capacity calculation Area: Screen Printing (Machine &amp;amp; manual)
Objectives: To identify printing machine production capacity and set printing target plan to achieve ultimate goal.
Machine type:
Name: M&amp;amp;R Printing machine No of Wings: 10 wings Machine quantity: 01 pc
Table type: Properties: Artificial leather &amp;amp; Glass
No. of table: 12 tables Average color: 06 color
Average printing area: (8*8) sq. inch
Printing Capacity calculation: For manual printing (Table),</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOP of claim and complaint</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-11-sop-of-claim-and-complaint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-11-sop-of-claim-and-complaint/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we got a quality complaint and claim, we need to provide a reasonable explanation to the buyer of how and why it happened. To provide this explanation, we need to make a thorough investigation to find out the possible root cause as well as provide the correct action plan to avoid future happening. During the investigation, we need to involve a lot of data and questions. In our past experiences, we spent a lot of time back and forth emails to collect the data and find out the root cause because either we forgot to check this or that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance and Sustainability: Conflict Minerals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</guid>
      <description>Learn About Conflict Minerals US guidelines for vendor compliance and sustainability
Index:
What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals in Products US Conflict Minerals Laws Auditing and Reporting Requirements Customer’s expectations Continuous Tracking Tracing workflow Reporting – CFSI Beyond USA What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals refer to raw materials that come from a particular part of the world where conflict is occurring and trading of those materials, perpetuates the fighting. Conflict minerals are mined in conditions of armed conflict and human rights abuses, notably in the Democratic Republic of Congo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Coach Self Evaluation Checklist By Harvard Business School</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-06-a-coach-self-evaluation-checklist-by-harvard-business-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-06-a-coach-self-evaluation-checklist-by-harvard-business-school/</guid>
      <description>Harvard Manage Mentor — COACHING TOOLS A Coach’s Self-Evaluation Checklist The questions below relate to the skills and qualities needed for effective coaching. Use this tool to evaluate your own effectiveness as a coach. The answer is Yes/No. Yes = 1, No=0. There has a total of 25 questions. Effective Coach = 25, If Result &amp;lt; 25, then find it out where need improvement.Question:1. Do you seize learning opportunities and focus on immediate performance problems for your employees?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest sello oil price in Altoona on 5 Mar 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-05-sello-oil-price-in-altoona-pa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-05-sello-oil-price-in-altoona-pa/</guid>
      <description>sello oil price in Altoona on 5 Mar 2021 All latest price of Heating Oil fuel in Blair county
Sel-Lo Oil Inc. is one of the family-owned heating oil, kerosene, vehicle oil, and fuel delivery service during an emergency in Altoona PA. Sello&amp;rsquo;s latest price update today. You can get more information about the sello fuel delivery schedule.
| UPDATED 03/05/21 | Heating Oil | Blend | Kerosene | Dyed ULSD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn End To End Merchandising Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-05-learn-end-to-end-merchandising-process-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-05-learn-end-to-end-merchandising-process-2/</guid>
      <description>Strategic Marketing Original Idea ‐ Trend &amp;amp; Concept Research The original idea or concept can come from many sources. In this process, Design team conduct trend and concept research by shopping US and European markets and conducts market research through mediums such as WGSN, WWD and etc., including competitive landscape, consumer research, reviewing sales data and brainstorming.
Consumer Research In consumer research, consumer statistics and behavior are studied to understand the consumer, to anticipate his/her product needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AQL Inspection System</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-aql-inspection-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-aql-inspection-system/</guid>
      <description>What is AQL Inspection System? AQL Inspection System to Merchandisers
AQL stands for Acceptable Quality Level. AQL is an internationally recognized standard for
inspection. It determines the number of samples to be picked and inspected randomly and the
maximum defect quantity allowed in order to pass the inspection.
Here is an example:
Step 1: First to get customer quality requirement
**Step 2 : Check AQL table 1 to get batch size</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Supplier Safety And Product Quality Specifications</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-garment-supplier-safety-and-product-quality-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-garment-supplier-safety-and-product-quality-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Suppliers of private brand products to Fashion Retail (the “Suppliers”) and its subsidiaries undertake to
comply with the following requirements.
Product safety and quality 1.1. The Suppliers must assure: 1.1.1. The safety and the compliance of the products with the laws and standards in force in the countries
of sale at the time of purchase
1.1.2. A level of aesthetic quality, performance, and minimum product life that is usual for the kind of goods</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supplier Quality Management System</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-supplier-quality-management-system-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-supplier-quality-management-system-ca/</guid>
      <description>Inspection manual for suppliers This manual is part of the Quality Management System which remains the reference with the updated versions
I – Inspection tools The supplier has to supply to the inspector the following information:
the correct approval sample, accompanied by sample approval form and size specifications; the results of the fabric tests; a complete and confirmed fabric and accessory card when necessary; an up-to-date copy of the order with the latest remarks; previous inspection reports and In line inspection reports if available; list of QCCI codes After identification of the total quantity delivered, the Square Root Sample Matrix is used to select the sample pick at random and throughout the entire shipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definition of Terms of Payment</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-27-definition-of-terms-of-payment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-27-definition-of-terms-of-payment/</guid>
      <description>Documents Against Acceptance (D/A) Arrangement under documentary collection in which an exporter instructs the presenting bank to hand over shipping and title documents to the importer only if the importer accepts the accompanying bill of exchange or draft by signing it. Documents Against Payment (D/P) Arrangement under documentary collection in which an exporter instructs the presenting bank to hand over shipping and title documents to the importer only if the importer fully pays the accompanying bill of exchange or draft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incoterms</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-27-incoterms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-27-incoterms/</guid>
      <description>Incoterms (International Commercial Terms) Incoterms are the recognized abbreviation for the International Chamber of Commerce Terms
of Sale.
The 11 Incoterms are listed below: EXW - Ex-Works, named place where shipment is available to the buyer, not loaded. The
seller will not contract for any transportation.
International Carriage NOT Paid by Seller FCA - Free Carrier, unloaded at the seller&amp;rsquo;s dock OR a named place where shipment is
available to the international carrier or agent, not loaded.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn End To End Merchandising Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-27-learn-end-to-end-merchandising-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-27-learn-end-to-end-merchandising-process/</guid>
      <description>Strategic Marketing Original Idea ‐ Trend &amp;amp; Concept Research The original idea or concept can come from many sources. In this process, the Design team conducts trend and concept research by shopping US and European markets and conducts market research through mediums such as WGSN, WWD and etc., including competitive landscape, consumer research, reviewing sales data, and brainstorming.
Consumer Research In consumer research, consumer statistics and behavior are studied to understand the consumer, to anticipate his/her product needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivational Quote</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-26-motivational-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-26-motivational-quote/</guid>
      <description>Inside every person, there are two bears. One bear is all things good, compassion, love, trust.. The other is all things evil, fear, shame and self destruction. Which one win? The answer is the one you feed.
Motivational Quote by bdmeter.info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabric Inspection Standard Procedures</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-fabric-inspection-standard-procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-fabric-inspection-standard-procedures/</guid>
      <description>In general, There are two type of fabrics need to inspect during fabric manufacturing.
Greige fabric inspection Final fabric inspection GREIGE FABRIC INSPECTION PROCEDURE: PROCESS DEFINITION: Shell Fabric inspection: Greige fabric inspection process defined as a system of visual assessment through an inspection machine to detect and identify the knitting faults in the fabric produced by a Circular Knit Machine. Collar &amp;amp; Cuff inspection: Expected quality verification of Collar and Cuff fabric produced in Flat Knit Machine is called collar cuff inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOP of Sewing Inline and Initial Process Inspection</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-sop-of-sewing-inline-and-initial-process-inspection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-sop-of-sewing-inline-and-initial-process-inspection/</guid>
      <description>Purpose For Ensuring the Quality of the Initial product output is according to buyer required standard. Scope Starts from Setting the required tools, Equipment, Guidelines, and Instructions in the Sewing room quality controlling workstation by the factory QC department. Responsible for process The output should be inspected for Construction, styling, Material, Measurements, Aesthetic, Overall workmanship &amp;amp; defects, very thoroughly.
Guidelines as a sample, Sample Comments, First Piece Approval, Aesthetic Standard Approvals, Approved Trim Card, Key Quality Instructions, Checking sequence, should be used for the inspection by performers of the inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embroidery capacity calculation</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-embroidery-production-capacity-calculation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-embroidery-production-capacity-calculation/</guid>
      <description>Embroidery industry is very much important for garment and textile industry. All customer need a logo of their brand on garment. Embroidery is so much popular and expensive rather than printing process. If you want to setup your own embroidery factory, you need to do capacity calculation based on your machine and manpower. Today we will show you how to calculate capacity of a embroidery industry:
Embroidery Production capacity calculation Area: Embroidery Objectives: To identify embroidery production capacity and set embroidery target plan to achieve ultimate goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Projects</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-fashion-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-fashion-projects/</guid>
      <description>https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lauren-wadkins-7a7a474b_designer-design-interview-activity-6767423142542491648-rFAv
Over past few months world have several fashion projects for prospective designer opportunities. Even though they are still looking for more fashion design projects to prepare for next fashion trends. There have ladies items fashion design and those are very much popular globally. They are trying to do much more projects and looking for sample Development from global manufacturer. There are many manufacturer from Asia Europe hub. Fashion designers are looking for fashion show samples and once any design will sold out to brand owner, them Fashion designers will make consumption and pricing for the next season fashion goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housekeeping Manual of Largest Industry</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-housekeeping-manual-of-largest-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-housekeeping-manual-of-largest-industry/</guid>
      <description>General Housekeeping Manual, A Guideline for Good Housekeeping Practice in Workplace. This manual is prepared by the Department of SOP, Textile Group of Companies. This edition developed on dates September 2020.
This manual is issued for A Textile Group of Companies and can be obtained from SOP Department. Please contact www.bdmeter.info for custom development
This guideline is not for advertising, endorsement, or commercial purposes. Please acknowledge the source as &amp;ldquo;Guidelines for Good housekeeping Practice in a Workplace&amp;rdquo;, published by the Policy Implementation and Risk Management-Textile Group of Companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to solve sewing machines general problem</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-sewing-machine-problem-and-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-sewing-machine-problem-and-solutions/</guid>
      <description>সেলাই মেশিনের কমন সমস্যাবলী (Common Problems of Sewing Machines):
সেলাই করতে গিয়ে যেসব সমস্যা হয় (Problems occured during sewing): স্কীপ স্টিচ(Skip Stitch) ব্রকেন স্টিচ(Broken Stitch) লুজ স্টিচ(Loose Stitch) হার্ড স্টিচ(Hard Stitch) নিডেল ব্রকেন(Needle Broken) ফিড ডগ সমস্যা(Feed Dog Problem) বডি সেয়ারিং(স্কুইজিং) সমস্যা(Body Squizing problem) বডি ওয়েভিং সমস্যা(Body Waving Problem) হাফ স্টিচ (Half Stitch) অটো মেশিনের সমস্যা ( যেসব সমস্যার কারনে মেশিন রান বা চালানো যায় না)(Problems of Auto Maching) সারভোমটরে সমস্যা(Servomotor Problem) পাওয়ার বোর্ড সমস্যা(Power Board Problem) সিনক্রোনাইজার সমস্যা(Syncronizer Problem) সেফটি সুইচ সমস্যা(Sefty Switch Problem) পেডেলের পাওয়ার রেগুলেটর বোর্ড(Problem in Power regulator board of padle ) ইরর সিগনাল সমস্যা (Error Signal Problem) নরমাল এবং অটো মেশিনের কমন সমস্যা ( Common problems of normal and auto machine) রোটারী হুক সমস্যা(rotary hook problem) লুপার সমস্যা(Looper problem) নিডেল প্লেট সমস্যা(Needle plate problem) প্রেসার ফুট সমস্যা(Pressure foot problem) ফোল্ডার সমস্যা(Folder problem) লুপার কানেকটর সমস্যা(Looper connetor problem) লুপার হোল্ডার সমস্যা(Looper holder problem) লুপার গাইড সমস্যা(Looper guide problem) নিডেল ক্লাম্প সমস্যা(Needle clamp problem) নিডেল ক্লাম্প হোল্ডার সমস্যা(Needle clamp holder problem) নিডেল প্লেট স্ক্রু সমস্যা(Needle plate scrow problem) স্টীম আয়রনে সমস্যা(Problem of Steam Iron): স্টীম লাইন জেম(Steam line gem) হেন্ডেল সমস্যা(Handle Problem) ভাল্ব সমস্যা(Valve Problem) ভাল্ব স্প্রিং সমস্যা(Valve Spring Problem) ভাল্ব স্ক্রু সমস্যা(Valve Screw Problem) জংশন নিপিলের সমস্যা (Junction Nipple Problem) স্কীপ স্টিচ দূরীকরনের বিস্তারিত বিবরন (Description of Skip Stitch Problem Solving):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Sewing Operator Training Program Guideline</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create a garment sewing operator training module. This training module was developed and tested successfully to take thousands of sewing operators training in different garment and textile manufacturing industries in Bangladesh. This training module fully structured and full of all technical guidelines about garment sewing operator&amp;rsquo;s long-time training procedure, schedule, practical training guide, technical sewing information, exam process, and others all necessary reporting formats. The step-by-step guide will help garment and textile manufacturers globally to know how to train sewing operators in big industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Operating Procedure of A Small Business</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</guid>
      <description>Standard operating procedures (SOP) of a garment idustry A Standard Operating Procedure or SOP means is structured documentation that provides step-by-step guidelines and instructions on how to do a particular business activity, such as production or record keeping. We need SOP in a company with different operations in different areas.
Example of business operating procedure manual: Standard operating procedures or SOP needs to develop as a structured documented office word or pdf file and manual printed copy for management approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York City Come Back Strong in 2021!</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-city-come-back-strong-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-city-come-back-strong-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>We need a recovery that brings back the life of the heart the energy of the city. This is New York City. Everyone is calling to part of the enjoyment of New York City. Everyone gonna does that to join the Open culture of the city on New York city roads. Coronavirus makes New York city stop more than a year. During this pandemic period, New York was facing a great loss of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Fashion Week</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-fashion-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-fashion-week/</guid>
      <description>This year new fashion week has been started in New York City. This year 2021 they are celebrating a lockdown fashion look. They had started their fashion from the kitchen and their fashion. in 2021, the latest fashion week is showing fully brand new looks of lockdown in New York Fashion Week. Few lite fashion shows held in New York. Regarding this, this fashion show launched in a general store by Fashion Designer Jason Wu in New York city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Padma Bridge will open within 2022!</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-padma-bridge-will-open-within-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-padma-bridge-will-open-within-2022/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh dream Padma Bridge will open for road transport entrance within 2022, Road transport Minister Obaidul Kader said today in a meeting. Padma bridge is the dream of Bangladesh people and the Padma bridge will connect the Southeast Southwest part of Bangladesh with the capital city Dhaka.
Created with Bdmeter.info
Padma bridge was the biggest challenge of Bangladesh. But Bangladesh already has completed the main structure of the Padma bridge. Today in a press conference Road transport minister Obaidul Kader said that The Padma will open for vehicle movement within 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sello Oil Price Update 17-Feb-2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-sello-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-sello-oil/</guid>
      <description>Sello Oil Price Update 17-Feb-2021 | On Dated 2/17/21 | Heating Oil | Blend | Kerosene | Dyed ULSD
(Off-Road Vehicle) 100 Gallon Minimum 2.23 2.53 2.83 2.23 Over 200 Gallons 2.19 2.49 2.79 2.19 Over 400 Gallons 2.17 2.47 2.77 2.19 Over 800 Gallons 2.15 2.45 2.75 2.19 Over 1200 Gallons 2.11 2.41 2.71 2.15 Sello oil price update on dated 17th Feb 2021
Sello oil is one of the family owned company in Altoona city situated in Pennsylvania state of USA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Present Bangladesh Government Teacher is Staying in USA!</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-15-a-present-bangladesh-government-teacher-is-staying-in-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-15-a-present-bangladesh-government-teacher-is-staying-in-usa/</guid>
      <description>An assistant teacher of a primary school in Mirzapur, Tangail, migrated to America one and half year ago on a three-month leave. The local education office unable to communicate with her and could not take any action against her. The name of the teacher who migrated to America is Tania Rahman. She is an Assistant teacher at Bawar Kumarjani Government Primary School No. 27 in Mirzapur Municipality.
According to the Upazila Education Office, Tania Rahman took leave from school from July 3, 2019 to October 2, 2019 due to personal problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Khulnaflix update</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-latest-khulnaflix-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-latest-khulnaflix-update/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about khulnaflix.net, the largest FTP server for entertainment
Khulnaflix is a largest ftp server in Khulna Bangladesh. Khulnaflix have movie server of hollywood, bollywoo, bangla, international movies, tv shows, gaming server, tutorial, books, documentery, hadish, quran, live tv channel more than 100 channel fully HD all in hone offered only with ssali isp and cogent broadband internet connection.
Khulnaflix server address: https://khulnaflix.net POINT TO BE NOTED: You can only get khulnaflix ftp server only when you are connected with below IP range:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Sello oil Price in the United States Feb 14, 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-latest-sello-oil-price-in-the-united-states-feb-14-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-latest-sello-oil-price-in-the-united-states-feb-14-2021/</guid>
      <description>Sello oil Price in the United States Feb 14, 2021 As of 2/14/21 Heating Oil Blend Kerosene Dyed ULSD (Off-Road) 100 Gallon Minimum 2.23 2.53 2.83 2.23 Over 200 Gallons 2.19 2.49 2.79 2.19 Over 400 Gallons 2.17 2.47 2.77 2.19 Over 800 Gallons 2.15 2.45 2.75 2.19 Over 1200 Gallons 2.11 2.41 2.71 2.15 Price: Sello Oil Company price
Other available Oil company in Altoona PA: **Sel-Lo Oil
**Rating: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speednet Internet broadband service direct results</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-speednet-internet-broadband-service-direct-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-speednet-internet-broadband-service-direct-results/</guid>
      <description>What is Speednet Khulna? Speednet is a broadband internet service provider in Khulna city. Khulna situated on the Southeast side of Bangladesh. Bangladesh is a small country on the Southeast Asia border with India and Myanmar. Bangladesh has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest Sandy beach Cox&amp;rsquo;s Bazaar and the Largest mangrove forest Sundarban. Khulna is a port city name Mongla Port, is the second-largest port of Bangladesh after Chittagong port. Speednet internet supplier started the journey in Khulna city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is digbazi.net</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-what-is-digbazi-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-what-is-digbazi-net/</guid>
      <description>Learn more about digbazi.net - Local FTP server for entertainment and Islamic books
HOW TO CONNECT WITH DIGBAZI FTP? digbazi is a largest ftp server in Khulna Bangladesh. digbazi have movie server of hollywood, bollywoo, bangla, international movies, tv shows, gaming server, tutorial, books, documentery, hadish, quran, live tv channel more than 100 channel fully HD all in hone offered only with ssali isp and cogent broadband internet connection.
Digbazi server address:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is GOISP</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-what-is-goisp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-what-is-goisp/</guid>
      <description>GOISP is a 9th generation broadband internet supplier registered in 2019 at Khulna city, southeast part of Bangladesh and a largest port city adjacent with Indian border. Goisp is established all latest technologies direct from Taiwan, Singapore and Germany. They have fully installed own cloud server and data center facilities in Khulna area.
GOISP internet technology is using fiber optics internet technology and covering khulna to bagherhaat, fultala, noapara, jessore, gopalgonj, madaripur all area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>khulnaFlix movies 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-13-khulnaflix-movies-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-13-khulnaflix-movies-2021/</guid>
      <description>Khulnaflix is the largest local movie server in Southeast Asia Khulna Bangladesh. KhulnaFlix movie collection 1902 to 2021. Today I will show you how to download the latest khulnaflix movies easily online thru local FTP. If you are connected with ssaliisp or cogent broadband, you can download those easily.
.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-content-wrapper{text-align:center;margin-top:30px;margin-bottom:30px}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-section-header-wrapper{border-color:#ff201f}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-mainheader-wrap{box-shadow:0px 6px 12px -10px #000;border-radius:5px;background-color:#fff}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-section-wrapper{padding-top:30px;padding-right:30px;padding-bottom:30px;padding-left:30px;margin-top:0px;margin-right:0px;margin-bottom:0px;margin-left:0px}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-section-head-wrap{text-align:center;padding-top:0px;padding-right:0px;padding-bottom:0px;margin-top:0px;margin-bottom:0px;padding-left:0px}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-section-head-wrap .magic-content-box-title{color:#404040;font-size:32px;font-family:Default;padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-section-head-wrap .magic-content-box-subtitle{color:#6d6d6d;font-size:18px;font-family:Default;padding-top:5px;padding-bottom:5px}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-title-dash{color:#ff201f}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-block-button span{color:#fff;border-width:1px;font-size:16px;font-family:Default}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-block-button .magic-content-box-button{background-color:#ff201f}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .magic-content-box-block-button i{color:#fff;font-size:13px}.magic-content-box-a24cbe6d-325c-4 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sello oil in Altoona PA on 12 Feb 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-12-sello-oil-in-altoona/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-12-sello-oil-in-altoona/</guid>
      <description>Sello Oil price update on 12 Feb 2021 What is sello oil? Sello oil (Sel-Lo Oil) is a fuel supplier and distributor in Altoona, PA, United States of America. They deliver different kinds of fuel like Ultra-low-sulfur diesel oil (Dyed ULSD), blended fuel, kerosene fuel, and heating oil. Sello Oil company established in 1988 has been operated by a family in central Pennsylvania. Sello oil company is one of the largest heating oil distributors in central Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX internet user total 10000</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-06-spacex-internet-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-06-spacex-internet-service/</guid>
      <description>Starlink SpaceX internet have started it&amp;rsquo;s beta testing Internet service from last year. First accessibility to SpaceX internet to 3 selected countries citizen from USA, Canada, and UK. Recent statistics report is that SpaceX have total 10000 intertnet user now. US news channel CNBC stated that Starlink demands to introduce them as the ideal telecommunication company worldwide. Rubal digital opportunity fund gave millons dollar funding to Satrlink. Regarding this funding, Starlink is trying to expand their satellite internet technology in some other countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungary Denied Bangladeshi Gifts Of 10000 Corona Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-05-al-jazeera-tv-news-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-05-al-jazeera-tv-news-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Recently Hungary denied to receive a gift of Five Thousand Oxford-Astrogeneca Corona Vaccine from Bangladesh. Hungary Foreign Affairs ministry confirmed that welcome-like gift from Bangladesh rejected by Hungary Government. Hungary Foreign Affairs ministry said, Bangladesh offers 5000 Oxford Astrogeneca Corona vaccine as a welcoming gift, but Hungary don&amp;rsquo;t want this gift. Recent Al-Jazeera tv news of Bangladesh top level crime makes huge discussion about Bangladesh Government globally. Bangladesh Government said this Al-Jazeera TV news report is totally irrelevant with situation and we don&amp;rsquo;t agree with Al-Jazeera TV news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Internet Service Provider in Khulna</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-04-best-internet-service-provider-in-khulna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-04-best-internet-service-provider-in-khulna/</guid>
      <description>Broadband internet is the blessing of the modern age. Khulna is a large city with innovation in information technology, engineering, and industrialization. Khulna is the 3rd largest city in Bangladesh. Khulna is located in the southwest part of Bangladesh. Khulna is a district and a division. Khulna economy is the third largest position, one sea post-Mongla, and has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest Mangrove forest Sundarban. Khulna municipal council was established on 12 December 1884 and Khulna city corporation was established on 6 August 1990.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to setup IP TV in Samsung Smart TV</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-24-how-to-setup-ip-tv-in-samsung-smart-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-24-how-to-setup-ip-tv-in-samsung-smart-tv/</guid>
      <description>Samsung smart TV so much popular now a days because we can see satellite TV channels and IP TV, browsing web, can use smart TV applications and android TV with all android smart phone features. You can see live TV streaming online via IP TV service provider connectivity. Customer can use application to see IP TV and use internet browser to see IP TV live streaming online.
Prerequisite:
Samsung smart tv or Samsung android TV Broadband internet connectivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somoy News Live Streaming</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-24-somoy-news-live-streaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-24-somoy-news-live-streaming/</guid>
      <description>Definition &amp;ldquo;Somoy News Live Streaming&amp;rdquo; means a 24-hour television channel in Bangladesh. The legal business name is &amp;ldquo;Somoy Television&amp;rdquo; or, &amp;ldquo;Time television&amp;rdquo;. Another name is &amp;ldquo;Somoy TV&amp;rdquo;, which is the most popular 24/7 hour news channel in the 简体中文 language from Bangladesh. Somoy TV headquarter location is 89, Bir Uttam CR Dutta Road, Banglamotor, Dhaka.
Business category: Somoy Television is a 24 hour news Television channel government of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of Bangladesh registered NOC Broadcasting channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#boycottindianonion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-19-boycottindianonion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-19-boycottindianonion/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is now fullfil to grow onion countrywide and original deshi onion price is now 30 to 40 tk countrywide.
Indian onion market price is 10 taka higher than deshi quality right now. That&amp;rsquo;s why Bangladesh onion importer stopped to import onion from India last 10 days.
Even there is 10 taka less prices onion in available in market price around 15 - 20 taka</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Hills probation: Donald Trump</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>US president Donald Trump urges Capital Hill issue to stop violences. Trump said &amp;quot; We want no violence&amp;quot;.
Trump visited Maxico boarder and provide susch statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona vaccination: No expectations to stop Corona in 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>WHO said &amp;ldquo;There is no hope to stop Corona virus in 2021. Vaccine program ongoing but human need to aware to maintain all preventive actions to stop spread.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump : A True Hero in United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-donald-trump-a-true-hero-in-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-donald-trump-a-true-hero-in-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump news today is the, He is the only President in American history that has been accused twice for insurrection incitement.
Donald Trump news: He incited during recent past week&amp;rsquo;s capital riots and accused for this issue twice. This is the first time ever in US History. Regarding BBC Donald Trump news, this is not the first time, Donald trump is doing this and unstoppable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get rid from unwanted skin hair</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-09-how-to-get-rid-from-unwanted-skin-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-09-how-to-get-rid-from-unwanted-skin-hair/</guid>
      <description>Unwanted hair? You can be released unwanted skin hair in a domestic way. You can be removed in a domestic way When hair grows on a part of the body that is not supposed to have, we call it unwanted hair. Especially on the face or under the nose in the mustache line. These cause loss of beauty. Many people admit to expensive treatments and permanent hair removal to remove these unwanted hairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cable Indstry Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-08-cable-indstry-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-08-cable-indstry-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is one of the most growing GDP country in Southeast Asian region. According to wiki information, in 2020, Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s GDP per capita income is estimated as per IMF data at US $5,139 (PPP) and US$2,064 (nominal).
According to Trading Economics global macro models and analyst, the Bangladesh GDP is projected to trend around 310.00 USD Billion in 2021 and 340.00 USD Billion in 2022, according to our econometric models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical laboratory test market size analysis &amp; research</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-08-clinical-laboratory-test-market-size-analysis-and-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-08-clinical-laboratory-test-market-size-analysis-and-research/</guid>
      <description>Clinical Laboratory Test Market Size Shares and Trend Analysis Report Report Overview of The global clinical trial market size in 2019 was in USA 16.6 billion. The CBC, HBB / HCT, BMP, BN Creatinine, Electrolyte Test, HBA1C, CMP, Liver Panel, Renal Panel, Lipid Panel gives around 16 million business of clinical lab up to 2025.
Clinical laboratory testing is needed to diagnose of the diseases such as cardiovascular disorders, tuberculosis and diabetes, which are driven by increasing of investment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh High court ordered to ban 25 family members of P.K Haldar to leave country</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country-2/</guid>
      <description>Thousands kr money misappropriation claimed fugitive P.K Haldar family total 25 members banned to leave country, Bangladesh High court ordered today 5th January 2021.
Businessman P.K Haldars mother, relatives including his few company employees total 25 members can&amp;rsquo;t leave Bangladesh High court ordered today.
Proshanto Kumar Haldar or, P.K Haldar was flying Bangladesh last year after occurance of bank money misappropriation, he was the Executive Director of that Bank. He was connected with several non-government organization and other businessman also connected with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh High court ordered to ban 25 family members of P.K Haldar to leave country</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country/</guid>
      <description>Thousands kr money misappropriation claimed fugitive P.K Haldar family total 25 members banned to leave country, Bangladesh High court ordered today 5th January 2021.
Businessman P.K Haldars mother, relatives including his few company employees total 25 members can&amp;rsquo;t leave Bangladesh High court ordered today.
Proshanto Kumar Haldar or, P.K Haldar was flying Bangladesh last year after occurance of bank money misappropriation, he was the Executive Director of that Bank. He was connected with several non-government organization and other businessman also connected with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renouned novelist Rabeya khatun has died</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-renouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died-nouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-renouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died-nouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died/</guid>
      <description>Bngladesh renouned novelist Rabeya Khatun has died in 3rd January, 2021
President Abdul Hamid and Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina have expressed grief over the death of Rabeya Khatun
In a condolence message, the President said, “The death of Rabia Khatun is an irreparable loss for the literary arena of the country. His contribution to the spread of 简体中文 literature will always be remembered. ”
The President prayed for the forgiveness of the soul of the late Rabia Khatun and extended his deepest condolences to her bereaved family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hard Time in UK, Lock-down Again</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-05-hard-time-in-uk-lock-down-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-05-hard-time-in-uk-lock-down-again/</guid>
      <description>Corona virus new type is increasing rapidly in UK. Boris Jonson circulated national lock-down from Monday 4th January 2021. UK Prime Minister told that before complete Corona vaccine program this lock-down shall help to reduce growth corona virus and this will help in public health. British prime minister statement from BBC and Reuters news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is khulnaflix</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-05-what-is-khulnaflix-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-05-what-is-khulnaflix-net/</guid>
      <description>khulnaflix.net is a local FTP server operated by Cogent broadband internet service provider. khulnaflix server total space 400 TB. Processor capacity high-end server PC, Ram 40 GB, and upgrading day by day.
khulnaflix local address: http://khulnaflix.net
khulnaflix local file address: http://file.khulnaflix.net
Khulnaflix streaming: http://php.khulnaflix.net/
Khulnaflix live TV: http://tv.khulnaflix.net/
Khulnaflix android application: Click here to download khulnaflix app</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire explosion in Narayanganj Dhaka</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-%E0%A6%A8%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B0%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%BC%E0%A6%A3%E0%A6%97%E0%A6%9E%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%9C%E0%A7%87-%E0%A6%86%E0%A6%97%E0%A7%81%E0%A6%A8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-%E0%A6%A8%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B0%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%BC%E0%A6%A3%E0%A6%97%E0%A6%9E%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%9C%E0%A7%87-%E0%A6%86%E0%A6%97%E0%A7%81%E0%A6%A8/</guid>
      <description>A fire broke out at Konka Fridge factory in Sonargaon, Naranganj, injuring more than a dozen people and causing a lot of damage. The fire broke out at Mograpara in Sonargaon upazila around 11am on Sunday. Local fire service personnel have been able to bring the fire under control. Arefin Siddique, deputy assistant director of the fire service, told BDMeter that six units of the fire service are working to extinguish the fire after receiving the news of the fire at the Konka battery factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renouned novelist Rabeya khatun has died</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-renouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-renouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died/</guid>
      <description>Bngladesh renouned novelist Rabeya Khatun has died in 3rd January, 2021
President Abdul Hamid and Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina have expressed grief over the death of Rabeya Khatun
In a condolence message, the President said, “The death of Rabia Khatun is an irreparable loss for the literary arena of the country. His contribution to the spread of 简体中文 literature will always be remembered. ”
The President prayed for the forgiveness of the soul of the late Rabia Khatun and extended his deepest condolences to her bereaved family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>26 Canal renovation and management : Dhaka city</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-26-canal-renovation-and-management-dhaka-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-26-canal-renovation-and-management-dhaka-city/</guid>
      <description>The capital&amp;rsquo;s city enterprises yesterday officially assumed control over the administration and support obligations of 26 channels and 10 kilometres of box ducts from Dhaka Wasa, raising expectation that the city&amp;rsquo;s long-standing water logging issue would be addressed.
Dhaka Water Supply and Sewerage Authority (Wasa) had been answerable for the 26 trenches (84.5km) and the 10 box ducts (around 10km) since 1988. It additionally takes care of 385km of tempest water waste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy of United States in  2020: Rising from the ruins</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</guid>
      <description>The year 2020 started with a haze of vulnerability looming into the great beyond. The tale Covid was spreading in Europe, the objective of more than 60% fares from Bangladesh, subsequent to unleashing ruin in China, its biggest exchanging accomplice.
Source: The daily Star
Bangladesh felt the warmth of an approaching worldwide emergency however the infection had not at this point advanced into the nation.
The awful news came two or after three months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Badi Bhai left forever : Top  Actor Died in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-26-bengal-bodi-rupnogor-no-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-26-bengal-bodi-rupnogor-no-more/</guid>
      <description>This morning our beloved Abdul Quader, Badi Bhai did not leave for the country of return. Inna lillahi wa inna ilahi rajiun.
We, the country and the nation, mourn the death of our dear brother Abdul Quader. We wish her perfume forgiveness. Condolences to his bereaved family. Kader Bhai, a prominent playwright in Bangla Natangan, has given us innumerable plays, movies and programs.
We hope that all the eminent personalities of Natangan will cooperate with his family and children in the minimum respect and multi-future plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in America: Next steps 75 plus and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</guid>
      <description>A federal advisory panel on Sunday recommended the next phase of the COVID-19 vaccine for seniors age 75 and older and essential workers such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers.
According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given the primary shot through the vaccination program that began last week.
A COVID-19 vaccine made by Pfizer Inc. and Germany&amp;rsquo;s BioEntech is already being distributed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in the United States: The next step is 75 senior and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</guid>
      <description>The Bieber Federal Advisory Panel has recommended 75-year-olds and older workers, such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers, to take the next step in the CVID-19 vaccine.
According to the Department of Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given initial shots through the vaccination program that began last week.
Pfizer Inc. And the COVID-19 vaccine, developed by Bionetech in Germany, is already being distributed. Moderna Inc. Its vaccine was approved last week and distributed last Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing one more point extension of leave: BD News</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</guid>
      <description>The country has announced to extend the holiday once again till January 16. According to the Ministry of Education on Friday, all educational institutions, schools, colleges, universities and national universities will remain closed till January 16. Until December 17, all educational institutions in the country were closed except Qawmi Madrasa.
To curb the spread of corona virus in Bangladesh, all educational institutions were closed from March 17 and all educational institutions were closed till December 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The name of the dream cherished for thousands of years is &#34;Russian Bridge&#34;</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-the-name-of-the-dream-cherished-for-thousands-of-years-is-russian-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-the-name-of-the-dream-cherished-for-thousands-of-years-is-russian-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The latest span of 150 meters has been placed on pillars 12 and 13. Total 8. The main work of the 15 km long Padma Bridge was successfully completed at around 12 noon yesterday. Through which the long cherished dream of the people of 21 districts of southwestern Bangladesh, direct connection with the capital Dhaka has come true today. The Padma Bridge will be opened for use in June 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House has threatened Hane with approving the vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</guid>
      <description>White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine later in the day, two administration officials said. The vaccine, developed by Pfizer and its German partner Bioentech, was endorsed by an FDA panel on Thursday and reached the public.
White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine by the end of the day, two administration officials said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U.S. experts call for Pfizer vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-us-scientist-pfizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-us-scientist-pfizer/</guid>
      <description>U.S. experts on Thursday called on a panel of U.S. government advisers to decide whether to support the large-scale use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s COVID-19 vaccine to combat the outbreak of nearly 300,000 American corona deaths.
Pfizer vaccine for corona prevention The meeting of Food and Drug Administration advisers will present the potential hurdles from the beginning to the end of the largest immunization program in U.S. history. Vaccination activities could begin in a few days, depending on how quickly the FDA signs the panel&amp;rsquo;s recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need a strong global climate alliance to save our planet: Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina has said that a strong global climate alliance is urgently needed to save future generations and the planet from the adverse effects of climate change by reducing carbon emissions.
She said he would like to emphasize the importance of a positive and strong international climate alliance to move towards achieving carbon balance by effectively reducing global carbon emissions before the middle of the century.
This was stated by the Prime Minister in a pre-recorded speech at a virtual conference titled &amp;lsquo;Thimphu Ambition Summit&amp;rsquo; aimed at accelerating the pace of globalization by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bd telecommunication acts: Say no to crime</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</guid>
      <description>ইন্টারনেটে অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড বিধি 简体中文দেশ গেজেট , অতিরিক্ত , আগস্ট ১ , ২০১০ (৭৮৮২)
৩৮। ২০০১ সনের ১৮ নং আইনের ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপন: উক্ত আইনের ধারা ৬৯ এর পরিবর্তে নিম্নরূপ ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপিত হইবে , যথা :-
“ ৬৯। অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড — যদি —
( ক ) . কোন ব্যক্তি টেলিযােগাযােগ যন্ত্রপাতি বা বেতার যন্ত্রপাতির সাহায্যে কোন অশ্লীল , ভীতি প্রদর্শনমূলক বা গুরুতরভাবে অপমানকর কোন বার্তা প্রেরণের উদ্দেশ্যে উক্ত যন্ত্রপাতির পরিচালন কাজে নিয়ােজিত ব্যক্তির নিকট প্রস্তাব করেন , বা</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19: United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</guid>
      <description>According to the World Health Organisation (WHO), for the first wave of COVID-19 to be over, the number of people testing positive for COVID-19 has to drop below 5%. Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s present data says the infection rate is still above 10%. So the first wave of COVID-19 in Bangladesh is continuing and the rate of infection is increasing to some extent.
Why is the infection rate still increasing? The answer probably is we have become relaxed, or exhausted, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say NO to corruption: Bangladesh Telecommunication Act</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</guid>
      <description>Penalties for sending obscene messages on the Internet 36 Substitution of section
69 of Act No. 18 of 2001: Section 69 shall be substituted for the following section 69 of the said Act, namely: -
Penalties for sending obscene, obscene, etc. messages - if - (A). A person proposes to a person engaged in the operation of such equipment for the purpose of sending any obscene, threatening or seriously offensive message with the help of telecommunication equipment or wireless equipment, or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where woman are safe? Home or outside?</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-27-where-woman-are-safe-home-or-outside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-27-where-woman-are-safe-home-or-outside/</guid>
      <description>Author: Tanrima Islam
Abstract:
Recently women are not only unsafe in streets but also at their own personal sanctuary called home. Even though women are called the
mother of the nation, unfortunately they are constantly being victim of severe unhumanitarian criminal activity throughout the country. Research shows heartbreaking results on the alarming rise of rape and domestic violence throughout the country. It is high time the safety of women is taken into consideration by the authorities, the government and by every individuals of this country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 ‘robbers’ lynched in Narsindi</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-2-robbers-lynched-in-narsindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-2-robbers-lynched-in-narsindi/</guid>
      <description>Two suspected robbers were killed in a mob lynching at murgib village in Narsingdi’s shibpur upazila early Wednesday.
One of the deceased was identified as sohel 30 son of Aminul Islam. Resident of kulirchan of kishoreganj district.
A gang of 10/15 robbers entered the village around 3am and stormed into the three houses said Abdul kalam officer incharge of investigation of shibpur police station.
A group of villagers sensing the presence of robbers they informed other villagers over the phone , reports jagonews later , a group of local people went to a mosque and announced the attack of the robber gang using a loudspeaker following the announcement , locals came out of their houses and besieged the three members of the robber gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 domestic workers killed , tortured in 9months : speakers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-28-domestic-workers-killed-tortured-in-9months-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-28-domestic-workers-killed-tortured-in-9months-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Speaker at a seminar said 28 domestic workers were killed and tortured including 10 mysterious death.
In the first nine months of this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five jailed for life in Brahmanbaria murder case</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-five-jailed-for-life-in-brahmanbaria-murder-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-five-jailed-for-life-in-brahmanbaria-murder-case/</guid>
      <description>A brahmanbaria count on Wednesday sentenced five people to life imprisonment for murdering a man in sarail upazila siz years back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOOTBALL LEGEND DIEGO MARADONA IS NO MORE</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-football-legend-diego-maradona-is-no-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-football-legend-diego-maradona-is-no-more/</guid>
      <description>Reports in Argentina said football legend Diego Maradona had a cardiac arrest yesterday.
Argentine newspapers claim the World Cup winner suffered a cardiorespiratory arrest on Wednesday morning local time in the town of Tigre.
Later, news agency AFP was among a host of outlets to tweet that the legend had died.
Maradona, who won Argentina&amp;rsquo;s second World Cup in 1986 almost single-handedly, recently had a surgery to remove a blood clot from his brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legend Never Dies</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-legend-never-dies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-legend-never-dies/</guid>
      <description>“I worked hard all my life for this. Those who say I don&amp;rsquo;t deserve anything, that it all came easy, can kiss my arse.” - Diego Maradona
Maradona, world famous legendary, great Footballer, as popular in world as he is in Argentina. Diego Armando Maradona was an Argentine professional football player and manager. He is born in October 30, 1960 Lanús is the capital of Lanús Partido, Buenos Aires Province in Argentina, and Died in November 25, 2020 (aged 60).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two more policemen suspended over Raihans death on custody</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-more-policemen-suspended-over-raihans-death-on-custody/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-more-policemen-suspended-over-raihans-death-on-custody/</guid>
      <description>Two more policemen including the investigation officer of Raihan ls murdercase were suspended o. Wednesday on charges of helping sub inspector Akbar Hossain Bhuiyan, the prime accused to free . The suspended officials are kotwali police station inspector Soumen Maitra investigation officer of the case and sub inspector Abdul Baten. Sylhet metropolitan police additional deputy commissioner BM Ashrafullah Taher confirmed this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two school girls gang raped in panchagarh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-school-girls-gang-raped-in-panchagarh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-school-girls-gang-raped-in-panchagarh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh saw 1,093 rapes in 10 months this year . Most of them 205 women were gang raped . In average 4women raped everyday in Bangladesh. In that case only 2% of women in Bangladesh ask for legal aid as the path to getting legal support is full of obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA improves on terrorism risk</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</guid>
      <description>Among seven countries in south asia , Bangladesh is with the second lowest impact of terrorism after Bhutan.
Bangladesh has been making improvement in tackling terrorism since 2018 according to terrorism index ( GTI ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Zealand chief honcho Ardern offers annoy power to Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-progressive-zealand-chief-honcho-ardern-offers-annoy-power-to-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-progressive-zealand-chief-honcho-ardern-offers-annoy-power-to-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>Ardern voiced the stain of the 20-minute phone application call was good-natured and go wool-gathering Biden spoke totally favorably helter-skelter nevertheless Avant-garde Zealand was escort the universal. &amp;ldquo;What has been unreservedly at the center of our confession has been divers part respecting respect to exploration, communication dogging, isolation,&amp;rdquo; Ardern voiced. &amp;ldquo;go off at a tangent&amp;rsquo;s go away outlander and insusceptible to what we&amp;rsquo;ve concluded at our dynamism.&amp;rdquo; Experimental Zealand has been abundantly prominent in excision the make tracks chip a dogmatic lockdown in Evidence and conclusion its animation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The management is annex beside domineering in spurn obligatory masks</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-the-management-is-annex-beside-domineering-in-spurn-obligatory-masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-the-management-is-annex-beside-domineering-in-spurn-obligatory-masks/</guid>
      <description>The supervision is pleasing moan far exotic harsh drawing need far stranger to in consequence whereof vital masks to buffer the countrymen Wean away outlander the uphold pending flaunt of Kovid-19. For this, the adjustable courts effort been instructed to be call far from absolute.
Directors Woman Khandaker Anwarul Islam forced the remarks in a indoctrinate corroboration the used provisions appointment. The undertaking was dominate at a customary house choice chaired by Shrewd Representative Sheikh Hasina on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Without delay posterior Bangladesh look forward to a Covid-19 protection?</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-without-delay-posterior-bangladesh-look-forward-to-a-covid-19-protection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-without-delay-posterior-bangladesh-look-forward-to-a-covid-19-protection/</guid>
      <description>The surprising saving exotic Covid-19 hindering trials by Pfizer-BioNTech and Moderna elevated perspective beating the planet in the deportment compete relative to the nefarious failing, but experts curb beamy challenges for Bangladesh to as well moderate foreign the pair vaccines suited to to its current tainted nude strand. They word-of-mouth the mRNA technology-based vaccines qualified by Moderna and Pfizer address to be stored at at large of pocket 70-80 degrees Celsius temperature, but the wilderness has a unveil mooring having the talent of preserving life-saving drugs and progeny&amp;rsquo;s vaccines at temperatures as inferior as missing 20 degrees Celsius less than the Inflated Proclaim on Immunisation (EPI) background .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>County at Vikings Week 11, 2020 Games Live Discussion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-22-county-at-vikings-week-11-2020-games-live-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-22-county-at-vikings-week-11-2020-games-live-discussion/</guid>
      <description>The Cowboys treat the Vikings to the bone
all sharing options.
Minnesota Vikings vs. Dallas Cowboys.
The week is over. The Cowboys won again against the Minnesota Vikings. Dallas is more likely to try to get a win by playing better football over the past few games.
https://youtu.be/Fqqyl1KzaIk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something chronicled: Push for different Biden Cabinet</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-something-chronicled-push-for-different-biden-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-something-chronicled-push-for-different-biden-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (BDM) — Native Americans are encouraging President-elect Joe Biden to impact the world forever by choosing one of their own to lead the amazing office that manages the country&amp;rsquo;s clans, setting up one of a few approaching trial of Biden&amp;rsquo;s promise to have a Cabinet illustrative of Americans.
O.J. Semans is one of many ancestral authorities and casting a ballot activists around the nation pushing choice of Rep. Deb Haaland, a New Mexico Democrat and individual from the Pueblo of Laguna, to turn into the main Native American secretary of inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The story of Golden Monir</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-the-story-of-golden-monir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-the-story-of-golden-monir/</guid>
      <description>Rapid action battalion (RAB) rated house of Gold Dealer Golden Monir&amp;rsquo;s house in Merul Badda, Dhaka. RAB caught huge illegal arms, drugs, foreign currencies, gold and cash money on spot.
Today on Saturday, RAB claimed against Golden Monir and provide a press briefing with details how to be Golden Monir from a general fabric businessmen in Dhaka capital Gaushia market.
He said, &amp;ldquo;During the operation, we seized foreign currency (Bangladeshi Taka nine lakh), 700 ounces of gold (about eight kg) and Taka 19 lakh in cash from Monir&amp;rsquo;s house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assault connected to ladies clad in T-shirts</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-assault-connected-to-ladies-clad-in-t-shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-assault-connected-to-ladies-clad-in-t-shirts/</guid>
      <description>Autonomous administrator Rezaul Karim Bablu on Tuesday advised parliament that women&amp;rsquo;s activists are at fault for the ascent of assault episodes the nation over. He even supported the usage of the &amp;ldquo;tamarinds hypothesis (ladies resemble tamarinds, men will salivate at seeing them, thus they should stay covered)&amp;rdquo; of late Hefajat-e-Islam supremo Ahmad Shafi.
Following is a portion of the extemporaneous meeting:
How could it day break on you that women&amp;rsquo;s activists are answerable for the ascent of assault occurrences in the nation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid emergency indicated us treatment is conceivable in USA, says Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-covid-emergency-indicated-us-treatment-is-conceivable-in-usa-says-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-covid-emergency-indicated-us-treatment-is-conceivable-in-usa-says-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden has indeed called upon individuals to carefully follow the prudent well-being conventions against Covid to ward off the second influx of the pandemic.
Joe Biden talked about altogether fighting the infection in a video gathering with the secretaries of theDemocrat at the gathering base camp on Thursday evening.
&amp;ldquo;Everyone needs to follow the well-being mandates to battle the second flood of Covid. Only I&amp;rsquo;m at home right now, so I&amp;rsquo;m not wearing a veil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Govt can&#39;t put youngsters in danger  - Joe Biden said</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-govt-cant-put-youngsters-in-danger-pm-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-govt-cant-put-youngsters-in-danger-pm-said/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden yesterday recognized that remaining at home had been progressively hard for understudies, however, the public authority would not put youngsters&amp;rsquo; lives in danger by returning the instructive organizations.
He was conveying the wrapping up discourse in the main ever unique meeting in parliament.
Prior to her discourse, the Deputy Leader of the Opposition and Party Chairman requested that the public authority resume every instructive establishment.
The President answered that the USA, diverse European nations, and the UK had resumed their instructive foundations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India quick to work with Bangladesh on guard equipment stages</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-india-quick-to-work-with-bangladesh-on-guard-equipment-stages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-india-quick-to-work-with-bangladesh-on-guard-equipment-stages/</guid>
      <description>India has said it is quick to work with Bangladesh on safeguard equipment stages like Akash rocket, radars, mortars, cannons weapons and ammo and welcomed ventures from its eastern neighbor in two key Indian protection modern hallways.
India likewise said that its shipyards are happy to band together with Bangladeshi shipyards for development of stages according to Bangladesh prerequisites through joint endeavors, co-improvement and cooperation for both business and safeguard necessities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India&#39;s absolute Covid diseases cross 9 million</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-indias-absolute-covid-diseases-cross-9-million/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-indias-absolute-covid-diseases-cross-9-million/</guid>
      <description>ndia crossed the horrid achievement of 9 million Covid cases, with 45,882 new diseases recorded over the most recent 24 hours, the wellbeing service said on Friday.
India is just the subsequent nation to cross 9 million Covid diseases, after the United States, however cases have eased back down in the nation in the wake of hitting a top in September.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacked specialists of Bangladesh&#39;s Dragon Sweater surrendered a large portion of their compensation. Presently businesses break bargain</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-sacked-specialists-of-bangladeshs-dragon-sweater-surrendered-a-large-portion-of-their-compensation-presently-businesses-break-bargain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-sacked-specialists-of-bangladeshs-dragon-sweater-surrendered-a-large-portion-of-their-compensation-presently-businesses-break-bargain/</guid>
      <description>Among the most seasoned in the attire business, Dragon Sweater Bangladesh Ltd started laying off around 500 laborers in March this year as it set out to drive away the individuals who have been with the organization for quite a while.
The conservation was wrapped up as arranged by June yet the laborers were not paid their cash. In the course of the most recent five months, they have gone to numerous administration organizations and held serene fights for backpay without progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Superbrands Bangladesh praises 40 esteemed brands</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-superbrands-bangladesh-praises-40-esteemed-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-superbrands-bangladesh-praises-40-esteemed-brands/</guid>
      <description>Superbrands Bangladesh yesterday respected 40 associations, including The Daily Star, as the most esteemed and important brand in the nation for 2020-21.
The brands incorporate Aamra Companies, Green Delta Insurance, AKS, Igloo Ice Cream, ACI Pure Salt, IPDC Finance, Matador Group, Bashundhara LP Gas, Metlife, Monno Ceramic, Pride Ltd, Beximco Pharmaceuticals, Radio Foorti and Brac.
Sprinter, BRB Cable Industries, Channel I, Shah Cement, Cow Brand Color Coated Steel, Shanta Holdings, Daraz Bangladesh, Shwapno, DBL Group, Singer Bangladesh, Elite Paint, SMC Condoms, Epyllion Group, Super Board, FOGG, Super Fresh Drinking Water, Rahimafrooz Globatt Batteries, The Palace Luxury Resort, Grameenphone, and Walton were likewise named as Superbrands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oxford immunization is required to show up in February, with two dosages costing Rs 100</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-the-oxford-immunization-is-required-to-show-up-in-february-with-two-dosages-costing-rs-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-the-oxford-immunization-is-required-to-show-up-in-february-with-two-dosages-costing-rs-100/</guid>
      <description>Oxford&amp;rsquo;s Corona immunization is required to show up in February, said Adar Punwala, CEO of the Serum Institute of India.
Oxford&amp;rsquo;s Corona antibody is probably going to be given to wellbeing laborers and the old in February , NDTV provided details regarding Friday, the best chief told the Hindustan Times .
He additionally said that the immunization might be given to people in general in April.
Punwala added that for ordinary patients, two dosages of the immunization could cost up to Rs 1,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visa spending falls as customers fix belts</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-visa-spending-falls-as-customers-fix-belts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-visa-spending-falls-as-customers-fix-belts/</guid>
      <description>Spending through Visas declined in September as buyers are as yet feeling the warmth of the more slow than-anticipated monetary recuperation, while the danger of a second rush of Covid contaminations poses a potential threat.
Absolute card credits held by loan specialists remained at Tk 1,245 crore in September, down 19.78 percent a month sooner, as indicated by information from the national bank.
Exchange through Visas, nonetheless, rose 23.68 percent year-on-year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Economic Forum recognition winner is Green Delta, Denim Manufacturer</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-world-economic-forum-recognition-winner-is-green-delta-demin-manufacturer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-world-economic-forum-recognition-winner-is-green-delta-demin-manufacturer/</guid>
      <description>Denim Expert Ltd and Green Delta Insurance Company have come up as respectable notices in a World Economic Forum (WEF) &amp;ldquo;New Champion&amp;rdquo; grant classification prior this month for their uncommon presentation on manageability and inclusivity.
The pair won the honor in the Excellence in Sustainability classification of the honor offered on worldwide reusing organization Gemini Corporation, discernibility innovations supplier Optel Group and danger the executives warning and consultancy Risk Insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young person &#39;assaulted&#39; in Dhaka, 6 including her cousin included</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-young-person-assaulted-in-dhaka-6-including-her-cousin-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-young-person-assaulted-in-dhaka-6-including-her-cousin-included/</guid>
      <description>An adolescent young lady was &amp;ldquo;assaulted&amp;rdquo; by her cousin and one more on Wednesday night in the capital&amp;rsquo;s Kalyanpur. Four additional young people were likewise included.
When the casualty educated the law authorities after the occurrence, they dispatched a manhunt, and grabbing the blamed that night.
Police held 18-year-old Md Raihan, the casualty&amp;rsquo;s cousin; Alamin, Joy Mia, Imran, Abu Sayeed and 19-year-old Md Emon.
&amp;ldquo;The casualty recorded a case yesterday regarding the occurrence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football stars&#39; spouses conflict in &#39;WAGatha Christie&#39; legal dispute in London</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-football-stars-spouses-conflict-in-wagatha-christie-legal-dispute-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-football-stars-spouses-conflict-in-wagatha-christie-legal-dispute-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Football - World Cup - Quarter Final - Sweden versus England - Samara Arena, Samara, Russia - July 7, 2018 Wife of England&amp;rsquo;s Jamie Vardy, Rebekah Vardy, in the remain after the match. Reuters
Football - World Cup - Quarter Final - Sweden versus England - Samara Arena, Samara, Russia - July 7, 2018 Wife of England&amp;rsquo;s Jamie Vardy, Rebekah Vardy, in the remain after the match. Reuters
A court fight between the spouses of previous England football stars Wayne Rooney and Jamie Vardy commenced in London on Thursday, a heightening in a story of selling out and beginner criminologist work that has tantalized the British public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science, expressions, business streams to go as Bangladesh redoes auxiliary training educational plan</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-science-expressions-business-streams-to-go-as-bangladesh-redoes-auxiliary-training-educational-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-science-expressions-business-streams-to-go-as-bangladesh-redoes-auxiliary-training-educational-plan/</guid>
      <description>Science, expressions, business streams to go as Bangladesh redoes auxiliary instruction educational plan in Parliament Correspondent.
Schooling Minister Dipu Moni says the auxiliary training educational program will not, at this point be part into Science, Arts and Business Studies streams.
She declared the move during the entry of the Madrasa Education Board Bill in parliament on Thursday.
&amp;ldquo;As you definitely know, the total of the educational program is being investigated. We will deliver the last form very soon,&amp;rdquo; she said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces likely difficulty in Georgia relate, drops Michigan claim</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-trump-faces-likely-difficulty-in-georgia-relate-drops-michigan-claim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-trump-faces-likely-difficulty-in-georgia-relate-drops-michigan-claim/</guid>
      <description>Workers of the Fulton County Board of Registration and Elections measure polling forms in Atlanta, Georgia US, November 4, 2020. Reuters
Representatives of the Fulton County Board of Registration and Elections measure voting forms in Atlanta, Georgia US, November 4, 2020. Reuters
The US official political race milestone province of Georgia was required on Thursday to insist Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s triumph over Donald Trump after a meticulous relate, as Trump&amp;rsquo;s re-appointment crusade said it was pulling out a claim in Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA&#39;s Joe Biden urges world pioneers to be intense to handle environmental change</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</guid>
      <description>US President Joe Biden has encouraged the world chiefs to assume a striking part in decreasing carbon emanations to guarantee the assurance of life and property.
He made the allure while tending to the High-Level Panel Closing Session of the UNFCCC Race to Zero Dialogs by means of a video message.
States in the current year confronted intermittent flooding alongside two typhoons that harmed harvests and living spaces and influenced individuals&amp;rsquo; occupation in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We can&#39;t put understudies&#39; lives in danger by resuming schools: Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-we-cant-put-understudies-lives-in-danger-by-resuming-schools-hasina/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-we-cant-put-understudies-lives-in-danger-by-resuming-schools-hasina/</guid>
      <description>The instructive foundations are not returning now in the midst of the Covid flare-up, as indicated by President Joe Biden.
He shielded the choice to keep the schools and universities shut when Democrats requested returning of the organizations in parliament on Thursday.
&amp;ldquo;Schools and universities have been shut since March and the public authority has dispatched an &amp;lsquo;auto-pass&amp;rsquo; framework while workplaces and courts have stayed open. I don&amp;rsquo;t perceive any rationale in keeping just the instructive organizations shut,&amp;rdquo; said the representative head of the resistance in parliament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldwide economy recuperating, yet might be losing energy: IMF boss</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-worldwide-economy-recuperating-yet-might-be-losing-energy-imf-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-worldwide-economy-recuperating-yet-might-be-losing-energy-imf-boss/</guid>
      <description>Global Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva. Reuters
Global Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva. Reuters
The worldwide economy is recuperating from the profundities of the Covid emergency, however there are indications of easing back force in nations with resurging contamination rates, the International Monetary Fund said in another report for G20 significant economies.
The report, delivered in front of the current week&amp;rsquo;s virtual gatherings of account authorities and pioneers from the Group of 20 nations, underscored the lopsided idea of the worldwide recuperation and cautioned the emergency would probably leave profound, inconsistent scars.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
