<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>building-materials on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/building-materials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in building-materials on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/building-materials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building systems design and analysis</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/building-systems-design-and-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/building-systems-design-and-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Building system design Systems design comprises a logical series of steps that leads to the best decision for a given set of conditions. The procedure requires:
Analysis of a building system Synthesis, or selection of components, to form a system that meets specific objectives while subject to constraints, or variables controllable by designers. Appraisal of system performance, including comparisons with alternative systems. Feedback to analysis and synthesis of information obtained in system evaluation, to improve the design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traditional building construction procedures</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/traditional-building-construction-procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/traditional-building-construction-procedures/</guid>
      <description>Construction under the traditional construction procedure is performed by contractors. While they would like to satisfy the owner and the building designers, contractors have the main objective of making a profit. Hence, their initial task is to prepare a bid price based on an accurate estimate of construction costs. This requires development of a concept for performance of the work and a construction time schedule. After a contract has been awarded, contractors must furnish and pay for all materials, equipment, power, labor, and supervision required for construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admixtures for concrete in building construction</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/admixtures-for-concrete-in-building-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/admixtures-for-concrete-in-building-construction/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s Admixtures? Admixtures are anything other than portland cement, water, and aggregates that are added to a concrete mix to modify its properties. Included in this definition are chemical admixtures (ASTM C494 and C260), mineral admixtures such as fly ash (C618) and silica fume, corrosion inhibitors, colors, fibers, and miscellaneous (pumping aids, dampproofing, gas-forming, permeability-reducing agents).
Chemical and mineral admixtures Chemical admixtures used in concrete generally serve as water reducers, accelerators, set retarders, or a combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determination of Moist Air Properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</guid>
      <description>An air-water mixture is found from the heat and mass balance to be at 60°C (333 K) and 0.025 kg/kg (25 g/kg) absolute humidity. Calculate the other main parameters for the mixture. Take atmospheric pressure as 101,325 Pa.
Method: Consult item (vi) in Table 12-5 for the calculation methodology.
From the initial terminology section, specific humidity YW = 0.02439 kg/kg, mole ratio z = 0.0402 kmol/kmol, mole fraction y = 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process control and elements in a control loop</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/process-control-and-elements-in-a-control-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/process-control-and-elements-in-a-control-loop/</guid>
      <description>Process Control In order to produce a product with consistently high quality, tight process control is necessary. A simple-to-understand example of process control would be the supply of water to a number of cleaning stations, where the water temperature needs to be kept constant in spite of the demand. A simple control block is shown in Fig. 1.1a, steam, and cold water are fed into a heat exchanger, where heat from the steam is used to bring the cold water to the required working temperature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cementitious materials and their classification</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/02/cementitious-materials-and-their-classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/02/cementitious-materials-and-their-classification/</guid>
      <description>Cementitious materials include the many products that are mixed with either water or some other liquid or both to form a cementing paste that may be formed or molded while plastic but will set into a rigid shape. When sand is added to the paste, mortar is formed. A combination of coarse and fine aggregate (sand) added to the paste forms concrete.
Types of cementitious materials There are many varieties of cement and numerous ways of classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building protection system against lightning and thundering</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-system-against-lightning-and-thundering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-system-against-lightning-and-thundering/</guid>
      <description>What is lightning or Thunder? Lightning, a high-voltage, high-current electrical discharge between clouds and the ground, may strike and destroy life and property anywhere thunderstorms have occurred in the past. Buildings and their occupants, however, can be protected against this hazard by the installation of a special electrical system. Because an incomplete or poor installation can cause worse damage or injuries than no protection at all, a lightning-protection system should be designed and installed by experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building protection against fire</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-against-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-against-fire/</guid>
      <description>There are two distinct aspects of building fire protection: life safety and property protection. Although providing for one aspect generally results in some protection for the other, the two goals are not mutually inclusive. A program that provides for prompt notification and evacuation of occupants meets the objectives for life safety but provides no protection for the property. Conversely, it is possible that adequate building protection might not be sufficient for the protection of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</guid>
      <description>for New Construction, Major Renovation, and Commercial Interiors Introduction Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation Suggestions present a menu of options that can be adopted or implemented to integrate sustainable design, equipment, materials and other elements into new buildings and major renovations. The Suggestions include elements scored by the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design (LEED) standard, as well as the best practices Bdmeter has implemented in our global network.
Suppliers worldwide are encouraged to adopt as many of the items in these Suggestions whenever feasible and applicable to your location and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoning and building codes</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/zoning-and-building-codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/zoning-and-building-codes/</guid>
      <description>Many of the restrictions encountered in building design are imposed by legal regulations. While all must be met, those in building codes are the most significant because they affect almost every part of a building. Building codes are established under the police powers of a state to protect the health, welfare, and safety of communities. A code is administered by a building official of the municipality or state that adopts it by legislation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to protect your building against wind, storm, or tornado</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</guid>
      <description>For practical design, wind and earthquakes may be treated as horizontal, or lateral, loads. Although wind and seismic loads may have vertical components, these generally are small and readily resisted by columns and bearing walls. Vertical earthquake components can be important in the design of connections as in precast concrete structures. Wind often generates significant uplift forces that require special attention to vertical restraint and lateral support for members in reverse bending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building construction protection against water, flood, and heavy rainfall</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/building-construction-protection-against-water-flood-and-heavy-rainfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/building-construction-protection-against-water-flood-and-heavy-rainfall/</guid>
      <description>PROTECTION AGAINST WATER Whether thrust against and into a building by a flood, driven into the interior by heavy rain, leaking from plumbing, storm surge, or seeping through the exterior enclosure, water can cause costly damage to a building. Consequently, designers should protect buildings and their contents against water damage.
Protective measures may be divided into two classes: floodproofing and waterproofing. Floodproofing provides protection against flowing surface water, commonly caused by a river overflowing its banks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light and sight: Lighting control system</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/09/light-and-sight-lighting-control-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/09/light-and-sight-lighting-control-system/</guid>
      <description>Lighting is part of the environmental control system, which also includes sound control and heating, ventilation, and air conditioning (HVAC), within a building.
The prime purpose of a lighting system is to provide good visibility for the execution of the tasks to be performed within the building. With good visibility, occupants can execute their tasks comfortably, efficiently, and safely.
Lighting also is desirable for other purposes. For example, it can be used to develop color effects for pleasure or accident prevention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building stones and it&#39;s properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</guid>
      <description>Principal building stones generally used in the United States are limestones, marbles, granites, and sandstones. Other stones such as serpentine and quartzite are used locally but to a much lesser extent. Stone, in general, makes an excellent
building material, if properly selected on the basis of experience; but the cost may be relatively high.
The properties of stone depend on what nature has provided. Therefore, the designer does not have the choice of properties and colors available in some of the manufactured building units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Sustainable Building or Green Building</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</guid>
      <description>What is a sustainable building? For your building to be sustainable, many factors need to be considered. These include air quality, energy
efficiency, and the use of ‘green’ materials among others. This document focuses on 1) building a sustainable building 2) retrofitting and 3) certification.
Why should I make my buildings sustainable? Apart from the environmental benefits, a sustainable building can reduce your operational costs by as much as 30-50% on your energy usage and 40-50% on your water usage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
