<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fashion-week on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/fashion-week/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fashion-week on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/fashion-week/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Projects</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-fashion-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-fashion-projects/</guid>
      <description>https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lauren-wadkins-7a7a474b_designer-design-interview-activity-6767423142542491648-rFAv
Over past few months world have several fashion projects for prospective designer opportunities. Even though they are still looking for more fashion design projects to prepare for next fashion trends. There have ladies items fashion design and those are very much popular globally. They are trying to do much more projects and looking for sample Development from global manufacturer. There are many manufacturer from Asia Europe hub. Fashion designers are looking for fashion show samples and once any design will sold out to brand owner, them Fashion designers will make consumption and pricing for the next season fashion goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Fashion Week</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-fashion-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-fashion-week/</guid>
      <description>This year new fashion week has been started in New York City. This year 2021 they are celebrating a lockdown fashion look. They had started their fashion from the kitchen and their fashion. in 2021, the latest fashion week is showing fully brand new looks of lockdown in New York Fashion Week. Few lite fashion shows held in New York. Regarding this, this fashion show launched in a general store by Fashion Designer Jason Wu in New York city.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
