<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>industry on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/industry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in industry on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:47:31 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bdmeter</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/bdmeter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:47:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/bdmeter/</guid>
      <description>Real-time information of industry and technology.
You can write us directly. Our email address bdmeter.info@gmail.com
**Our Address:
**22 W 34th St, 301, New York, NY 10001, US</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps for Process-related Risk  Assessment in the Plastic Toys Industry</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</guid>
      <description>Understand the process flow on how to manufacture the product. Identify the hazards from its process step (task). Decide who might be harmed and how. Evaluate the risks and decide on precautions. Record your findings and implement them 6. Review your assessment and update if necessary. Plastic Toys Production Process Flow: Fig: process flow of toys production
Types of Materials used for Injection Molding SL. Material name Description Applications 1 Acetal Strong, rigid, excellent fatigue resistance, excellent creep resistance, chemical resistance, moisture resistance, naturally opaque white, low/medium cost Bearings, cams, gears, handles, plumbing components, rollers, rotors, slide guides, valves 2 Acrylic Rigid, brittle, scratch resistant, transparent, optical clarity, low/medium cost Display stands, knobs, lenses, light housings, panels, reflectors, signs, shelves, trays 3 Acrylonitrile Butadiene Styrene Strong, flexible, low mold shrinkage (tight tolerances), chemical resistance, electroplating capability, naturally opaque, low/medium cost Automotive (consoles, panels, trim, vents), boxes, gauges, housings, inhalers, toys 4 Cellulose Acetate Tough, transparent, high cost Handles, eyeglass frames 5 Polyamide 6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Bearings, bushings, gears, rollers, wheels 6 Polyamide 6/6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Handles, levers, small housings, zip ties 7 Polyamide 11+12 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque to clear, very high cost Air filters, eyeglass frames, safety masks 8 Polycarbonate Very tough, temperature resistance, dimensional stability, transparent, high cost Automotive (panels, lenses, consoles), bottles, containers, housings, light covers, reflectors, safety helmets, and shields 9 Polyester - Thermoplastic Rigid, heat resistance, chemical resistance, medium/high cost Automotive (filters, handles, pumps), bearings, cams, electrical components (connectors, sensors), gears, housings, rollers, switches, valves 10 Polyether Tough, very high chemical resistance, clear, very high-cost Sulphone Valves 11 Polyetheretherketone Strong, thermal stability, chemical resistance, abrasion resistance, low moisture absorption Aircraft components, electrical connectors, pump impellers, seals 12 Polyetherimide Heat resistance, flame resistance, transparent (amber color) Electrical components (connectors, boards, switches), covers, shields, surgical tools 13 Polyethylene - Low Density Lightweight, tough and flexible, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Kitchenware, housings, covers, and containers 14 Polyethylene - High Density Tough and stiff, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Chair seats, housings, covers, and containers 15 Polyphenylene Oxide Tough, heat resistance, flame resistance, dimensional stability, low water absorption, electroplating capability, high cost Automotive (housings, panels), electrical components, housings, plumbing components 16 Polyphenylene Sulphide Very high strength, heat resistance, brown, very high cost Bearings, covers, fuel system components, guides, switches, and shields 17 Polypropylene Lightweight, heat resistance, high chemical resistance, scratch resistance, natural waxy appearance, tough and stiff, low cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</guid>
      <description>Today we will learn about vendor compliance and sustainability terms to identify hazards and assess risks.
Agenda:
Terms &amp;amp; Definitions HIRA Process Hazard Identification Risk Matrix &amp;amp; Risk Assessment Operational Controls Good Documentation Practices &amp;amp; Recommendations Company Sustainability Development Example HIRA &amp;amp; Discussion Factory Assignment : Risk Never Sleeps! The Cost of Safety The Importance of Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment HIRA is the Basis (First Step) to SafeGuard Employees, Contractors, Visitors, Contract workers, People who share the workplace from Significant Injuries or ill Health in a Systematic Approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thermodynamics, heat transfer, and fluid flow mechanics</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-20-thermodynamics-heat-transfer-and-fluid-flow-free-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-20-thermodynamics-heat-transfer-and-fluid-flow-free-handbook/</guid>
      <description>Fluid flow is an important part of most industrial processes; especially those involving the transfer of heat. Frequently, when it is desired to remove heat from the point at which it is generated, some type of fluid is involved in the heat transfer process. Examples of this are the cooling water circulated through a gasoline or diesel engine, the airflow past the windings of a motor, and the flow of water through the core of a nuclear reactor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Textile Manufacturer List In Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is one of the largest and biggest manufacturers of textile goods and materials over decades. Bangladesh has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest garment and textile manufacturer after China. After Coronavirus spreads all over the world from 2019 to 2021, the world market is changing dramatically. The apparel and fashion goods-making market is changing. Bangladesh has a total of more than 7000 industries in this sector. Bangladesh already achieved the world&amp;rsquo;s largest knitwear manufacturer country in the western marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knit Garments CM Calculation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</guid>
      <description>In Apparel and Fashion industry, CM means Cost of Manufacture. In the garment manufacturing industry, CM means Manufacturing Cost of one dozen or 12 pcs garments. To calculate the CM of 12 pcs knit garments we must follow the below criterion-
monthly expenditure of the industry total no. of running machine machine qty to execute the layout of the specific order, productivity per shift dollar exchange rate Let, Monthly Industry Expenditure is BDT 80,00,000 Working days of the 30 days = 26 days Daily Factory Expenditure = BDT 307692.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
