<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>corona-vaccine on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/corona-vaccine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in corona-vaccine on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/corona-vaccine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corona vaccination: No expectations to stop Corona in 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>WHO said &amp;ldquo;There is no hope to stop Corona virus in 2021. Vaccine program ongoing but human need to aware to maintain all preventive actions to stop spread.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in America: Next steps 75 plus and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</guid>
      <description>A federal advisory panel on Sunday recommended the next phase of the COVID-19 vaccine for seniors age 75 and older and essential workers such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers.
According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given the primary shot through the vaccination program that began last week.
A COVID-19 vaccine made by Pfizer Inc. and Germany&amp;rsquo;s BioEntech is already being distributed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in the United States: The next step is 75 senior and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</guid>
      <description>The Bieber Federal Advisory Panel has recommended 75-year-olds and older workers, such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers, to take the next step in the CVID-19 vaccine.
According to the Department of Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given initial shots through the vaccination program that began last week.
Pfizer Inc. And the COVID-19 vaccine, developed by Bionetech in Germany, is already being distributed. Moderna Inc. Its vaccine was approved last week and distributed last Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
