<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Crisis: Understanding the Alarming Decline in Lake Mead Water Levels</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/navigating-the-crisis-understanding-the-alarming-decline-in-lake-mead-water-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/navigating-the-crisis-understanding-the-alarming-decline-in-lake-mead-water-levels/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Lake Mead, located on the Colorado River, is the largest reservoir in the United States, providing water and power to millions of people in the Southwest. It has long been a vital resource for agricultural, industrial, and municipal needs, supporting cities such as Las Vegas, Phoenix, and Los Angeles. However, in recent years, the water levels of Lake Mead have been steadily declining, raising concerns about the sustainability of water resources in the region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building systems design and analysis</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/building-systems-design-and-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/building-systems-design-and-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Building system design Systems design comprises a logical series of steps that leads to the best decision for a given set of conditions. The procedure requires:
Analysis of a building system Synthesis, or selection of components, to form a system that meets specific objectives while subject to constraints, or variables controllable by designers. Appraisal of system performance, including comparisons with alternative systems. Feedback to analysis and synthesis of information obtained in system evaluation, to improve the design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traditional building construction procedures</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/traditional-building-construction-procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/traditional-building-construction-procedures/</guid>
      <description>Construction under the traditional construction procedure is performed by contractors. While they would like to satisfy the owner and the building designers, contractors have the main objective of making a profit. Hence, their initial task is to prepare a bid price based on an accurate estimate of construction costs. This requires development of a concept for performance of the work and a construction time schedule. After a contract has been awarded, contractors must furnish and pay for all materials, equipment, power, labor, and supervision required for construction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to protect heat and flame</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/learn-how-to-protect-heat-and-flame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/learn-how-to-protect-heat-and-flame/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to protect heat and flame during emergency Introduction With industrialisation, the safety of human beings has become an important issue. A growing segment of the industrial textiles industry has therefore been involved in a number of new developments in ﬁbres, fabrics, protective clothing.Major challenges to coatings and fabrication technology for production in the ﬂame-retardant textile industry have been to produce environmentally friendly, non-toxic ﬂame-retardant systems that complement the comfort properties of textiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AC Electricity: The basic passive components in ac circuits</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/ac-electricity-the-basic-passive-components-in-ac-circuits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/06/ac-electricity-the-basic-passive-components-in-ac-circuits/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Three basic components, resistors, capacitors, and inductors, are very important elements in electrical circuits as individual devices, or together. Resistors are used as loads, delays, and current limiting devices. Capacitors are used as dc blocking devices, in level shifting, integrating, differentiating, frequency determination, selection, and delay circuits. Inductors are used for frequency selection and ac blocking, in analog meter movements and relays, and are the basis for transformers and motors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admixtures for concrete in building construction</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/admixtures-for-concrete-in-building-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/admixtures-for-concrete-in-building-construction/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s Admixtures? Admixtures are anything other than portland cement, water, and aggregates that are added to a concrete mix to modify its properties. Included in this definition are chemical admixtures (ASTM C494 and C260), mineral admixtures such as fly ash (C618) and silica fume, corrosion inhibitors, colors, fibers, and miscellaneous (pumping aids, dampproofing, gas-forming, permeability-reducing agents).
Chemical and mineral admixtures Chemical admixtures used in concrete generally serve as water reducers, accelerators, set retarders, or a combination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Occupational Health and Safety systems</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/occupational-health-and-safety-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/occupational-health-and-safety-systems/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bdmeter has developed this Occupational Health and Safety toolkit to support you to:
Understand what a robust occupational health and safety system means for your business; Make the case with factory management and other colleagues to invest in this area and support you; Assess the performance of your current health and safety system; Identify areas where you can improve and develop action plans to improve your health and safety system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building costs</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/building-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/05/building-costs/</guid>
      <description>Construction cost of a building usually is a dominant design concern. One reason is that if construction cost exceeds the owner’s budget, the owner may cancel the project. Another reason is that costs, such as property taxes and insurance, that occur after completion of the building often are proportional to the initial cost. Hence, owners usually try to keep that cost low. Designing a building to minimize construction cost, however, may not be in the owner’s best interests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bdmeter</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/bdmeter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:47:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/bdmeter/</guid>
      <description>Real-time information of industry and technology.
You can write us directly. Our email address bdmeter.info@gmail.com
**Our Address:
**22 W 34th St, 301, New York, NY 10001, US</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determination of Moist Air Properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</guid>
      <description>An air-water mixture is found from the heat and mass balance to be at 60°C (333 K) and 0.025 kg/kg (25 g/kg) absolute humidity. Calculate the other main parameters for the mixture. Take atmospheric pressure as 101,325 Pa.
Method: Consult item (vi) in Table 12-5 for the calculation methodology.
From the initial terminology section, specific humidity YW = 0.02439 kg/kg, mole ratio z = 0.0402 kmol/kmol, mole fraction y = 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are Smoke and Chemical Sensors and their applications</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/what-are-smoke-and-chemical-sensors-and-their-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/what-are-smoke-and-chemical-sensors-and-their-applications/</guid>
      <description>Smoke and Chemical Sensors: The detection of smoke, radiation, and chemicals is of great importance in industrial processing not only as it relates to the safety of humans and the control of environmental pollution both atmospheric and ground but is also used in process control applications to detect the presence, absence, or levels of impurities in processing chemicals.
Smoke detectors and heat sensors (automatic sprinklers) are now commonplace in the industry for the protection of people, and equipment, and for monitoring and control of chemical reactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process control and elements in a control loop</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/process-control-and-elements-in-a-control-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/process-control-and-elements-in-a-control-loop/</guid>
      <description>Process Control In order to produce a product with consistently high quality, tight process control is necessary. A simple-to-understand example of process control would be the supply of water to a number of cleaning stations, where the water temperature needs to be kept constant in spite of the demand. A simple control block is shown in Fig. 1.1a, steam, and cold water are fed into a heat exchanger, where heat from the steam is used to bring the cold water to the required working temperature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland cement materials and specifications</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/portland-cement-materials-and-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/portland-cement-materials-and-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Portland cement, the most common of modern cement, is made by carefully blending selected raw materials to produce a finished material meeting the requirements of ASTM C150 for one of eight specific cement types. Four major compounds [lime (CaO), iron (Fe2O3), silica (SiO2), and alumina (Al2O3)] and two minor compounds [gypsum (CaSO4 2H2O) and magnesia (MgO)] constitute the raw materials. The calcareous (CaO) materials typically come from limestone, calcite, marl, or shale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cementitious materials and their classification</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/02/cementitious-materials-and-their-classification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/02/cementitious-materials-and-their-classification/</guid>
      <description>Cementitious materials include the many products that are mixed with either water or some other liquid or both to form a cementing paste that may be formed or molded while plastic but will set into a rigid shape. When sand is added to the paste, mortar is formed. A combination of coarse and fine aggregate (sand) added to the paste forms concrete.
Types of cementitious materials There are many varieties of cement and numerous ways of classification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building protection system against lightning and thundering</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-system-against-lightning-and-thundering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-system-against-lightning-and-thundering/</guid>
      <description>What is lightning or Thunder? Lightning, a high-voltage, high-current electrical discharge between clouds and the ground, may strike and destroy life and property anywhere thunderstorms have occurred in the past. Buildings and their occupants, however, can be protected against this hazard by the installation of a special electrical system. Because an incomplete or poor installation can cause worse damage or injuries than no protection at all, a lightning-protection system should be designed and installed by experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heating Oil Price Up In Altoona PA on 28 Jan 2023</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/heating-oil-price-up-in-altoona-pa-on-28-jan-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/heating-oil-price-up-in-altoona-pa-on-28-jan-2023/</guid>
      <description>Heating Oil&amp;rsquo;s latest price update (Ref. Sel-Lo Oil) | Prices last changed on 1/26/23 | Heating Oil
$ | Blend
$ | Kerosene
$ | Dyed ULSD (Off-Road)
$ 100 Gallon Minimum 4.31 5.51 6.71 4.41 Reference: Sel-Lo oil price in Altoona PA
Get Heating Oil Price trend from 2016 to 2023 Chart ORDER SEL-LO Oil In Altoona PA We are collecting Heating Oil, including Sel-Lo oil prices from 2016 to 2023 to show you how United States fuel prices ups and down from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building protection against fire</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-against-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/building-protection-against-fire/</guid>
      <description>There are two distinct aspects of building fire protection: life safety and property protection. Although providing for one aspect generally results in some protection for the other, the two goals are not mutually inclusive. A program that provides for prompt notification and evacuation of occupants meets the objectives for life safety but provides no protection for the property. Conversely, it is possible that adequate building protection might not be sufficient for the protection of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sel-Lo Oil Price update on 13 Jan 2023</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sel-lo-oil-price-update-on-13-jan-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sel-lo-oil-price-update-on-13-jan-2023/</guid>
      <description>Sel-Lo Oil latest price update on 13 Jan 2023 | Prices last changed on 1/13/23 | Heating Oil
$ | Blend
$ | Kerosene
$ | Dyed ULSD (Off-Road)
$ 100 Gallon Minimum 3.99 4.79 5.59 4.09 Over 200 Gallons 3.95 4.75 5.55 4.09 Over 400 Gallons 3.93 4.73 5.53 4.05 Over 800 Gallons 3.91 4.71 5.51 4.05 Over 1200 Gallons 3.87 4.67 5.47 4.01 Table: Sel-Lo oil price
Get Sel-Lo Oil Price trend from 2016 to 2023 If you have problem to see preview of above Sel-Lo oil price chart, please click on link: Click to see Sel-Lo oil price change trend chart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combating human trafficking and forced labor</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/combating-human-trafficking-and-forced-labor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/combating-human-trafficking-and-forced-labor/</guid>
      <description>KEY ISSUES What is human trafficking &amp;amp; forced labor?
The challenge and response, including the California Transparency
Supply Chain Act and what LF is doing
Risks for global supply chains
Red flags and indicators of potential human trafficking &amp;amp; forced labor
Detecting and addressing potential instances of human trafficking &amp;amp; forced labor
WHAT IS HUMAN TRAFFICKING &amp;amp; FORCED LABOR? WHAT IS HUMAN TRAFFICKING? “The illegal trade of human beings for the purposes of exploitation forced labor and slavery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sello oil price update 07-Jan-2023</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sello-oil-price-update-07-jan-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sello-oil-price-update-07-jan-2023/</guid>
      <description>Sel-Lo Oil&amp;rsquo;s latest price update on 07 Jan 2023 | Prices last changed on 1/07/23 | Heating Oil
$ | Blend
$ | Kerosene
$ | Dyed ULSD (Off-Road)
$ 100 Gallon Minimum 3.99 4.79 5.59 4.09 Over 200 Gallons 3.95 4.75 5.55 4.09 Over 400 Gallons 3.93 4.73 5.53 4.05 Over 800 Gallons 3.91 4.71 5.51 4.05 Over 1200 Gallons 3.87 4.67 5.47 4.01 Table: Sel-Lo oil price
Get Sel-Lo Oil Price trend from 2016 to 2023 If you have problem to see preview of above Sel-Lo oil price chart, please click on link: Click to see Sel-Lo oil price change trend chart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</guid>
      <description>for New Construction, Major Renovation, and Commercial Interiors Introduction Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation Suggestions present a menu of options that can be adopted or implemented to integrate sustainable design, equipment, materials and other elements into new buildings and major renovations. The Suggestions include elements scored by the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design (LEED) standard, as well as the best practices Bdmeter has implemented in our global network.
Suppliers worldwide are encouraged to adopt as many of the items in these Suggestions whenever feasible and applicable to your location and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Khulnaflix</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/whats-khulnaflix/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/whats-khulnaflix/</guid>
      <description>Khulnaflix is an FTP server in the southeast region of Asia, Khulna BD. Its total size is more than thousands of gigabyte and khulnaflix have millions of happy customers locally. Khulnaflix&amp;rsquo;s name came from the city name Khulna and flix came from the media entertainment place online. So, Khulnaflix comes into life for Khulna and BD as well as all over the world from Khulna. Khulnaflix has better streaming and quality movies live streaming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zoning and building codes</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/zoning-and-building-codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/zoning-and-building-codes/</guid>
      <description>Many of the restrictions encountered in building design are imposed by legal regulations. While all must be met, those in building codes are the most significant because they affect almost every part of a building. Building codes are established under the police powers of a state to protect the health, welfare, and safety of communities. A code is administered by a building official of the municipality or state that adopts it by legislation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace building safety management</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/workplace-building-safety-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/12/workplace-building-safety-management/</guid>
      <description>This content will help Engineers, and architects learn about industrial or, warehouse building safety management and help to achieve certificates easily. It’s not easy to get building certificates and this article will help us to know about the step-by-step process to implement building safety in our own business zone and apply to achieve international certificates.
Evacuation map In case of emergency: Don&amp;rsquo;t panic
Leave the building in CALM by the nearest exit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to protect your building against wind, storm, or tornado</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</guid>
      <description>For practical design, wind and earthquakes may be treated as horizontal, or lateral, loads. Although wind and seismic loads may have vertical components, these generally are small and readily resisted by columns and bearing walls. Vertical earthquake components can be important in the design of connections as in precast concrete structures. Wind often generates significant uplift forces that require special attention to vertical restraint and lateral support for members in reverse bending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A study of digital circuits and converting to digital signals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/a-study-of-digital-circuits-and-converting-to-digital-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/a-study-of-digital-circuits-and-converting-to-digital-signals/</guid>
      <description>What are Digital circuits and digital signals?
The study of electronic circuits where the inputs and outputs are limited to two fixed or discrete values or logic levels is called digital electronics. Digital technology would take many signals to do justice, so in this text, we can only scratch the surface. There is a place for both analog and digital circuits in instrumentation. Sensors and instrumentation functions are analog in nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building construction protection against water, flood, and heavy rainfall</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/building-construction-protection-against-water-flood-and-heavy-rainfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/building-construction-protection-against-water-flood-and-heavy-rainfall/</guid>
      <description>PROTECTION AGAINST WATER Whether thrust against and into a building by a flood, driven into the interior by heavy rain, leaking from plumbing, storm surge, or seeping through the exterior enclosure, water can cause costly damage to a building. Consequently, designers should protect buildings and their contents against water damage.
Protective measures may be divided into two classes: floodproofing and waterproofing. Floodproofing provides protection against flowing surface water, commonly caused by a river overflowing its banks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light and sight: Lighting control system</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/09/light-and-sight-lighting-control-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/09/light-and-sight-lighting-control-system/</guid>
      <description>Lighting is part of the environmental control system, which also includes sound control and heating, ventilation, and air conditioning (HVAC), within a building.
The prime purpose of a lighting system is to provide good visibility for the execution of the tasks to be performed within the building. With good visibility, occupants can execute their tasks comfortably, efficiently, and safely.
Lighting also is desirable for other purposes. For example, it can be used to develop color effects for pleasure or accident prevention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk Assessment: Cosmetics Manufacturing Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/09/risk-assessment-cosmetics-manufacturing-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/09/risk-assessment-cosmetics-manufacturing-process/</guid>
      <description>Steps for Process-related Risk Assessment Understand the process flow on how to manufacture the product
Identify the hazards from its process step (task)
Decide who might be harmed and how
Evaluate the risks and decide on precaution
Record your findings and implement them
Review your assessment and update if necessary
Cosmetic Flow Production Process Flow Cosmetic Flow Production Process Flow
Cosmetic Production Process Flow Common EHS Hazards Receiving raw material from W/H</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building stones and it&#39;s properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/building-stones-and-its-properties/</guid>
      <description>Principal building stones generally used in the United States are limestones, marbles, granites, and sandstones. Other stones such as serpentine and quartzite are used locally but to a much lesser extent. Stone, in general, makes an excellent
building material, if properly selected on the basis of experience; but the cost may be relatively high.
The properties of stone depend on what nature has provided. Therefore, the designer does not have the choice of properties and colors available in some of the manufactured building units.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corrosion of iron and steel: Preventive action to stop corrosion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/corrosion-of-iron-and-steel-preventive-action-to-stop-corrosion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/corrosion-of-iron-and-steel-preventive-action-to-stop-corrosion/</guid>
      <description>Corrosion of ferrous metals is caused by the tendency of iron (anode) to go into solution in water as ferrous hydroxide and displace hydrogen, which in turn combines with dissolved oxygen to form more water. At the same time, the dissolved ferrous hydroxide is converted by more oxygen to the insoluble ferric hydroxide, thereby allowing more iron to go into the solution. Corrosion, therefore, requires liquid water (as in damp air) and oxygen (which is normally present dissolved in the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about plastic and polymer processing</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-about-plastic-and-polymer-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-about-plastic-and-polymer-processing/</guid>
      <description>Melt Processing Melt processing is the most important, most economical way of shaping plastics. It can be used for those thermoplastics with melting points and viscosity low enough not to subject die materials to excessive temperatures and stresses.
(a) Melt Processing of Thermoplastics: The raw material to be processed is usually supplied in the form of regular shape and even-size granules, because this makes quantity metering easier and quicker and leads to more uniform and predictable heating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steps for Process-related Risk  Assessment in the Plastic Toys Industry</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</guid>
      <description>Understand the process flow on how to manufacture the product. Identify the hazards from its process step (task). Decide who might be harmed and how. Evaluate the risks and decide on precautions. Record your findings and implement them 6. Review your assessment and update if necessary. Plastic Toys Production Process Flow: Fig: process flow of toys production
Types of Materials used for Injection Molding SL. Material name Description Applications 1 Acetal Strong, rigid, excellent fatigue resistance, excellent creep resistance, chemical resistance, moisture resistance, naturally opaque white, low/medium cost Bearings, cams, gears, handles, plumbing components, rollers, rotors, slide guides, valves 2 Acrylic Rigid, brittle, scratch resistant, transparent, optical clarity, low/medium cost Display stands, knobs, lenses, light housings, panels, reflectors, signs, shelves, trays 3 Acrylonitrile Butadiene Styrene Strong, flexible, low mold shrinkage (tight tolerances), chemical resistance, electroplating capability, naturally opaque, low/medium cost Automotive (consoles, panels, trim, vents), boxes, gauges, housings, inhalers, toys 4 Cellulose Acetate Tough, transparent, high cost Handles, eyeglass frames 5 Polyamide 6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Bearings, bushings, gears, rollers, wheels 6 Polyamide 6/6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Handles, levers, small housings, zip ties 7 Polyamide 11+12 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque to clear, very high cost Air filters, eyeglass frames, safety masks 8 Polycarbonate Very tough, temperature resistance, dimensional stability, transparent, high cost Automotive (panels, lenses, consoles), bottles, containers, housings, light covers, reflectors, safety helmets, and shields 9 Polyester - Thermoplastic Rigid, heat resistance, chemical resistance, medium/high cost Automotive (filters, handles, pumps), bearings, cams, electrical components (connectors, sensors), gears, housings, rollers, switches, valves 10 Polyether Tough, very high chemical resistance, clear, very high-cost Sulphone Valves 11 Polyetheretherketone Strong, thermal stability, chemical resistance, abrasion resistance, low moisture absorption Aircraft components, electrical connectors, pump impellers, seals 12 Polyetherimide Heat resistance, flame resistance, transparent (amber color) Electrical components (connectors, boards, switches), covers, shields, surgical tools 13 Polyethylene - Low Density Lightweight, tough and flexible, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Kitchenware, housings, covers, and containers 14 Polyethylene - High Density Tough and stiff, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Chair seats, housings, covers, and containers 15 Polyphenylene Oxide Tough, heat resistance, flame resistance, dimensional stability, low water absorption, electroplating capability, high cost Automotive (housings, panels), electrical components, housings, plumbing components 16 Polyphenylene Sulphide Very high strength, heat resistance, brown, very high cost Bearings, covers, fuel system components, guides, switches, and shields 17 Polypropylene Lightweight, heat resistance, high chemical resistance, scratch resistance, natural waxy appearance, tough and stiff, low cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional and business requirements of architects and engineers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/professional-and-business-requirements-of-architects-and-engineers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/professional-and-business-requirements-of-architects-and-engineers/</guid>
      <description>Management of the building process is best performed by the individuals educated and trained in the profession, that is, architects and engineers. While the laws of various states and foreign countries differ, they are consistent relative to the registration requirements for practicing architecture. No individual may legally indicate to the public that he or she is entitled to practice as an architect without a professional certificate of registration as an architect registered in the locale in which the project is to be constructed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn major building systems</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-major-building-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/learn-major-building-systems/</guid>
      <description>The simplest building system consists of only two components. One component is a floor, a flat, horizontal surface on which human activities can take place. The other component is an enclosure that extends over the floor and generally also around it to provide shelter from the weather for human activities.
The ground may serve as the floor in primitive buildings. In better buildings, however, the floor may be a structural deck laid on the ground or supported above ground on structural members, such as the joist and walls in Fig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greenhouse Gases and Renewable Energy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</guid>
      <description>Effect greenhouse What are greenhouse gases (GHG)? Greenhouse gases (GHGs) trap heat within the earth’s atmosphere, contributing to the ‘greenhouse’ effect and causing global warming. These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide, and water vapor. Industry, including manufacturing, is the second largest global emitter of human-created GHGs. Much of industrial GHG emissions are due to the burning of fossil fuels for heat and power generation.
Why should I care about GHGs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textile Sewing Machine Maintenance Checklist</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/textile-sewing-machine-maintenance-checklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/textile-sewing-machine-maintenance-checklist/</guid>
      <description>This article is about learning how to prepare a textile/garment sewing process maintenance checklist and the way to accomplish this procedure as periodic maintenance.
SEWING MAINTENANCE CHECKLIST Many Retail, Brand-name Marketing, Mail Order, and Sourcing Companies are visiting existing and potential Contractor sewing facilities and evaluating their sewing capabilities for producing quality products for their customers. In many cases, they even rate the vendor and give the plant a grade based on their observations during their visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building contractor&#39;s insurance restoration services in the United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/building-contractors-insurance-restoration-services-in-the-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/building-contractors-insurance-restoration-services-in-the-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Building contractor&amp;rsquo;s insurance services are very much important for contractors&amp;rsquo; life. Because there have so many uncertain hazards related to building construction works. That&amp;rsquo;s the reason building constructors live under different crises during building development works.
Roofing contractors need that insurance coverage in the service sector. There are many top-level roofing contractors&amp;rsquo; insurance services all over the United States area.
Take a short look at Illions Roofing Contractors&amp;rsquo; list with Addresses, Phone Numbers And, Email Addresses: To be continued&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best economical structures of building construction</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</guid>
      <description>STRUCTURAL STEEL CONSTRUCTION Structural steel is the economical construction material for building applications. It offers high ratios of strength to weight and strength to volume. Thus, structural steel has the advantage of permitting long clear spans for horizontal members and requiring less floor space for columns than other common construction materials. It also can be used in combination with reinforced concrete to provide cost-effective building components. For large industrial buildings, where the structural frame can be exposed, it is often the material of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different types of Steel Grades</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</guid>
      <description>Structural steel grades are referred to by their corresponding ASTM designation. For example, the most commonly used grade of structural steel is A36, which is produced to meet the requirements of the ASTM A36 specification. This grade offers a good mix of strength, weldability, and cost. In many designs, this specification alone will satisfy designers’ needs. Other specifications, such as A53 for pipe, provide an equivalent grade of steel for that type of product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Design Your Building Against Earthquake</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</guid>
      <description>Buildings should be designed to withstand minor earthquakes without damage, because they may occur almost everywhere. For major earthquakes, it may not be economical to prevent all damage but collapse should be precluded. Because an earthquake and a high wind are not likely to occur simultaneously, building codes usually do not require that buildings be designed for a combination of large seismic and wind loads. Thus, designers may assume that the full strength of wind bracing is also available to resist drift caused by earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about different types of industrial trucks &amp; vehicles</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Industrial vehicles/trucks are one of the most common groups of materials handling equipment used in industry as well as in the day-to-day distribution of goods in warehouses, large stores, transport depots, etc. The basic operation and construction features of some of the common types of industrial trucks will be discussed here. The adjective ‘‘industrial’’ used before this group of vehicles/trucks is to distinguish these from other groups of vehicles like buses, lorries, trucks, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Different Kinds of Sensors: Position and Motion Measurement</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-different-kinds-of-sensors-position-and-motion-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-different-kinds-of-sensors-position-and-motion-measurement/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you understand and become familiar with other sensors that play a very important part in process control, but may not be encountered on a daily basis. The following are covered in this chapter:
■ Position, distance, velocity, and acceleration sensors
■ Rotation sensors using light and Hall effect sensors
■ Force, torque, load cells, and balances
■ Smoke detectors, gas, and chemical sensors in the industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future: Material Handling Using Robots In Workplace</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/the-future-material-handling-using-robots-in-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/the-future-material-handling-using-robots-in-workplace/</guid>
      <description>MATERIALS HANDLING AT THE WORKPLACE Feeding parts and components into a machine for their processing and taking them out is an important activity in any discrete mass manufacturing process. This is known as materials handling at the workplace.
Operating robots in electronics lab
Robotic handling in Cable industry
Robot in complex operation in electroniocs industry
Robot to handle carton in industry
Robots ready as an Engineer
Robot in operation
Robotic Hand to handle carton on pallet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textile In Civil Engineering: Geotextile</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/textile-in-civil-engineering-geotextile/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/textile-in-civil-engineering-geotextile/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to geotextiles Although skins, brushwood, and straw–mud composites have been used to improve the soft ground for many thousands of years, it is not realistic to refer to these as ‘geotextiles’. The important factor that separates them from modern geotextiles is that they cannot be made with specific and consistent properties. When modern polymers were developed in the mid 20th century, it became possible to create textiles with designed forecastable performance and to produce them in large quantities with statistically consistent and repeatable properties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Environmental Biotechnology</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</guid>
      <description>When modern industrialization started in the 19th century, many people migrated from the agricultural area to the big cities. Public hygiene became a major problem. Human excrement and waste was discharged into open channels, rivers, and lakes. The pollution was disastrous and hygiene-related epidemic diseases, like cholera and typhus, occurred frequently. Therefore, it was an important step forward when public water collection systems and treatment plants were introduced at the end of the 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Basic Electrical Components</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-basic-electrical-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-basic-electrical-components/</guid>
      <description>This blog will help to refresh and expand your understanding of basic electrical components and the basic terms used in electricity as required for instrumentation.
This chapter discusses
■ Basic passive components (resistors, capacitors, and inductors) used in electrical circuits
■ Applications of Ohm’s law and Kirchoff’s laws
■ Use of resistors as voltage dividers
■ Effective equivalent circuits for basic devices connected in series and parallel
■ The Wheatstone bridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Sprinkler System Installation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Automatic fire sprinkler systems have been protecting property in the United States since the late 1800s; in fact, the Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems, 1896 was the first standard developed by the National Fire Protection Association (NFPA). Today the NFPA still develops the most widely accepted standards for the design and installation of sprinkler systems: NFPA 13, Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems; 20, Installation of Centrifugal Fire Pumps; 24, Installation of Private Fire Services Mains and Their Appurtenances; 231, General Storage and 231C, Rack Storage of Materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</guid>
      <description>Today we will learn about vendor compliance and sustainability terms to identify hazards and assess risks.
Agenda:
Terms &amp;amp; Definitions HIRA Process Hazard Identification Risk Matrix &amp;amp; Risk Assessment Operational Controls Good Documentation Practices &amp;amp; Recommendations Company Sustainability Development Example HIRA &amp;amp; Discussion Factory Assignment : Risk Never Sleeps! The Cost of Safety The Importance of Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment HIRA is the Basis (First Step) to SafeGuard Employees, Contractors, Visitors, Contract workers, People who share the workplace from Significant Injuries or ill Health in a Systematic Approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lean Thinking, Lean Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/lean-thinking-lean-manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/lean-thinking-lean-manufacturing/</guid>
      <description>What is Lean Manufacturing? “A systematic approach to identifying and eliminating waste (non-value-added activities) through continuous improvement by flowing the product at the pull of the customer in pursuit of perfection” – The MEP Lean Network
Lean manufacturing is a set of principles, concepts, and techniques for suppliers to deliver:
Exactly what customers need and pay for When they need it The right quantity product or service needed Without defects At the lowest possible cost Lean is about continually improving processes and products by identifying what can be fixed or enhanced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Sustainable Building or Green Building</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</guid>
      <description>What is a sustainable building? For your building to be sustainable, many factors need to be considered. These include air quality, energy
efficiency, and the use of ‘green’ materials among others. This document focuses on 1) building a sustainable building 2) retrofitting and 3) certification.
Why should I make my buildings sustainable? Apart from the environmental benefits, a sustainable building can reduce your operational costs by as much as 30-50% on your energy usage and 40-50% on your water usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Fire Safety Management System</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-fire-safety-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-fire-safety-management-system/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you to learn about industrial fire safety management system implementation, analysis, and inspection systems to install fire safety management systems in your own industrial premises.
We have completed our fire safety project implementation in an Indonesian Apparel manufacturer industry location is &amp;ldquo;Jl. Raya Wantilan RT.07/03, Ds. Wantilan, Kec. Wantilan, Kab. Subang, Jawa Barat&amp;rdquo;
In this fire safety project implementation, a total of 1164 Employees attended and, contributed their efforts to make this project successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Smoke and Chemical Sensors Process Control</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/industrial-smoke-and-chemical-sensors-process-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/industrial-smoke-and-chemical-sensors-process-control/</guid>
      <description>This article will help you understand and become familiar with other sensors that play a very important part in process control, but may not be encountered on a daily basis. The following are covered in this article:
■ Position, distance, velocity, and acceleration sensors
■ Rotation sensors using light and Hall effect sensors
■ Force, torque, load cells, and balances
■ Smoke detectors, gas, and chemical sensors in the industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics and Classifications Of Industrial Materials</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/characteristics-and-classifications-of-industrial-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/characteristics-and-classifications-of-industrial-materials/</guid>
      <description>Materials handling system Method to be adopted and choice of equipment for a materials handling system primarily depends on the type of material/s to be handled. It is, therefore, very important to know about different types of materials and their characteristics which are related to methods and equipment used for their handling.
As innumerable different materials are used and need to be handled in industries, they are classified based on specific characteristics relevant to their handling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
