<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TechTalk on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TechTalk on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:50:51 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Future of Technology in the United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/future-of-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 13:50:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/future-of-technology/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: The United States has long been at the forefront of technological innovation, consistently pushing boundaries and revolutionizing various industries. From the invention of the telephone to the advent of the Internet, the US has shaped the course of human progress. As we look ahead into the future, it is impossible to ignore the exciting developments and breakthroughs that await us. In this blog, we will delve into the potential future technologies that are set to transform the landscape of the United States and the way we live, work, and interact with the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain for sale from $0.1</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 13:50:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/domain/</guid>
      <description>Domain registration Get discounted .COMs with no limits Why choose a .COM domain?
Make a mighty .com your dedicated online address. One of the original top-level domains, the .com top-level domain (TLD) is the best option for building any trusted website. It’s an instant seal of approval for your brand and practically goes hand-in-hand with the Internet itself.
Is a .COM extension right for me?
The .com TLD is universal, known in every country and every market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D classic logo design</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-classic-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-classic-logo/</guid>
      <description>3D classic logo design using adobe cc 2020 3D classic logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020. Learn online Adobe Illustrator by Channel 365. All content created by a skilled graphics designer from India and content authority verified. This content will help you to learn about Adobe Illustrator 3D classic logo design using Adobe Illustrator cc 2020. Adobe illustrator 2020 cc is almost the same as Adobe illustrator 2021 latest update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D colorful logo design</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-colorful-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/3d-colorful-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>3D colorful logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020 Welcome to Adobe illustrator course cc 2020. And in this video I will be teaching you how you can create colorful logo. Now it’s super easy to do and let’s see how that’s done.
The first thing we have to do is to create on your document. So the document that I wouldn’t be using for district auditor is this custom sized document which is called in by a thousand pixels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abstract animal logo design</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/animal-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/animal-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>Abstract animal logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020 Abstract animal logo design using adobe illustrator cc 2020. Learn online Adobe Illustrator by Channel 365. All content created by a skilled graphics designer from India and content authority verified. This content will help you to learn about Adobe Illustrator Abstract animal logo design using Adobe Illustrator cc 2020. Adobe illustrator 2020 cc is almost the same as Adobe illustrator 2021 latest update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Create Google Sitemap</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/how-to-create-google-sitemap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/how-to-create-google-sitemap/</guid>
      <description>How To Create Google Sitemap in Ubuntu 20.04 Today we will learn how to create Google Sitemap. Google Sitemap is very important because you need to do page ranking with Google Sitemap. Sitemap is a type of mapping where there will be links to all the pages of your website. You can easily create a sitemap on the Linux operating system.
With Sitemap you can crawl any website online, but WordPress site php coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create Rectangle, Circle and Straigt line using Inkscape</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/-create-rectangle-circle-and-straigt-line-using-inkscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/-create-rectangle-circle-and-straigt-line-using-inkscape/</guid>
      <description>Create Rectangle, Circle and Straigt line using Inkscape Today we will learn how to create Rectangle, Circle and Straigt line using Inkscape.
Inkscape is a great design tool to create SVG images. Using Inkscape you can learn different designs very easily.
First you have to open Inkscape and follow below steps:
Select File –&amp;gt; New from Template –&amp;gt; Select your required template.
Then For straight line, select Draw Baizer curve and Straight lines tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube marketing cource CPA marketplace online</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/youtube-marketing-cpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:44:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/techtalk/youtube-marketing-cpa/</guid>
      <description>Learn CPA Marketing and YouTube Marketing Learn how to do youtube marketing in Bengali in this video tutorial. How to do SEO, how to make a profit of product online we can learn from here in this video tutorial. You can grow your product marketplace using youtube. youtube is the most popular place in your product market. To analyze a product quality you use some reviews and analysis in a video to grow your market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
