<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>process-flow on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/process-flow/</link>
    <description>Recent content in process-flow on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/process-flow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Steps for Process-related Risk  Assessment in the Plastic Toys Industry</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/steps-for-process-related-risk-assessment-in-the-plastic-toys-industry/</guid>
      <description>Understand the process flow on how to manufacture the product. Identify the hazards from its process step (task). Decide who might be harmed and how. Evaluate the risks and decide on precautions. Record your findings and implement them 6. Review your assessment and update if necessary. Plastic Toys Production Process Flow: Fig: process flow of toys production
Types of Materials used for Injection Molding SL. Material name Description Applications 1 Acetal Strong, rigid, excellent fatigue resistance, excellent creep resistance, chemical resistance, moisture resistance, naturally opaque white, low/medium cost Bearings, cams, gears, handles, plumbing components, rollers, rotors, slide guides, valves 2 Acrylic Rigid, brittle, scratch resistant, transparent, optical clarity, low/medium cost Display stands, knobs, lenses, light housings, panels, reflectors, signs, shelves, trays 3 Acrylonitrile Butadiene Styrene Strong, flexible, low mold shrinkage (tight tolerances), chemical resistance, electroplating capability, naturally opaque, low/medium cost Automotive (consoles, panels, trim, vents), boxes, gauges, housings, inhalers, toys 4 Cellulose Acetate Tough, transparent, high cost Handles, eyeglass frames 5 Polyamide 6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Bearings, bushings, gears, rollers, wheels 6 Polyamide 6/6 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque/white, medium/high cost Handles, levers, small housings, zip ties 7 Polyamide 11+12 (Nylon) High strength, fatigue resistance, chemical resistance, low creep, low friction, almost opaque to clear, very high cost Air filters, eyeglass frames, safety masks 8 Polycarbonate Very tough, temperature resistance, dimensional stability, transparent, high cost Automotive (panels, lenses, consoles), bottles, containers, housings, light covers, reflectors, safety helmets, and shields 9 Polyester - Thermoplastic Rigid, heat resistance, chemical resistance, medium/high cost Automotive (filters, handles, pumps), bearings, cams, electrical components (connectors, sensors), gears, housings, rollers, switches, valves 10 Polyether Tough, very high chemical resistance, clear, very high-cost Sulphone Valves 11 Polyetheretherketone Strong, thermal stability, chemical resistance, abrasion resistance, low moisture absorption Aircraft components, electrical connectors, pump impellers, seals 12 Polyetherimide Heat resistance, flame resistance, transparent (amber color) Electrical components (connectors, boards, switches), covers, shields, surgical tools 13 Polyethylene - Low Density Lightweight, tough and flexible, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Kitchenware, housings, covers, and containers 14 Polyethylene - High Density Tough and stiff, excellent chemical resistance, natural waxy appearance, low cost Chair seats, housings, covers, and containers 15 Polyphenylene Oxide Tough, heat resistance, flame resistance, dimensional stability, low water absorption, electroplating capability, high cost Automotive (housings, panels), electrical components, housings, plumbing components 16 Polyphenylene Sulphide Very high strength, heat resistance, brown, very high cost Bearings, covers, fuel system components, guides, switches, and shields 17 Polypropylene Lightweight, heat resistance, high chemical resistance, scratch resistance, natural waxy appearance, tough and stiff, low cost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
