<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>garment on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/garment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in garment on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/garment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Safety guideline: How to measure a drawstring in kids pant</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-02-safety-guideline-how-to-measure-a-drawstring-in-kids-pant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-02-safety-guideline-how-to-measure-a-drawstring-in-kids-pant/</guid>
      <description>[fluid-player video=&amp;ldquo;https://bdmeter.info/video/how%20to%20measure%20drawstring.mp4&#34; vast_file=&amp;ldquo;https://www.videosprofitnetwork.com/watch.xml?key=3780f50bd5e6cd43ba1c2d60f209cd44&#34;]
How to measure drawstring in five easy steps: Step one: Pull out the drawstrings end completely. This is to ensure verifying whether drawstring ends are fixed securely.
Step one
Step two: Re-open the garment flat on the table two end extended. So that the drawstring extended in the tunnel. Please make sure to not over straighten the garment.
Step two
Step three: Straighten the free ends of the drawstring and measure the length.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn How To Create an SOP of Claim And Complain Of QC</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we got a quality complaint and claim, we need to provide a reasonable explanation to the buyer how and why it happened. To provide this explanation, we need to make a thorough investigation to find out the possible root cause as well as provide the correct action plan to avoid future happening. During the investigation, we need to involve a lot of data and questions. In our past experiences, we spent a lot of time back and forth emails to collect the data and find out the root cause because either we forgot to check this or that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Textile Manufacturer List In Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is one of the largest and biggest manufacturers of textile goods and materials over decades. Bangladesh has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest garment and textile manufacturer after China. After Coronavirus spreads all over the world from 2019 to 2021, the world market is changing dramatically. The apparel and fashion goods-making market is changing. Bangladesh has a total of more than 7000 industries in this sector. Bangladesh already achieved the world&amp;rsquo;s largest knitwear manufacturer country in the western marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knit Garments CM Calculation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</guid>
      <description>In Apparel and Fashion industry, CM means Cost of Manufacture. In the garment manufacturing industry, CM means Manufacturing Cost of one dozen or 12 pcs garments. To calculate the CM of 12 pcs knit garments we must follow the below criterion-
monthly expenditure of the industry total no. of running machine machine qty to execute the layout of the specific order, productivity per shift dollar exchange rate Let, Monthly Industry Expenditure is BDT 80,00,000 Working days of the 30 days = 26 days Daily Factory Expenditure = BDT 307692.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPIs of Quality Management for Clothing Factories</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-27-performance-indicators-of-quality-management-system-in-a-garment-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-27-performance-indicators-of-quality-management-system-in-a-garment-industry/</guid>
      <description>In the apparel industry, professionals always talk about product quality, defects, and quality systems. To the buyers – the end product what they are receiving from factory, quality should be as per the requirement. No more, no less. Earlier buyers don’t bother how a factory makes quality? How much extra pieces they have processed to achieve all good pieces to handover the buyer?
On the other side, factories don’t think how much money they are losing through repair work and garment rejection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Printing Capacity Calculation Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-15-garment-printing-capacity-calculation-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-15-garment-printing-capacity-calculation-process/</guid>
      <description>Print Production capacity calculation Area: Screen Printing (Machine &amp;amp; manual)
Objectives: To identify printing machine production capacity and set printing target plan to achieve ultimate goal.
Machine type:
Name: M&amp;amp;R Printing machine No of Wings: 10 wings Machine quantity: 01 pc
Table type: Properties: Artificial leather &amp;amp; Glass
No. of table: 12 tables Average color: 06 color
Average printing area: (8*8) sq. inch
Printing Capacity calculation: For manual printing (Table),</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Supplier Safety And Product Quality Specifications</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-garment-supplier-safety-and-product-quality-specifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-garment-supplier-safety-and-product-quality-specifications/</guid>
      <description>Suppliers of private brand products to Fashion Retail (the “Suppliers”) and its subsidiaries undertake to
comply with the following requirements.
Product safety and quality 1.1. The Suppliers must assure: 1.1.1. The safety and the compliance of the products with the laws and standards in force in the countries
of sale at the time of purchase
1.1.2. A level of aesthetic quality, performance, and minimum product life that is usual for the kind of goods</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Projects</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-fashion-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-fashion-projects/</guid>
      <description>https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lauren-wadkins-7a7a474b_designer-design-interview-activity-6767423142542491648-rFAv
Over past few months world have several fashion projects for prospective designer opportunities. Even though they are still looking for more fashion design projects to prepare for next fashion trends. There have ladies items fashion design and those are very much popular globally. They are trying to do much more projects and looking for sample Development from global manufacturer. There are many manufacturer from Asia Europe hub. Fashion designers are looking for fashion show samples and once any design will sold out to brand owner, them Fashion designers will make consumption and pricing for the next season fashion goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Sewing Operator Training Program Guideline</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create a garment sewing operator training module. This training module was developed and tested successfully to take thousands of sewing operators training in different garment and textile manufacturing industries in Bangladesh. This training module fully structured and full of all technical guidelines about garment sewing operator&amp;rsquo;s long-time training procedure, schedule, practical training guide, technical sewing information, exam process, and others all necessary reporting formats. The step-by-step guide will help garment and textile manufacturers globally to know how to train sewing operators in big industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Operating Procedure of A Small Business</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</guid>
      <description>Standard operating procedures (SOP) of a garment idustry A Standard Operating Procedure or SOP means is structured documentation that provides step-by-step guidelines and instructions on how to do a particular business activity, such as production or record keeping. We need SOP in a company with different operations in different areas.
Example of business operating procedure manual: Standard operating procedures or SOP needs to develop as a structured documented office word or pdf file and manual printed copy for management approval.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
