<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>standard-operating-procedure on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/standard-operating-procedure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in standard-operating-procedure on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/standard-operating-procedure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn How To Create an SOP of Claim And Complain Of QC</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-19-learn-how-to-create-an-sop-of-claim-and-complain-of-qc/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we got a quality complaint and claim, we need to provide a reasonable explanation to the buyer how and why it happened. To provide this explanation, we need to make a thorough investigation to find out the possible root cause as well as provide the correct action plan to avoid future happening. During the investigation, we need to involve a lot of data and questions. In our past experiences, we spent a lot of time back and forth emails to collect the data and find out the root cause because either we forgot to check this or that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOP of claim and complaint</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-11-sop-of-claim-and-complaint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-11-sop-of-claim-and-complaint/</guid>
      <description>Whenever we got a quality complaint and claim, we need to provide a reasonable explanation to the buyer of how and why it happened. To provide this explanation, we need to make a thorough investigation to find out the possible root cause as well as provide the correct action plan to avoid future happening. During the investigation, we need to involve a lot of data and questions. In our past experiences, we spent a lot of time back and forth emails to collect the data and find out the root cause because either we forgot to check this or that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supplier Quality Management System</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-supplier-quality-management-system-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-28-supplier-quality-management-system-ca/</guid>
      <description>Inspection manual for suppliers This manual is part of the Quality Management System which remains the reference with the updated versions
I – Inspection tools The supplier has to supply to the inspector the following information:
the correct approval sample, accompanied by sample approval form and size specifications; the results of the fabric tests; a complete and confirmed fabric and accessory card when necessary; an up-to-date copy of the order with the latest remarks; previous inspection reports and In line inspection reports if available; list of QCCI codes After identification of the total quantity delivered, the Square Root Sample Matrix is used to select the sample pick at random and throughout the entire shipment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fabric Inspection Standard Procedures</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-fabric-inspection-standard-procedures/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-fabric-inspection-standard-procedures/</guid>
      <description>In general, There are two type of fabrics need to inspect during fabric manufacturing.
Greige fabric inspection Final fabric inspection GREIGE FABRIC INSPECTION PROCEDURE: PROCESS DEFINITION: Shell Fabric inspection: Greige fabric inspection process defined as a system of visual assessment through an inspection machine to detect and identify the knitting faults in the fabric produced by a Circular Knit Machine. Collar &amp;amp; Cuff inspection: Expected quality verification of Collar and Cuff fabric produced in Flat Knit Machine is called collar cuff inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOP of Sewing Inline and Initial Process Inspection</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-sop-of-sewing-inline-and-initial-process-inspection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-25-sop-of-sewing-inline-and-initial-process-inspection/</guid>
      <description>Purpose For Ensuring the Quality of the Initial product output is according to buyer required standard. Scope Starts from Setting the required tools, Equipment, Guidelines, and Instructions in the Sewing room quality controlling workstation by the factory QC department. Responsible for process The output should be inspected for Construction, styling, Material, Measurements, Aesthetic, Overall workmanship &amp;amp; defects, very thoroughly.
Guidelines as a sample, Sample Comments, First Piece Approval, Aesthetic Standard Approvals, Approved Trim Card, Key Quality Instructions, Checking sequence, should be used for the inspection by performers of the inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Housekeeping Manual of Largest Industry</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-housekeeping-manual-of-largest-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-housekeeping-manual-of-largest-industry/</guid>
      <description>General Housekeeping Manual, A Guideline for Good Housekeeping Practice in Workplace. This manual is prepared by the Department of SOP, Textile Group of Companies. This edition developed on dates September 2020.
This manual is issued for A Textile Group of Companies and can be obtained from SOP Department. Please contact www.bdmeter.info for custom development
This guideline is not for advertising, endorsement, or commercial purposes. Please acknowledge the source as &amp;ldquo;Guidelines for Good housekeeping Practice in a Workplace&amp;rdquo;, published by the Policy Implementation and Risk Management-Textile Group of Companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Sewing Operator Training Program Guideline</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create a garment sewing operator training module. This training module was developed and tested successfully to take thousands of sewing operators training in different garment and textile manufacturing industries in Bangladesh. This training module fully structured and full of all technical guidelines about garment sewing operator&amp;rsquo;s long-time training procedure, schedule, practical training guide, technical sewing information, exam process, and others all necessary reporting formats. The step-by-step guide will help garment and textile manufacturers globally to know how to train sewing operators in big industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Operating Procedure of A Small Business</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-17-standard-operating-procedure-of-a-garment-industry/</guid>
      <description>Standard operating procedures (SOP) of a garment idustry A Standard Operating Procedure or SOP means is structured documentation that provides step-by-step guidelines and instructions on how to do a particular business activity, such as production or record keeping. We need SOP in a company with different operations in different areas.
Example of business operating procedure manual: Standard operating procedures or SOP needs to develop as a structured documented office word or pdf file and manual printed copy for management approval.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
