<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>asia on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in asia on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stunning Beautiful City Of Khulna</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-30-stunning-beautiful-city-of-khulna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-30-stunning-beautiful-city-of-khulna/</guid>
      <description>khulna is the third largest city of Bangladesh after Dhaka city and Chittagong City. Khulna is very old city and third largest economy area of Bangladesh out of others division. Khulna is most popular worldwide for largest mangrove forest specially for grand Royal Bengal tigers, the beautiful Sundari 🌴 tress and stunning beauty of green mangrove forests. Khulna is the second largest sea port city of Bangladesh. All imported cars, vehicles, heavy weight vehicles and carrier oil tanks, cargos entrance from Mongla port situated in khulna city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Textile Manufacturer List In Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-30-garment-textile-manufacturer-list-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is one of the largest and biggest manufacturers of textile goods and materials over decades. Bangladesh has the world&amp;rsquo;s largest garment and textile manufacturer after China. After Coronavirus spreads all over the world from 2019 to 2021, the world market is changing dramatically. The apparel and fashion goods-making market is changing. Bangladesh has a total of more than 7000 industries in this sector. Bangladesh already achieved the world&amp;rsquo;s largest knitwear manufacturer country in the western marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh Export Import Duty</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-24-bangladesh-export-import-duty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-24-bangladesh-export-import-duty/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh Government has export-import operative tariff plan executed and published by Bangladesh custom governing body. This board is under the Bangladesh National Board Of Revenue. Bangladesh customs are under the department of the National Board of Revenue. You can calculate import duty by this plan and this will help you in Bangladesh if you want to import products/materials/anything from the international marketplace.
Search Bangladesh Import Export Duty Tariff Plan: Download file here ::</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of all call centers in Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-23-list-of-all-call-centers-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-23-list-of-all-call-centers-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh emergency call centers number for hotline help organized by Bangladesh Government. All call centers help free of cost. These emergency contacts are free of cost. You can get 24/7 online help in case of emergency situation eg. legal, crime, public service, health, general health, mother &amp;amp; kids health, pregnancy period help, community support, international help, National helpline center for violence against women, National Emergency Hotline Number, Covid help, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh NID Registration</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-19-bangladesh-nid-registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-19-bangladesh-nid-registration/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for Bangladesh Government portal for NID Registration (National identify card registration), you can apply online. You need your valid birth certificate and registered mobile number and email address for security verification.
Voter ID (photo ID) registration documents: You need your father and mother&amp;rsquo;s name, NID for registration. If you have any brother or Sister or wife/husband available, you need their valid NID number during registration. Once registration done, you need to wait for approval.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A list of Government Ministry and Divisions of Bangladesh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-18-a-list-of-government-ministry-and-divisions-of-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-18-a-list-of-government-ministry-and-divisions-of-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Download a list of 58 Govt. Ministry and Divisions of Bangladesh.
The country is Bangladesh, the Capital city is Dhaka. Bangladesh has a total of 58 government ministries and divisions. Bangladesh Prime Minister name is Sheikh Hasina, daughter of the father of nation Sheikh Mujibor Rahman. Bangladesh has a total of 8 divisions, 64 sub-division, 492 Upuzila, and 4554 Union.
A full list of Bangladesh Ministry and Divisions: Download Here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapid cash fraudulent: watch this video to know details</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-rapid-cash-fraud-case-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-rapid-cash-fraud-case-analysis/</guid>
      <description>简体中文দেশের রেপিড ক্যাশ নামের প্লে ষ্টোরের এপ্লিকেশন টি আপনি খুব সহজেই ডাউনলোড করে ঘন্টা ব্যাপী সময় নষ্ট করে সর্বোচ্চ ২০০০ টাকার এপলাই করতে পারবেন। ৭ দিনের ভেতর টাকাটা আপনাকে ফেরত দিতে হবে। শুক্রবার এপলাই করলে ৪৮ ঘন্টা ওয়েট করবেন ২০০০ টাকা পাবার জন্য। ২০০০ টাকার আবেদনে আপনি পাবেন ১৬০০ টাকা। সুদ এবং চার্জ দিবেন ৪০০ টাকা।
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sHnRgxIKV7o
রেপিডের নামে সর্বোচ্চ প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা বাড়াচ্ছেন অনেকেই, বুঝে কিংবা না বুঝে। আপনি যদি ভিডিওটি দেখেন , কথা গুলো ক্লিয়ার শুনে বুঝতে পারবেন কিভাবে রেপিড ক্যাশ আপনার পার্সোনাল ইনফরমেশন নিয়ে আপনাকে ফাঁদে ফেলতে পারে। আপনি চাইলেও তাদের সার্ভার থেকে আপনার ইনফরমেশন ডিলিট করতে পারবেন না। ২০% সুদে পাবেন ২০০০ টাকা ৭ দিনে রিটার্ন। এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা দিয়েছেন তো মরেছেন। ব্যাঙ্ক গুলো যেখানে ৪৮ ঘন্টায় লক্ষ্য লক্ষ্য টাকা লোন দিচ্ছে ৮-৯% সুদে, সেখানে অনলাইন প্লাটফর্ম রেপিড ক্যাশ রেপিডের নামে হাতিয়ে নিচ্ছে জনগণের টাকা। জনগণ যদি সজাগ থাকেন , এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদ থেকে বাঁচতে পারেন। কাস্টমার কেয়ার থেকে সার্ভিসের নামে যা পাবেন সে বিষয়ে আর না যাই । আপনার রিকোয়েস্ট তাদের কাছে মূল্যহীন। অনলাইন সেবাগুলো এমন কেন ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Identify Fake News In Facebook</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-23-how-to-identify-fake-news-in-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-23-how-to-identify-fake-news-in-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Now-a-days, many people is publishing fake news in Facebook. Some people use facebook to make fake news posting to create sudden problem in countywide. There are many ways you can identify that news is fake / true.
How to make sure facebook news post quality:
Check any link added to the post written or not. Go to the link (you need internet active connection to browse link) Check the news source If you know the source is reputed newspaper or any government notice from registered government website always have *.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#boycottindianonion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-19-boycottindianonion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-19-boycottindianonion/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is now fullfil to grow onion countrywide and original deshi onion price is now 30 to 40 tk countrywide.
Indian onion market price is 10 taka higher than deshi quality right now. That&amp;rsquo;s why Bangladesh onion importer stopped to import onion from India last 10 days.
Even there is 10 taka less prices onion in available in market price around 15 - 20 taka</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh High court ordered to ban 25 family members of P.K Haldar to leave country</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country/</guid>
      <description>Thousands kr money misappropriation claimed fugitive P.K Haldar family total 25 members banned to leave country, Bangladesh High court ordered today 5th January 2021.
Businessman P.K Haldars mother, relatives including his few company employees total 25 members can&amp;rsquo;t leave Bangladesh High court ordered today.
Proshanto Kumar Haldar or, P.K Haldar was flying Bangladesh last year after occurance of bank money misappropriation, he was the Executive Director of that Bank. He was connected with several non-government organization and other businessman also connected with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is khulnaflix</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-05-what-is-khulnaflix-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-05-what-is-khulnaflix-net/</guid>
      <description>khulnaflix.net is a local FTP server operated by Cogent broadband internet service provider. khulnaflix server total space 400 TB. Processor capacity high-end server PC, Ram 40 GB, and upgrading day by day.
khulnaflix local address: http://khulnaflix.net
khulnaflix local file address: http://file.khulnaflix.net
Khulnaflix streaming: http://php.khulnaflix.net/
Khulnaflix live TV: http://tv.khulnaflix.net/
Khulnaflix android application: Click here to download khulnaflix app</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire explosion in Narayanganj Dhaka</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-%E0%A6%A8%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B0%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%BC%E0%A6%A3%E0%A6%97%E0%A6%9E%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%9C%E0%A7%87-%E0%A6%86%E0%A6%97%E0%A7%81%E0%A6%A8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-%E0%A6%A8%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B0%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%BC%E0%A6%A3%E0%A6%97%E0%A6%9E%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%9C%E0%A7%87-%E0%A6%86%E0%A6%97%E0%A7%81%E0%A6%A8/</guid>
      <description>A fire broke out at Konka Fridge factory in Sonargaon, Naranganj, injuring more than a dozen people and causing a lot of damage. The fire broke out at Mograpara in Sonargaon upazila around 11am on Sunday. Local fire service personnel have been able to bring the fire under control. Arefin Siddique, deputy assistant director of the fire service, told BDMeter that six units of the fire service are working to extinguish the fire after receiving the news of the fire at the Konka battery factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renouned novelist Rabeya khatun has died</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-renouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-03-renouned-novelist-rabeya-khatun-has-died/</guid>
      <description>Bngladesh renouned novelist Rabeya Khatun has died in 3rd January, 2021
President Abdul Hamid and Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina have expressed grief over the death of Rabeya Khatun
In a condolence message, the President said, “The death of Rabia Khatun is an irreparable loss for the literary arena of the country. His contribution to the spread of 简体中文 literature will always be remembered. ”
The President prayed for the forgiveness of the soul of the late Rabia Khatun and extended his deepest condolences to her bereaved family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing one more point extension of leave: BD News</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-18-one-more-point-extnsion-of-leave/</guid>
      <description>The country has announced to extend the holiday once again till January 16. According to the Ministry of Education on Friday, all educational institutions, schools, colleges, universities and national universities will remain closed till January 16. Until December 17, all educational institutions in the country were closed except Qawmi Madrasa.
To curb the spread of corona virus in Bangladesh, all educational institutions were closed from March 17 and all educational institutions were closed till December 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say NO to corruption: Bangladesh Telecommunication Act</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</guid>
      <description>Penalties for sending obscene messages on the Internet 36 Substitution of section
69 of Act No. 18 of 2001: Section 69 shall be substituted for the following section 69 of the said Act, namely: -
Penalties for sending obscene, obscene, etc. messages - if - (A). A person proposes to a person engaged in the operation of such equipment for the purpose of sending any obscene, threatening or seriously offensive message with the help of telecommunication equipment or wireless equipment, or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 ‘robbers’ lynched in Narsindi</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-2-robbers-lynched-in-narsindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-2-robbers-lynched-in-narsindi/</guid>
      <description>Two suspected robbers were killed in a mob lynching at murgib village in Narsingdi’s shibpur upazila early Wednesday.
One of the deceased was identified as sohel 30 son of Aminul Islam. Resident of kulirchan of kishoreganj district.
A gang of 10/15 robbers entered the village around 3am and stormed into the three houses said Abdul kalam officer incharge of investigation of shibpur police station.
A group of villagers sensing the presence of robbers they informed other villagers over the phone , reports jagonews later , a group of local people went to a mosque and announced the attack of the robber gang using a loudspeaker following the announcement , locals came out of their houses and besieged the three members of the robber gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 domestic workers killed , tortured in 9months : speakers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-28-domestic-workers-killed-tortured-in-9months-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-28-domestic-workers-killed-tortured-in-9months-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Speaker at a seminar said 28 domestic workers were killed and tortured including 10 mysterious death.
In the first nine months of this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five jailed for life in Brahmanbaria murder case</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-five-jailed-for-life-in-brahmanbaria-murder-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-five-jailed-for-life-in-brahmanbaria-murder-case/</guid>
      <description>A brahmanbaria count on Wednesday sentenced five people to life imprisonment for murdering a man in sarail upazila siz years back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two more policemen suspended over Raihans death on custody</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-more-policemen-suspended-over-raihans-death-on-custody/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-more-policemen-suspended-over-raihans-death-on-custody/</guid>
      <description>Two more policemen including the investigation officer of Raihan ls murdercase were suspended o. Wednesday on charges of helping sub inspector Akbar Hossain Bhuiyan, the prime accused to free . The suspended officials are kotwali police station inspector Soumen Maitra investigation officer of the case and sub inspector Abdul Baten. Sylhet metropolitan police additional deputy commissioner BM Ashrafullah Taher confirmed this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The management is annex beside domineering in spurn obligatory masks</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-the-management-is-annex-beside-domineering-in-spurn-obligatory-masks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-the-management-is-annex-beside-domineering-in-spurn-obligatory-masks/</guid>
      <description>The supervision is pleasing moan far exotic harsh drawing need far stranger to in consequence whereof vital masks to buffer the countrymen Wean away outlander the uphold pending flaunt of Kovid-19. For this, the adjustable courts effort been instructed to be call far from absolute.
Directors Woman Khandaker Anwarul Islam forced the remarks in a indoctrinate corroboration the used provisions appointment. The undertaking was dominate at a customary house choice chaired by Shrewd Representative Sheikh Hasina on Monday morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
