<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>research on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in research on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Determination of Moist Air Properties</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/03/determination-of-moist-air-properties/</guid>
      <description>An air-water mixture is found from the heat and mass balance to be at 60°C (333 K) and 0.025 kg/kg (25 g/kg) absolute humidity. Calculate the other main parameters for the mixture. Take atmospheric pressure as 101,325 Pa.
Method: Consult item (vi) in Table 12-5 for the calculation methodology.
From the initial terminology section, specific humidity YW = 0.02439 kg/kg, mole ratio z = 0.0402 kmol/kmol, mole fraction y = 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greenhouse Gases and Renewable Energy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</guid>
      <description>Effect greenhouse What are greenhouse gases (GHG)? Greenhouse gases (GHGs) trap heat within the earth’s atmosphere, contributing to the ‘greenhouse’ effect and causing global warming. These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide, and water vapor. Industry, including manufacturing, is the second largest global emitter of human-created GHGs. Much of industrial GHG emissions are due to the burning of fossil fuels for heat and power generation.
Why should I care about GHGs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different types of Steel Grades</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</guid>
      <description>Structural steel grades are referred to by their corresponding ASTM designation. For example, the most commonly used grade of structural steel is A36, which is produced to meet the requirements of the ASTM A36 specification. This grade offers a good mix of strength, weldability, and cost. In many designs, this specification alone will satisfy designers’ needs. Other specifications, such as A53 for pipe, provide an equivalent grade of steel for that type of product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Design Your Building Against Earthquake</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/06/how-to-design-your-building-against-earthquake/</guid>
      <description>Buildings should be designed to withstand minor earthquakes without damage, because they may occur almost everywhere. For major earthquakes, it may not be economical to prevent all damage but collapse should be precluded. Because an earthquake and a high wind are not likely to occur simultaneously, building codes usually do not require that buildings be designed for a combination of large seismic and wind loads. Thus, designers may assume that the full strength of wind bracing is also available to resist drift caused by earthquakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about different types of industrial trucks &amp; vehicles</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Industrial vehicles/trucks are one of the most common groups of materials handling equipment used in industry as well as in the day-to-day distribution of goods in warehouses, large stores, transport depots, etc. The basic operation and construction features of some of the common types of industrial trucks will be discussed here. The adjective ‘‘industrial’’ used before this group of vehicles/trucks is to distinguish these from other groups of vehicles like buses, lorries, trucks, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Environmental Biotechnology</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</guid>
      <description>When modern industrialization started in the 19th century, many people migrated from the agricultural area to the big cities. Public hygiene became a major problem. Human excrement and waste was discharged into open channels, rivers, and lakes. The pollution was disastrous and hygiene-related epidemic diseases, like cholera and typhus, occurred frequently. Therefore, it was an important step forward when public water collection systems and treatment plants were introduced at the end of the 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Basic Electrical Components</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-basic-electrical-components/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-basic-electrical-components/</guid>
      <description>This blog will help to refresh and expand your understanding of basic electrical components and the basic terms used in electricity as required for instrumentation.
This chapter discusses
■ Basic passive components (resistors, capacitors, and inductors) used in electrical circuits
■ Applications of Ohm’s law and Kirchoff’s laws
■ Use of resistors as voltage dividers
■ Effective equivalent circuits for basic devices connected in series and parallel
■ The Wheatstone bridge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Sprinkler System Installation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Automatic fire sprinkler systems have been protecting property in the United States since the late 1800s; in fact, the Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems, 1896 was the first standard developed by the National Fire Protection Association (NFPA). Today the NFPA still develops the most widely accepted standards for the design and installation of sprinkler systems: NFPA 13, Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems; 20, Installation of Centrifugal Fire Pumps; 24, Installation of Private Fire Services Mains and Their Appurtenances; 231, General Storage and 231C, Rack Storage of Materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics and Classifications Of Industrial Materials</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/characteristics-and-classifications-of-industrial-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/01/characteristics-and-classifications-of-industrial-materials/</guid>
      <description>Materials handling system Method to be adopted and choice of equipment for a materials handling system primarily depends on the type of material/s to be handled. It is, therefore, very important to know about different types of materials and their characteristics which are related to methods and equipment used for their handling.
As innumerable different materials are used and need to be handled in industries, they are classified based on specific characteristics relevant to their handling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification &amp; Risk Assessment</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-28-industrial-hazard-identification-risk-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-28-industrial-hazard-identification-risk-assessment/</guid>
      <description>What Industrial Supplier Compliance Manual said? Hazard identification and risk assessment (HIRA) should be
performed for all activities conducted at the facility, and include off-site activities are related to the Supplier’s business. HIRA should be contradicted at least once (1) per year EHS risk assessment should include Why we need Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment at Workplace Level? As part of the key aspects of Risk Management, it aims to:- Reduce the likelihood and consequence of a workplace incident that may result in injury or disease Free from significant risks in the factory workplace Control risks and prevent workplace injuries The Risk Pyramid</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is COP26 And Why Its Matter</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</guid>
      <description>UK hosts a summit amongst United Nations countries to talk about global climate changes, how to tackle this situation and what necessary steps should take in immediate action is called COP26.
It was a plan to host in Glasgow, in a city of Scotland in November 2020 last year and attend more than 200 world countries leader, but due to Coronavirus Pandemic, the COP26 program delayed more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Design And Construction - Principals Of Architecture</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-16-building-design-and-construction-principals-of-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-16-building-design-and-construction-principals-of-architecture/</guid>
      <description>Sociological changes, new technology in industry and commerce, new building codes, other new laws and regulations, inflationary economies of nations, and advances in building technology place an ever-increasing burden on building designers and constructors. They need more and more knowledge and skill to cope with the demands placed on them.
The public continually demands more complex buildings than in the past. They must serve more purposes, last longer, and require less maintenance and repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dyeing of polyester and cotton blended fabrics</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-27-dyeing-of-polyester-and-cotton-blend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-27-dyeing-of-polyester-and-cotton-blend/</guid>
      <description>Classification of the methods for dyeing of P/C blend Exhaust dyeing method or batch dyeing method This is again classiﬁed in the following three groups-
Two bath dyeing One bath one step dyeing One bath two-step dyeing method Thermosol Dyeing method It is again classiﬁed into two groups-
Continuous dyeing- Pad batch process (semi-continuous)
Note-In continuous dyeing process may be single bath or double bath. EXHAUST DYEING Two bath dyeing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking news: 8 infant deaths from 2015 to 2020 due to Boppy newborn loungers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-23-heartbreaking-news-8-infant-deaths-from-2015-to-2020-due-to-boppy-newborn-loungers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-23-heartbreaking-news-8-infant-deaths-from-2015-to-2020-due-to-boppy-newborn-loungers/</guid>
      <description>US staff reporter:
Boppy newborn loungers are sold to approximately 3.3 million which is recalled after the death of 8 infants. Boppy newborn loungers are sold nationwide in over 3.3 million pieces including top retailers Walmart, Target, Amazon, and Pottery barn kids.
The US consumer product safety commission (CPSC) and the Boppy company recalled 3.3 million loungers after the death of 8 infants reported from December 2015 to June 2020. This is reported that the infant deaths are being connected with Boppy loungers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT GUIDELINES</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-17-performance-management-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-17-performance-management-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Goal Setting &amp;amp; Cascading **Purpose
**Goal setting is a powerful tool that is used to align the team and individual goals to
Operating Group objectives and strategies. This strategy keeps all levels of the
organization on the same page. It not only helps improve the attainment of the 3- Year
Plan strategy but also encourages on-going communication between employees and
their managers. As well, each individual can see how their job makes a difference in the</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance and Sustainability: Conflict Minerals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</guid>
      <description>Learn About Conflict Minerals US guidelines for vendor compliance and sustainability
Index:
What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals in Products US Conflict Minerals Laws Auditing and Reporting Requirements Customer’s expectations Continuous Tracking Tracing workflow Reporting – CFSI Beyond USA What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals refer to raw materials that come from a particular part of the world where conflict is occurring and trading of those materials, perpetuates the fighting. Conflict minerals are mined in conditions of armed conflict and human rights abuses, notably in the Democratic Republic of Congo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get rid from unwanted skin hair</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-09-how-to-get-rid-from-unwanted-skin-hair/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-09-how-to-get-rid-from-unwanted-skin-hair/</guid>
      <description>Unwanted hair? You can be released unwanted skin hair in a domestic way. You can be removed in a domestic way When hair grows on a part of the body that is not supposed to have, we call it unwanted hair. Especially on the face or under the nose in the mustache line. These cause loss of beauty. Many people admit to expensive treatments and permanent hair removal to remove these unwanted hairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical laboratory test market size analysis &amp; research</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-08-clinical-laboratory-test-market-size-analysis-and-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-08-clinical-laboratory-test-market-size-analysis-and-research/</guid>
      <description>Clinical Laboratory Test Market Size Shares and Trend Analysis Report Report Overview of The global clinical trial market size in 2019 was in USA 16.6 billion. The CBC, HBB / HCT, BMP, BN Creatinine, Electrolyte Test, HBA1C, CMP, Liver Panel, Renal Panel, Lipid Panel gives around 16 million business of clinical lab up to 2025.
Clinical laboratory testing is needed to diagnose of the diseases such as cardiovascular disorders, tuberculosis and diabetes, which are driven by increasing of investment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
