<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>green-building on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/green-building/</link>
    <description>Recent content in green-building on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/green-building/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</guid>
      <description>for New Construction, Major Renovation, and Commercial Interiors Introduction Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation Suggestions present a menu of options that can be adopted or implemented to integrate sustainable design, equipment, materials and other elements into new buildings and major renovations. The Suggestions include elements scored by the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design (LEED) standard, as well as the best practices Bdmeter has implemented in our global network.
Suppliers worldwide are encouraged to adopt as many of the items in these Suggestions whenever feasible and applicable to your location and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Sustainable Building or Green Building</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/learn-about-sustainable-building-or-green-building/</guid>
      <description>What is a sustainable building? For your building to be sustainable, many factors need to be considered. These include air quality, energy
efficiency, and the use of ‘green’ materials among others. This document focuses on 1) building a sustainable building 2) retrofitting and 3) certification.
Why should I make my buildings sustainable? Apart from the environmental benefits, a sustainable building can reduce your operational costs by as much as 30-50% on your energy usage and 40-50% on your water usage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
