<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sports on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sports on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Australian beat New Zealand in World Cup T20 Final 2021 in Dubai</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-australia-won-world-t20-final-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-14-australia-won-world-t20-final-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Australia beat New Zealand in the seventh edition of T20 to become the champions. Australia won the toss and invited New Zealand to bat. At the end of the allotted 20 overs, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s total stood at 162, with New Zealand captain Kem Williams scoring 65 and Hazelwood taking three wickets for 16 runs in 4 overs for Australia.
Australia chased down 172 runs to beat New Zealand, with Mitchell Marsh top-scoring with 7 for Australia, the first time Australia had won the World Twenty20 with seven balls to spare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOOTBALL LEGEND DIEGO MARADONA IS NO MORE</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-football-legend-diego-maradona-is-no-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-football-legend-diego-maradona-is-no-more/</guid>
      <description>Reports in Argentina said football legend Diego Maradona had a cardiac arrest yesterday.
Argentine newspapers claim the World Cup winner suffered a cardiorespiratory arrest on Wednesday morning local time in the town of Tigre.
Later, news agency AFP was among a host of outlets to tweet that the legend had died.
Maradona, who won Argentina&amp;rsquo;s second World Cup in 1986 almost single-handedly, recently had a surgery to remove a blood clot from his brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legend Never Dies</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-legend-never-dies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-legend-never-dies/</guid>
      <description>“I worked hard all my life for this. Those who say I don&amp;rsquo;t deserve anything, that it all came easy, can kiss my arse.” - Diego Maradona
Maradona, world famous legendary, great Footballer, as popular in world as he is in Argentina. Diego Armando Maradona was an Argentine professional football player and manager. He is born in October 30, 1960 Lanús is the capital of Lanús Partido, Buenos Aires Province in Argentina, and Died in November 25, 2020 (aged 60).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>County at Vikings Week 11, 2020 Games Live Discussion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-22-county-at-vikings-week-11-2020-games-live-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-22-county-at-vikings-week-11-2020-games-live-discussion/</guid>
      <description>The Cowboys treat the Vikings to the bone
all sharing options.
Minnesota Vikings vs. Dallas Cowboys.
The week is over. The Cowboys won again against the Minnesota Vikings. Dallas is more likely to try to get a win by playing better football over the past few games.
https://youtu.be/Fqqyl1KzaIk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Football stars&#39; spouses conflict in &#39;WAGatha Christie&#39; legal dispute in London</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-football-stars-spouses-conflict-in-wagatha-christie-legal-dispute-in-london/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-football-stars-spouses-conflict-in-wagatha-christie-legal-dispute-in-london/</guid>
      <description>Football - World Cup - Quarter Final - Sweden versus England - Samara Arena, Samara, Russia - July 7, 2018 Wife of England&amp;rsquo;s Jamie Vardy, Rebekah Vardy, in the remain after the match. Reuters
Football - World Cup - Quarter Final - Sweden versus England - Samara Arena, Samara, Russia - July 7, 2018 Wife of England&amp;rsquo;s Jamie Vardy, Rebekah Vardy, in the remain after the match. Reuters
A court fight between the spouses of previous England football stars Wayne Rooney and Jamie Vardy commenced in London on Thursday, a heightening in a story of selling out and beginner criminologist work that has tantalized the British public.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
