<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sustainable on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/sustainable/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sustainable on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/sustainable/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sustainable-design-building-and-renovation/</guid>
      <description>for New Construction, Major Renovation, and Commercial Interiors Introduction Sustainable Design, Building, and Renovation Suggestions present a menu of options that can be adopted or implemented to integrate sustainable design, equipment, materials and other elements into new buildings and major renovations. The Suggestions include elements scored by the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design (LEED) standard, as well as the best practices Bdmeter has implemented in our global network.
Suppliers worldwide are encouraged to adopt as many of the items in these Suggestions whenever feasible and applicable to your location and operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Resources Management</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-20-corporate-resources-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-20-corporate-resources-management/</guid>
      <description>Energy Efficiency Reducing your energy consumption is a great way to reduce both costs and greenhouse gas emissions. Lowering your utility costs and reducing your environmental impact also helps your factory prepare for new policies and regulatory requirements, improve your competitive advantage and grow your business efficiently.
Conducting an energy audit of your facilities is the best way to start. It will help you assess your energy usage and identify what you can do to lower energy consumption, including changes to behavior, equipment, and processes, and how much can be potentially saved.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
