<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>world on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/world/</link>
    <description>Recent content in world on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Different types of Steel Grades</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</guid>
      <description>Structural steel grades are referred to by their corresponding ASTM designation. For example, the most commonly used grade of structural steel is A36, which is produced to meet the requirements of the ASTM A36 specification. This grade offers a good mix of strength, weldability, and cost. In many designs, this specification alone will satisfy designers’ needs. Other specifications, such as A53 for pipe, provide an equivalent grade of steel for that type of product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to earn 15000 USD in a month</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-16-earn-money-online-ringid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-16-earn-money-online-ringid/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that ring ID is very easy to earn a lot of money? Nowadays many people are sitting at home very easily by opening Ring ID account and earning a minimum of 15000 rupees per month. You can invest in Ring ID without any tension. You should see 50-100 ads per month. An ad is 20-30 seconds max. 100 ad will be seen in less than 1 hour. Guaranteed income of 15000 rupees with less than 1 hour daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manual process to slaughter cows to get fresh meat</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-20-how-to-do-kurbani-in-halal-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-20-how-to-do-kurbani-in-halal-way/</guid>
      <description>ইসলামী আইনে গরু/ চতুষ্পদ জন্তু হালাল উপায়ে জবাই করা অত্যাবশ্যক। গরু হালাল জবাই মুসলিমদের জন্য গ্রহণযোগ্য একমাত্র পদ্ধতি। হালাল জবাইয়ের সংক্ষিপ্ত বিবরণ:
১. কুরবানীর জন্য জবাই করতে হবে এমন চতুষ্পদ জন্তু যা মুসলমানদের খাওয়ার জন্য অনুমতিপ্রাপ্ত।
২. জবাইয়ের সময় অবশ্যই জীবিত থাকতে হবে।
হালাল উপায়ে পশু কোরবানি পদ্ধতি
৩. ধারালো ছুরি ব্যবহার করে জবাই করতে হবে। এমন ছুরি ব্যাবহার করা যাবেনা যার ওজন বেশি এবং ওজনের ভারেই জবাই হয়ে যেতে পারে। যদি ছুটির ওজনের প্রভাবে জবাই করা হয়, তবে সেই মাংস খাওয়া যাবেনা ।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance and Sustainability: Conflict Minerals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</guid>
      <description>Learn About Conflict Minerals US guidelines for vendor compliance and sustainability
Index:
What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals in Products US Conflict Minerals Laws Auditing and Reporting Requirements Customer’s expectations Continuous Tracking Tracing workflow Reporting – CFSI Beyond USA What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals refer to raw materials that come from a particular part of the world where conflict is occurring and trading of those materials, perpetuates the fighting. Conflict minerals are mined in conditions of armed conflict and human rights abuses, notably in the Democratic Republic of Congo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivational Quote</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-26-motivational-quote/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-26-motivational-quote/</guid>
      <description>Inside every person, there are two bears. One bear is all things good, compassion, love, trust.. The other is all things evil, fear, shame and self destruction. Which one win? The answer is the one you feed.
Motivational Quote by bdmeter.info</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sello oil in Altoona PA on 12 Feb 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-12-sello-oil-in-altoona/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-12-sello-oil-in-altoona/</guid>
      <description>Sello Oil price update on 12 Feb 2021 What is sello oil? Sello oil (Sel-Lo Oil) is a fuel supplier and distributor in Altoona, PA, United States of America. They deliver different kinds of fuel like Ultra-low-sulfur diesel oil (Dyed ULSD), blended fuel, kerosene fuel, and heating oil. Sello Oil company established in 1988 has been operated by a family in central Pennsylvania. Sello oil company is one of the largest heating oil distributors in central Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungary Denied Bangladeshi Gifts Of 10000 Corona Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-05-al-jazeera-tv-news-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-05-al-jazeera-tv-news-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Recently Hungary denied to receive a gift of Five Thousand Oxford-Astrogeneca Corona Vaccine from Bangladesh. Hungary Foreign Affairs ministry confirmed that welcome-like gift from Bangladesh rejected by Hungary Government. Hungary Foreign Affairs ministry said, Bangladesh offers 5000 Oxford Astrogeneca Corona vaccine as a welcoming gift, but Hungary don&amp;rsquo;t want this gift. Recent Al-Jazeera tv news of Bangladesh top level crime makes huge discussion about Bangladesh Government globally. Bangladesh Government said this Al-Jazeera TV news report is totally irrelevant with situation and we don&amp;rsquo;t agree with Al-Jazeera TV news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Hills probation: Donald Trump</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>US president Donald Trump urges Capital Hill issue to stop violences. Trump said &amp;quot; We want no violence&amp;quot;.
Trump visited Maxico boarder and provide susch statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corona vaccination: No expectations to stop Corona in 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-corona-vaccination-no-expectations-to-stop-corona-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>WHO said &amp;ldquo;There is no hope to stop Corona virus in 2021. Vaccine program ongoing but human need to aware to maintain all preventive actions to stop spread.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump : A True Hero in United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-donald-trump-a-true-hero-in-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-donald-trump-a-true-hero-in-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump news today is the, He is the only President in American history that has been accused twice for insurrection incitement.
Donald Trump news: He incited during recent past week&amp;rsquo;s capital riots and accused for this issue twice. This is the first time ever in US History. Regarding BBC Donald Trump news, this is not the first time, Donald trump is doing this and unstoppable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need a strong global climate alliance to save our planet: Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina has said that a strong global climate alliance is urgently needed to save future generations and the planet from the adverse effects of climate change by reducing carbon emissions.
She said he would like to emphasize the importance of a positive and strong international climate alliance to move towards achieving carbon balance by effectively reducing global carbon emissions before the middle of the century.
This was stated by the Prime Minister in a pre-recorded speech at a virtual conference titled &amp;lsquo;Thimphu Ambition Summit&amp;rsquo; aimed at accelerating the pace of globalization by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Zealand chief honcho Ardern offers annoy power to Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-progressive-zealand-chief-honcho-ardern-offers-annoy-power-to-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-23-progressive-zealand-chief-honcho-ardern-offers-annoy-power-to-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>Ardern voiced the stain of the 20-minute phone application call was good-natured and go wool-gathering Biden spoke totally favorably helter-skelter nevertheless Avant-garde Zealand was escort the universal. &amp;ldquo;What has been unreservedly at the center of our confession has been divers part respecting respect to exploration, communication dogging, isolation,&amp;rdquo; Ardern voiced. &amp;ldquo;go off at a tangent&amp;rsquo;s go away outlander and insusceptible to what we&amp;rsquo;ve concluded at our dynamism.&amp;rdquo; Experimental Zealand has been abundantly prominent in excision the make tracks chip a dogmatic lockdown in Evidence and conclusion its animation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something chronicled: Push for different Biden Cabinet</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-something-chronicled-push-for-different-biden-cabinet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-something-chronicled-push-for-different-biden-cabinet/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (BDM) — Native Americans are encouraging President-elect Joe Biden to impact the world forever by choosing one of their own to lead the amazing office that manages the country&amp;rsquo;s clans, setting up one of a few approaching trial of Biden&amp;rsquo;s promise to have a Cabinet illustrative of Americans.
O.J. Semans is one of many ancestral authorities and casting a ballot activists around the nation pushing choice of Rep. Deb Haaland, a New Mexico Democrat and individual from the Pueblo of Laguna, to turn into the main Native American secretary of inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India quick to work with Bangladesh on guard equipment stages</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-india-quick-to-work-with-bangladesh-on-guard-equipment-stages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-india-quick-to-work-with-bangladesh-on-guard-equipment-stages/</guid>
      <description>India has said it is quick to work with Bangladesh on safeguard equipment stages like Akash rocket, radars, mortars, cannons weapons and ammo and welcomed ventures from its eastern neighbor in two key Indian protection modern hallways.
India likewise said that its shipyards are happy to band together with Bangladeshi shipyards for development of stages according to Bangladesh prerequisites through joint endeavors, co-improvement and cooperation for both business and safeguard necessities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces likely difficulty in Georgia relate, drops Michigan claim</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-trump-faces-likely-difficulty-in-georgia-relate-drops-michigan-claim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-trump-faces-likely-difficulty-in-georgia-relate-drops-michigan-claim/</guid>
      <description>Workers of the Fulton County Board of Registration and Elections measure polling forms in Atlanta, Georgia US, November 4, 2020. Reuters
Representatives of the Fulton County Board of Registration and Elections measure voting forms in Atlanta, Georgia US, November 4, 2020. Reuters
The US official political race milestone province of Georgia was required on Thursday to insist Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s triumph over Donald Trump after a meticulous relate, as Trump&amp;rsquo;s re-appointment crusade said it was pulling out a claim in Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldwide economy recuperating, yet might be losing energy: IMF boss</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-worldwide-economy-recuperating-yet-might-be-losing-energy-imf-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-worldwide-economy-recuperating-yet-might-be-losing-energy-imf-boss/</guid>
      <description>Global Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva. Reuters
Global Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva. Reuters
The worldwide economy is recuperating from the profundities of the Covid emergency, however there are indications of easing back force in nations with resurging contamination rates, the International Monetary Fund said in another report for G20 significant economies.
The report, delivered in front of the current week&amp;rsquo;s virtual gatherings of account authorities and pioneers from the Group of 20 nations, underscored the lopsided idea of the worldwide recuperation and cautioned the emergency would probably leave profound, inconsistent scars.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
