<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hazard on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/hazard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hazard on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/hazard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Auto Sprinkler System Installation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/auto-sprinkler-system-installation-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Automatic fire sprinkler systems have been protecting property in the United States since the late 1800s; in fact, the Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems, 1896 was the first standard developed by the National Fire Protection Association (NFPA). Today the NFPA still develops the most widely accepted standards for the design and installation of sprinkler systems: NFPA 13, Standard for the Installation of Sprinkler Systems; 20, Installation of Centrifugal Fire Pumps; 24, Installation of Private Fire Services Mains and Their Appurtenances; 231, General Storage and 231C, Rack Storage of Materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment Process</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/02/industrial-hazard-identification-and-risk-assessment-process/</guid>
      <description>Today we will learn about vendor compliance and sustainability terms to identify hazards and assess risks.
Agenda:
Terms &amp;amp; Definitions HIRA Process Hazard Identification Risk Matrix &amp;amp; Risk Assessment Operational Controls Good Documentation Practices &amp;amp; Recommendations Company Sustainability Development Example HIRA &amp;amp; Discussion Factory Assignment : Risk Never Sleeps! The Cost of Safety The Importance of Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment HIRA is the Basis (First Step) to SafeGuard Employees, Contractors, Visitors, Contract workers, People who share the workplace from Significant Injuries or ill Health in a Systematic Approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Hazard Identification &amp; Risk Assessment</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-28-industrial-hazard-identification-risk-assessment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-28-industrial-hazard-identification-risk-assessment/</guid>
      <description>What Industrial Supplier Compliance Manual said? Hazard identification and risk assessment (HIRA) should be
performed for all activities conducted at the facility, and include off-site activities are related to the Supplier’s business. HIRA should be contradicted at least once (1) per year EHS risk assessment should include Why we need Hazard Identification and Risk Assessment at Workplace Level? As part of the key aspects of Risk Management, it aims to:- Reduce the likelihood and consequence of a workplace incident that may result in injury or disease Free from significant risks in the factory workplace Control risks and prevent workplace injuries The Risk Pyramid</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
