<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>internet on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in internet on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX internet user total 10000</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-06-spacex-internet-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-06-spacex-internet-service/</guid>
      <description>Starlink SpaceX internet have started it&amp;rsquo;s beta testing Internet service from last year. First accessibility to SpaceX internet to 3 selected countries citizen from USA, Canada, and UK. Recent statistics report is that SpaceX have total 10000 intertnet user now. US news channel CNBC stated that Starlink demands to introduce them as the ideal telecommunication company worldwide. Rubal digital opportunity fund gave millons dollar funding to Satrlink. Regarding this funding, Starlink is trying to expand their satellite internet technology in some other countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bd telecommunication acts: Say no to crime</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</guid>
      <description>ইন্টারনেটে অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড বিধি 简体中文দেশ গেজেট , অতিরিক্ত , আগস্ট ১ , ২০১০ (৭৮৮২)
৩৮। ২০০১ সনের ১৮ নং আইনের ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপন: উক্ত আইনের ধারা ৬৯ এর পরিবর্তে নিম্নরূপ ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপিত হইবে , যথা :-
“ ৬৯। অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড — যদি —
( ক ) . কোন ব্যক্তি টেলিযােগাযােগ যন্ত্রপাতি বা বেতার যন্ত্রপাতির সাহায্যে কোন অশ্লীল , ভীতি প্রদর্শনমূলক বা গুরুতরভাবে অপমানকর কোন বার্তা প্রেরণের উদ্দেশ্যে উক্ত যন্ত্রপাতির পরিচালন কাজে নিয়ােজিত ব্যক্তির নিকট প্রস্তাব করেন , বা</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say NO to corruption: Bangladesh Telecommunication Act</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</guid>
      <description>Penalties for sending obscene messages on the Internet 36 Substitution of section
69 of Act No. 18 of 2001: Section 69 shall be substituted for the following section 69 of the said Act, namely: -
Penalties for sending obscene, obscene, etc. messages - if - (A). A person proposes to a person engaged in the operation of such equipment for the purpose of sending any obscene, threatening or seriously offensive message with the help of telecommunication equipment or wireless equipment, or</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
