<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>united-states on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/united-states/</link>
    <description>Recent content in united-states on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/united-states/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sel-Lo Oil Price update on 13 Jan 2023</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sel-lo-oil-price-update-on-13-jan-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2023/01/sel-lo-oil-price-update-on-13-jan-2023/</guid>
      <description>Sel-Lo Oil latest price update on 13 Jan 2023 | Prices last changed on 1/13/23 | Heating Oil
$ | Blend
$ | Kerosene
$ | Dyed ULSD (Off-Road)
$ 100 Gallon Minimum 3.99 4.79 5.59 4.09 Over 200 Gallons 3.95 4.75 5.55 4.09 Over 400 Gallons 3.93 4.73 5.53 4.05 Over 800 Gallons 3.91 4.71 5.51 4.05 Over 1200 Gallons 3.87 4.67 5.47 4.01 Table: Sel-Lo oil price
Get Sel-Lo Oil Price trend from 2016 to 2023 If you have problem to see preview of above Sel-Lo oil price chart, please click on link: Click to see Sel-Lo oil price change trend chart</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get a paper manufacturers list to order bulk paper rolls</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-15-a-list-of-paper-mills-in-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-15-a-list-of-paper-mills-in-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>The United States is one of the biggest marketplaces of different kinds of papers. Most US people need papers for their kids during the learning stage and you know how papers are intertwining with human daily needs. States people buy readymade art paper, rolled paper, drawing paper, regular typing paper, handwritten paper, books paper, magazine paper, and different GSM papers for daily needs.
One of my customers from California once asked for papers same as the below job:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York City Come Back Strong in 2021!</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-city-come-back-strong-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-new-york-city-come-back-strong-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>We need a recovery that brings back the life of the heart the energy of the city. This is New York City. Everyone is calling to part of the enjoyment of New York City. Everyone gonna does that to join the Open culture of the city on New York city roads. Coronavirus makes New York city stop more than a year. During this pandemic period, New York was facing a great loss of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Hills probation: Donald Trump</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>US president Donald Trump urges Capital Hill issue to stop violences. Trump said &amp;quot; We want no violence&amp;quot;.
Trump visited Maxico boarder and provide susch statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in America: Next steps 75 plus and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-america-covid-19-vaccine-era/</guid>
      <description>A federal advisory panel on Sunday recommended the next phase of the COVID-19 vaccine for seniors age 75 and older and essential workers such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers.
According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given the primary shot through the vaccination program that began last week.
A COVID-19 vaccine made by Pfizer Inc. and Germany&amp;rsquo;s BioEntech is already being distributed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 vaccine in the United States: The next step is 75 senior and emergency service workers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-21-unitrd-states-covid-19-vaccine/</guid>
      <description>The Bieber Federal Advisory Panel has recommended 75-year-olds and older workers, such as firefighters, teachers and grocery store workers, to take the next step in the CVID-19 vaccine.
According to the Department of Disease Control and Prevention, about 556,000 Americans have been given initial shots through the vaccination program that began last week.
Pfizer Inc. And the COVID-19 vaccine, developed by Bionetech in Germany, is already being distributed. Moderna Inc. Its vaccine was approved last week and distributed last Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Govt can&#39;t put youngsters in danger  - Joe Biden said</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-govt-cant-put-youngsters-in-danger-pm-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-govt-cant-put-youngsters-in-danger-pm-said/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden yesterday recognized that remaining at home had been progressively hard for understudies, however, the public authority would not put youngsters&amp;rsquo; lives in danger by returning the instructive organizations.
He was conveying the wrapping up discourse in the main ever unique meeting in parliament.
Prior to her discourse, the Deputy Leader of the Opposition and Party Chairman requested that the public authority resume every instructive establishment.
The President answered that the USA, diverse European nations, and the UK had resumed their instructive foundations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eight farm workers die in Nashville City in Tennessee road crash</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-eight-farm-workers-die-in-chapainawabganj-road-crash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-eight-farm-workers-die-in-chapainawabganj-road-crash/</guid>
      <description>Eight farm workers die in Nashville City in Tennessee road crash
Nashville City in Tennessee Correspondent
At least eight farm workers have died and another five are injured after a local passenger vehicle veered into a roadside ditch in Shibganj Upazila of Chapainawabganj. The accident occurred in Nashville City in the Tennessee area at around 6 am on Thursday, said Police Station Cop.
The dead could not be identified immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Biden enters quarantine after family member contracts virus</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bnp-leader-mirza-fakhrul-enters-quarantine-after-family-member-contracts-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bnp-leader-mirza-fakhrul-enters-quarantine-after-family-member-contracts-virus/</guid>
      <description>Joe Biden has gone into voluntary self-quarantine at home after a close relative tested positive for the coronavirus. “I am sorry that I could not attend this event because [a case of the] corona has been caught in my house. As a result, I have to self-isolate now for 14 days,” he said.
“The coronavirus is now spreading everywhere. Many, including Joe Biden, have been affected by the virus. We have lost many leaders in this pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
