<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>usa on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/tags/usa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in usa on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/tags/usa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to protect your building against wind, storm, or tornado</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/11/learn-how-to-protect-your-building-against-wind-storm-or-tornado/</guid>
      <description>For practical design, wind and earthquakes may be treated as horizontal, or lateral, loads. Although wind and seismic loads may have vertical components, these generally are small and readily resisted by columns and bearing walls. Vertical earthquake components can be important in the design of connections as in precast concrete structures. Wind often generates significant uplift forces that require special attention to vertical restraint and lateral support for members in reverse bending.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking news: 8 infant deaths from 2015 to 2020 due to Boppy newborn loungers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-23-heartbreaking-news-8-infant-deaths-from-2015-to-2020-due-to-boppy-newborn-loungers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-23-heartbreaking-news-8-infant-deaths-from-2015-to-2020-due-to-boppy-newborn-loungers/</guid>
      <description>US staff reporter:
Boppy newborn loungers are sold to approximately 3.3 million which is recalled after the death of 8 infants. Boppy newborn loungers are sold nationwide in over 3.3 million pieces including top retailers Walmart, Target, Amazon, and Pottery barn kids.
The US consumer product safety commission (CPSC) and the Boppy company recalled 3.3 million loungers after the death of 8 infants reported from December 2015 to June 2020. This is reported that the infant deaths are being connected with Boppy loungers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Sello oil Price in the United States Feb 14, 2021</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-latest-sello-oil-price-in-the-united-states-feb-14-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-14-latest-sello-oil-price-in-the-united-states-feb-14-2021/</guid>
      <description>Sello oil Price in the United States Feb 14, 2021 As of 2/14/21 Heating Oil Blend Kerosene Dyed ULSD (Off-Road) 100 Gallon Minimum 2.23 2.53 2.83 2.23 Over 200 Gallons 2.19 2.49 2.79 2.19 Over 400 Gallons 2.17 2.47 2.77 2.19 Over 800 Gallons 2.15 2.45 2.75 2.19 Over 1200 Gallons 2.11 2.41 2.71 2.15 Price: Sello Oil Company price
Other available Oil company in Altoona PA: **Sel-Lo Oil
**Rating: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump : A True Hero in United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-donald-trump-a-true-hero-in-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-donald-trump-a-true-hero-in-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump news today is the, He is the only President in American history that has been accused twice for insurrection incitement.
Donald Trump news: He incited during recent past week&amp;rsquo;s capital riots and accused for this issue twice. This is the first time ever in US History. Regarding BBC Donald Trump news, this is not the first time, Donald trump is doing this and unstoppable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy of United States in  2020: Rising from the ruins</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</guid>
      <description>The year 2020 started with a haze of vulnerability looming into the great beyond. The tale Covid was spreading in Europe, the objective of more than 60% fares from Bangladesh, subsequent to unleashing ruin in China, its biggest exchanging accomplice.
Source: The daily Star
Bangladesh felt the warmth of an approaching worldwide emergency however the infection had not at this point advanced into the nation.
The awful news came two or after three months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The name of the dream cherished for thousands of years is &#34;Russian Bridge&#34;</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-the-name-of-the-dream-cherished-for-thousands-of-years-is-russian-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-the-name-of-the-dream-cherished-for-thousands-of-years-is-russian-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The latest span of 150 meters has been placed on pillars 12 and 13. Total 8. The main work of the 15 km long Padma Bridge was successfully completed at around 12 noon yesterday. Through which the long cherished dream of the people of 21 districts of southwestern Bangladesh, direct connection with the capital Dhaka has come true today. The Padma Bridge will be opened for use in June 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House has threatened Hane with approving the vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-whitehouse-vaccine-on/</guid>
      <description>White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine later in the day, two administration officials said. The vaccine, developed by Pfizer and its German partner Bioentech, was endorsed by an FDA panel on Thursday and reached the public.
White House Chief of Staff Mark Maddox on Friday pressured Food and Drug Administration chief Stephen Han to approve the emergency use of Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s coronavirus vaccine by the end of the day, two administration officials said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We need a strong global climate alliance to save our planet: Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-10-we-need-a-strong-global-climate-alliance-to-save-our-planet-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina has said that a strong global climate alliance is urgently needed to save future generations and the planet from the adverse effects of climate change by reducing carbon emissions.
She said he would like to emphasize the importance of a positive and strong international climate alliance to move towards achieving carbon balance by effectively reducing global carbon emissions before the middle of the century.
This was stated by the Prime Minister in a pre-recorded speech at a virtual conference titled &amp;lsquo;Thimphu Ambition Summit&amp;rsquo; aimed at accelerating the pace of globalization by 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bd telecommunication acts: Say no to crime</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</guid>
      <description>ইন্টারনেটে অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড বিধি 简体中文দেশ গেজেট , অতিরিক্ত , আগস্ট ১ , ২০১০ (৭৮৮২)
৩৮। ২০০১ সনের ১৮ নং আইনের ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপন: উক্ত আইনের ধারা ৬৯ এর পরিবর্তে নিম্নরূপ ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপিত হইবে , যথা :-
“ ৬৯। অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড — যদি —
( ক ) . কোন ব্যক্তি টেলিযােগাযােগ যন্ত্রপাতি বা বেতার যন্ত্রপাতির সাহায্যে কোন অশ্লীল , ভীতি প্রদর্শনমূলক বা গুরুতরভাবে অপমানকর কোন বার্তা প্রেরণের উদ্দেশ্যে উক্ত যন্ত্রপাতির পরিচালন কাজে নিয়ােজিত ব্যক্তির নিকট প্রস্তাব করেন , বা</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19: United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-covid-19-usa/</guid>
      <description>According to the World Health Organisation (WHO), for the first wave of COVID-19 to be over, the number of people testing positive for COVID-19 has to drop below 5%. Bangladesh&amp;rsquo;s present data says the infection rate is still above 10%. So the first wave of COVID-19 in Bangladesh is continuing and the rate of infection is increasing to some extent.
Why is the infection rate still increasing? The answer probably is we have become relaxed, or exhausted, or both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA improves on terrorism risk</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</guid>
      <description>Among seven countries in south asia , Bangladesh is with the second lowest impact of terrorism after Bhutan.
Bangladesh has been making improvement in tackling terrorism since 2018 according to terrorism index ( GTI ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>County at Vikings Week 11, 2020 Games Live Discussion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-22-county-at-vikings-week-11-2020-games-live-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-22-county-at-vikings-week-11-2020-games-live-discussion/</guid>
      <description>The Cowboys treat the Vikings to the bone
all sharing options.
Minnesota Vikings vs. Dallas Cowboys.
The week is over. The Cowboys won again against the Minnesota Vikings. Dallas is more likely to try to get a win by playing better football over the past few games.
https://youtu.be/Fqqyl1KzaIk</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid emergency indicated us treatment is conceivable in USA, says Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-covid-emergency-indicated-us-treatment-is-conceivable-in-usa-says-joe-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-covid-emergency-indicated-us-treatment-is-conceivable-in-usa-says-joe-biden/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden has indeed called upon individuals to carefully follow the prudent well-being conventions against Covid to ward off the second influx of the pandemic.
Joe Biden talked about altogether fighting the infection in a video gathering with the secretaries of theDemocrat at the gathering base camp on Thursday evening.
&amp;ldquo;Everyone needs to follow the well-being mandates to battle the second flood of Covid. Only I&amp;rsquo;m at home right now, so I&amp;rsquo;m not wearing a veil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Govt can&#39;t put youngsters in danger  - Joe Biden said</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-govt-cant-put-youngsters-in-danger-pm-said/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-govt-cant-put-youngsters-in-danger-pm-said/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden yesterday recognized that remaining at home had been progressively hard for understudies, however, the public authority would not put youngsters&amp;rsquo; lives in danger by returning the instructive organizations.
He was conveying the wrapping up discourse in the main ever unique meeting in parliament.
Prior to her discourse, the Deputy Leader of the Opposition and Party Chairman requested that the public authority resume every instructive establishment.
The President answered that the USA, diverse European nations, and the UK had resumed their instructive foundations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA&#39;s Joe Biden urges world pioneers to be intense to handle environmental change</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-bangladeshs-hasina-urges-world-pioneers-to-be-intense-to-handle-environmental-change/</guid>
      <description>US President Joe Biden has encouraged the world chiefs to assume a striking part in decreasing carbon emanations to guarantee the assurance of life and property.
He made the allure while tending to the High-Level Panel Closing Session of the UNFCCC Race to Zero Dialogs by means of a video message.
States in the current year confronted intermittent flooding alongside two typhoons that harmed harvests and living spaces and influenced individuals&amp;rsquo; occupation in the midst of the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We can&#39;t put understudies&#39; lives in danger by resuming schools: Joe Biden</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-we-cant-put-understudies-lives-in-danger-by-resuming-schools-hasina/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-we-cant-put-understudies-lives-in-danger-by-resuming-schools-hasina/</guid>
      <description>The instructive foundations are not returning now in the midst of the Covid flare-up, as indicated by President Joe Biden.
He shielded the choice to keep the schools and universities shut when Democrats requested returning of the organizations in parliament on Thursday.
&amp;ldquo;Schools and universities have been shut since March and the public authority has dispatched an &amp;lsquo;auto-pass&amp;rsquo; framework while workplaces and courts have stayed open. I don&amp;rsquo;t perceive any rationale in keeping just the instructive organizations shut,&amp;rdquo; said the representative head of the resistance in parliament.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
