<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economy on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economy on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Greenhouse Gases and Renewable Energy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/08/greenhouse-gases-and-renewable-energy/</guid>
      <description>Effect greenhouse What are greenhouse gases (GHG)? Greenhouse gases (GHGs) trap heat within the earth’s atmosphere, contributing to the ‘greenhouse’ effect and causing global warming. These gases include carbon dioxide, methane, nitrous oxide, and water vapor. Industry, including manufacturing, is the second largest global emitter of human-created GHGs. Much of industrial GHG emissions are due to the burning of fossil fuels for heat and power generation.
Why should I care about GHGs?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building contractor&#39;s insurance restoration services in the United States</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/building-contractors-insurance-restoration-services-in-the-united-states/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/building-contractors-insurance-restoration-services-in-the-united-states/</guid>
      <description>Building contractor&amp;rsquo;s insurance services are very much important for contractors&amp;rsquo; life. Because there have so many uncertain hazards related to building construction works. That&amp;rsquo;s the reason building constructors live under different crises during building development works.
Roofing contractors need that insurance coverage in the service sector. There are many top-level roofing contractors&amp;rsquo; insurance services all over the United States area.
Take a short look at Illions Roofing Contractors&amp;rsquo; list with Addresses, Phone Numbers And, Email Addresses: To be continued&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best economical structures of building construction</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/best-economical-structures-of-building-construction/</guid>
      <description>STRUCTURAL STEEL CONSTRUCTION Structural steel is the economical construction material for building applications. It offers high ratios of strength to weight and strength to volume. Thus, structural steel has the advantage of permitting long clear spans for horizontal members and requiring less floor space for columns than other common construction materials. It also can be used in combination with reinforced concrete to provide cost-effective building components. For large industrial buildings, where the structural frame can be exposed, it is often the material of choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different types of Steel Grades</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/07/different-types-of-steel-grades/</guid>
      <description>Structural steel grades are referred to by their corresponding ASTM designation. For example, the most commonly used grade of structural steel is A36, which is produced to meet the requirements of the ASTM A36 specification. This grade offers a good mix of strength, weldability, and cost. In many designs, this specification alone will satisfy designers’ needs. Other specifications, such as A53 for pipe, provide an equivalent grade of steel for that type of product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about different types of industrial trucks &amp; vehicles</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/05/learn-about-different-types-of-industrial-trucks-vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Industrial vehicles/trucks are one of the most common groups of materials handling equipment used in industry as well as in the day-to-day distribution of goods in warehouses, large stores, transport depots, etc. The basic operation and construction features of some of the common types of industrial trucks will be discussed here. The adjective ‘‘industrial’’ used before this group of vehicles/trucks is to distinguish these from other groups of vehicles like buses, lorries, trucks, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn About Environmental Biotechnology</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/blog/2022/03/learn-about-environmental-biotechnology/</guid>
      <description>When modern industrialization started in the 19th century, many people migrated from the agricultural area to the big cities. Public hygiene became a major problem. Human excrement and waste was discharged into open channels, rivers, and lakes. The pollution was disastrous and hygiene-related epidemic diseases, like cholera and typhus, occurred frequently. Therefore, it was an important step forward when public water collection systems and treatment plants were introduced at the end of the 19th century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Concepts of Supply Chain Management</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-10-basic-concepts-of-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/12/2021-12-10-basic-concepts-of-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>Supply chains encompass the companies and the business activities needed to design, make, deliver, and use a product or service. Businesses depend on their supply chains to provide them with what they need to survive and thrive. Every business fits into one or more supply chains and has a role to play in each of them. The pace of change and the uncertainty about how markets will evolve has made it increasingly important for companies to be aware of the supply chains they participate in and to understand the roles that they play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Integration Strategy: What’s Best For Our Business</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-supply-chain-integration-strategy-whats-best-for-our-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-supply-chain-integration-strategy-whats-best-for-our-business/</guid>
      <description>BUILDING A SUPPLY CHAIN INTEGRATION STRATEGY Whether you are a manufacturer, distributor, or service provider, every organization has a supply chain that needs to be managed. For many, the overall benefit of supply chain management software (SCM) is not difficult to understand. However, considering all the business processes that comprise the supply chain and the numerous SCM tools available, the basic question is where to start. The following are the critical first steps that manufacturers should take</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is COP26 And Why Its Matter</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-04-what-is-cop26-and-why-its-matter/</guid>
      <description>UK hosts a summit amongst United Nations countries to talk about global climate changes, how to tackle this situation and what necessary steps should take in immediate action is called COP26.
It was a plan to host in Glasgow, in a city of Scotland in November 2020 last year and attend more than 200 world countries leader, but due to Coronavirus Pandemic, the COP26 program delayed more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thermodynamics, heat transfer, and fluid flow mechanics</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-20-thermodynamics-heat-transfer-and-fluid-flow-free-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/10/2021-10-20-thermodynamics-heat-transfer-and-fluid-flow-free-handbook/</guid>
      <description>Fluid flow is an important part of most industrial processes; especially those involving the transfer of heat. Frequently, when it is desired to remove heat from the point at which it is generated, some type of fluid is involved in the heat transfer process. Examples of this are the cooling water circulated through a gasoline or diesel engine, the airflow past the windings of a motor, and the flow of water through the core of a nuclear reactor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ringid news update</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-13-ringid-news-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/09/2021-09-13-ringid-news-update/</guid>
      <description>Today 13th September 2021, our blog reader Mohammad got a response from Ringid customer care helpline after waiting a month. Mohammad had few queries to Ringid, and no one replied him back from Ringid.
Ringid is a mobile application platform founded by Ayrin Islam in Ontaro Canada. Ayrin is a successful entrepreneur and CEO. Ringid first launched in 2015, and today Ringid have more than 3 million customers globally.
Ring id customers support services was very irregular and no one reply on time and they have no helpline number unless app chat options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh Export Import Duty</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-24-bangladesh-export-import-duty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-24-bangladesh-export-import-duty/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh Government has export-import operative tariff plan executed and published by Bangladesh custom governing body. This board is under the Bangladesh National Board Of Revenue. Bangladesh customs are under the department of the National Board of Revenue. You can calculate import duty by this plan and this will help you in Bangladesh if you want to import products/materials/anything from the international marketplace.
Search Bangladesh Import Export Duty Tariff Plan: Download file here ::</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to earn 15000 USD in a month</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-16-earn-money-online-ringid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/08/2021-08-16-earn-money-online-ringid/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that ring ID is very easy to earn a lot of money? Nowadays many people are sitting at home very easily by opening Ring ID account and earning a minimum of 15000 rupees per month. You can invest in Ring ID without any tension. You should see 50-100 ads per month. An ad is 20-30 seconds max. 100 ad will be seen in less than 1 hour. Guaranteed income of 15000 rupees with less than 1 hour daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret Of Making An Easy 5k A Month Within The Next 22 Days</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/05/2021-05-24-the-secret-of-making-an-easy-5k-a-month-within-the-next-22-days-2/</guid>
      <description>Making money is the big secret of life, it&amp;rsquo;s not so easy to make money. Many many people is trying to earn money, they are doing lots of things but money is not so easy to get much within short time. I have tried lots of things last couple of years. Amazon affiliate, digital marketing, learning programming, social media marketing, Upwork, Fiverr and more. But money is not easy to make online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factory Audit Form and Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-factory-audit-form-and-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-factory-audit-form-and-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>If you want to prepare a report based on your factory Audit/observation, you need to focus on some important factors. We have prepared a list of guidelines you can follow during the Audit factory apparel or garment or textile industry and prepare a report based on below specific key facts:
FACTORY OBSERVATION FORM Factory Report# :
Auditor Name :
Date :
Factory Code :
Division Code :
Factory Name: ABC LTD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knit Garments CM Calculation Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-31-knit-garments-cm-calculation-formula/</guid>
      <description>In Apparel and Fashion industry, CM means Cost of Manufacture. In the garment manufacturing industry, CM means Manufacturing Cost of one dozen or 12 pcs garments. To calculate the CM of 12 pcs knit garments we must follow the below criterion-
monthly expenditure of the industry total no. of running machine machine qty to execute the layout of the specific order, productivity per shift dollar exchange rate Let, Monthly Industry Expenditure is BDT 80,00,000 Working days of the 30 days = 26 days Daily Factory Expenditure = BDT 307692.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance and Sustainability: Conflict Minerals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</guid>
      <description>Learn About Conflict Minerals US guidelines for vendor compliance and sustainability
Index:
What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals in Products US Conflict Minerals Laws Auditing and Reporting Requirements Customer’s expectations Continuous Tracking Tracing workflow Reporting – CFSI Beyond USA What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals refer to raw materials that come from a particular part of the world where conflict is occurring and trading of those materials, perpetuates the fighting. Conflict minerals are mined in conditions of armed conflict and human rights abuses, notably in the Democratic Republic of Congo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embroidery capacity calculation</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-embroidery-production-capacity-calculation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-20-embroidery-production-capacity-calculation/</guid>
      <description>Embroidery industry is very much important for garment and textile industry. All customer need a logo of their brand on garment. Embroidery is so much popular and expensive rather than printing process. If you want to setup your own embroidery factory, you need to do capacity calculation based on your machine and manpower. Today we will show you how to calculate capacity of a embroidery industry:
Embroidery Production capacity calculation Area: Embroidery Objectives: To identify embroidery production capacity and set embroidery target plan to achieve ultimate goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garment Sewing Operator Training Program Guideline</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-18-garment-sewing-operator-training-program-guideline/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create a garment sewing operator training module. This training module was developed and tested successfully to take thousands of sewing operators training in different garment and textile manufacturing industries in Bangladesh. This training module fully structured and full of all technical guidelines about garment sewing operator&amp;rsquo;s long-time training procedure, schedule, practical training guide, technical sewing information, exam process, and others all necessary reporting formats. The step-by-step guide will help garment and textile manufacturers globally to know how to train sewing operators in big industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Padma Bridge will open within 2022!</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-padma-bridge-will-open-within-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-16-padma-bridge-will-open-within-2022/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh dream Padma Bridge will open for road transport entrance within 2022, Road transport Minister Obaidul Kader said today in a meeting. Padma bridge is the dream of Bangladesh people and the Padma bridge will connect the Southeast Southwest part of Bangladesh with the capital city Dhaka.
Created with Bdmeter.info
Padma bridge was the biggest challenge of Bangladesh. But Bangladesh already has completed the main structure of the Padma bridge. Today in a press conference Road transport minister Obaidul Kader said that The Padma will open for vehicle movement within 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#boycottindianonion</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-19-boycottindianonion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-19-boycottindianonion/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh is now fullfil to grow onion countrywide and original deshi onion price is now 30 to 40 tk countrywide.
Indian onion market price is 10 taka higher than deshi quality right now. That&amp;rsquo;s why Bangladesh onion importer stopped to import onion from India last 10 days.
Even there is 10 taka less prices onion in available in market price around 15 - 20 taka</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy of Bangladesh in  2020: Rising from the ruins</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-bangladesh-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-bangladesh-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</guid>
      <description>The year 2020 started with a haze of vulnerability looming into the great beyond. The tale Covid was spreading in Europe, the objective of more than 60% fares from Bangladesh, subsequent to unleashing ruin in China, its biggest exchanging accomplice.
Source: The daily Star
Bangladesh felt the warmth of an approaching worldwide emergency however the infection had not at this point advanced into the nation.
The awful news came two or after three months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economy of United States in  2020: Rising from the ruins</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-01-economy-of-usa-in-2020-rising-from-the-ruins/</guid>
      <description>The year 2020 started with a haze of vulnerability looming into the great beyond. The tale Covid was spreading in Europe, the objective of more than 60% fares from Bangladesh, subsequent to unleashing ruin in China, its biggest exchanging accomplice.
Source: The daily Star
Bangladesh felt the warmth of an approaching worldwide emergency however the infection had not at this point advanced into the nation.
The awful news came two or after three months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The name of the dream cherished for thousands of years is &#34;Russian Bridge&#34;</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-the-name-of-the-dream-cherished-for-thousands-of-years-is-russian-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-11-the-name-of-the-dream-cherished-for-thousands-of-years-is-russian-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The latest span of 150 meters has been placed on pillars 12 and 13. Total 8. The main work of the 15 km long Padma Bridge was successfully completed at around 12 noon yesterday. Through which the long cherished dream of the people of 21 districts of southwestern Bangladesh, direct connection with the capital Dhaka has come true today. The Padma Bridge will be opened for use in June 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>India quick to work with Bangladesh on guard equipment stages</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-india-quick-to-work-with-bangladesh-on-guard-equipment-stages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-india-quick-to-work-with-bangladesh-on-guard-equipment-stages/</guid>
      <description>India has said it is quick to work with Bangladesh on safeguard equipment stages like Akash rocket, radars, mortars, cannons weapons and ammo and welcomed ventures from its eastern neighbor in two key Indian protection modern hallways.
India likewise said that its shipyards are happy to band together with Bangladeshi shipyards for development of stages according to Bangladesh prerequisites through joint endeavors, co-improvement and cooperation for both business and safeguard necessities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Worldwide economy recuperating, yet might be losing energy: IMF boss</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-worldwide-economy-recuperating-yet-might-be-losing-energy-imf-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-worldwide-economy-recuperating-yet-might-be-losing-energy-imf-boss/</guid>
      <description>Global Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva. Reuters
Global Monetary Fund (IMF) Managing Director Kristalina Georgieva. Reuters
The worldwide economy is recuperating from the profundities of the Covid emergency, however there are indications of easing back force in nations with resurging contamination rates, the International Monetary Fund said in another report for G20 significant economies.
The report, delivered in front of the current week&amp;rsquo;s virtual gatherings of account authorities and pioneers from the Group of 20 nations, underscored the lopsided idea of the worldwide recuperation and cautioned the emergency would probably leave profound, inconsistent scars.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
