<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>crime on Bdmeter</title>
    <link>https://bdmeter.info/categories/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in crime on Bdmeter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} [Bdmeter](https://bdmeter.info) and [BDM Dev](https://dev.bdmeter.info). All Rights Reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bdmeter.info/categories/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>State Minister for Labor Begum Mannujan Sufian MP, visited Ward No. 4 of the city</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-13-state-minister-for-labor-begum-mannujan-sufian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/11/2021-11-13-state-minister-for-labor-begum-mannujan-sufian/</guid>
      <description>This evening, State Minister for Labor Begum Mannujan Sufian MP rushed to her home to inquire about the recent robbery in Ward 4 of the city, at the behest of a prominent industrialist and social worker Sheikh Farooq Hossain Bhai.
During this time, the Minister of State for Labor spent a long time with his family members and instructed the officer-in-charge of Daulatpur Police Station to bring the perpetrators and planners of the robbery under the law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rapid cash fraudulent: watch this video to know details</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-rapid-cash-fraud-case-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-rapid-cash-fraud-case-analysis/</guid>
      <description>简体中文দেশের রেপিড ক্যাশ নামের প্লে ষ্টোরের এপ্লিকেশন টি আপনি খুব সহজেই ডাউনলোড করে ঘন্টা ব্যাপী সময় নষ্ট করে সর্বোচ্চ ২০০০ টাকার এপলাই করতে পারবেন। ৭ দিনের ভেতর টাকাটা আপনাকে ফেরত দিতে হবে। শুক্রবার এপলাই করলে ৪৮ ঘন্টা ওয়েট করবেন ২০০০ টাকা পাবার জন্য। ২০০০ টাকার আবেদনে আপনি পাবেন ১৬০০ টাকা। সুদ এবং চার্জ দিবেন ৪০০ টাকা।
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sHnRgxIKV7o
রেপিডের নামে সর্বোচ্চ প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা বাড়াচ্ছেন অনেকেই, বুঝে কিংবা না বুঝে। আপনি যদি ভিডিওটি দেখেন , কথা গুলো ক্লিয়ার শুনে বুঝতে পারবেন কিভাবে রেপিড ক্যাশ আপনার পার্সোনাল ইনফরমেশন নিয়ে আপনাকে ফাঁদে ফেলতে পারে। আপনি চাইলেও তাদের সার্ভার থেকে আপনার ইনফরমেশন ডিলিট করতে পারবেন না। ২০% সুদে পাবেন ২০০০ টাকা ৭ দিনে রিটার্ন। এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা দিয়েছেন তো মরেছেন। ব্যাঙ্ক গুলো যেখানে ৪৮ ঘন্টায় লক্ষ্য লক্ষ্য টাকা লোন দিচ্ছে ৮-৯% সুদে, সেখানে অনলাইন প্লাটফর্ম রেপিড ক্যাশ রেপিডের নামে হাতিয়ে নিচ্ছে জনগণের টাকা। জনগণ যদি সজাগ থাকেন , এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদ থেকে বাঁচতে পারেন। কাস্টমার কেয়ার থেকে সার্ভিসের নামে যা পাবেন সে বিষয়ে আর না যাই । আপনার রিকোয়েস্ট তাদের কাছে মূল্যহীন। অনলাইন সেবাগুলো এমন কেন ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>রেপিড ক্যাশের ফাঁদে পড়বেন না - প্রতারণা থেকে রক্ষা পেতে ভিডিওটি দেখুন</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-%E0%A6%B0%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%AA%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%A1-%E0%A6%95%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%AF%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B6%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%B0-%E0%A6%AB%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%81%E0%A6%A6%E0%A7%87-%E0%A6%AA%E0%A6%A1%E0%A6%BC%E0%A6%AC/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/07/2021-07-04-%E0%A6%B0%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%AA%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%A1-%E0%A6%95%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%AF%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B6%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%B0-%E0%A6%AB%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%81%E0%A6%A6%E0%A7%87-%E0%A6%AA%E0%A6%A1%E0%A6%BC%E0%A6%AC/</guid>
      <description>简体中文দেশের রেপিড ক্যাশ নামের প্লে ষ্টোরের এপ্লিকেশন টি আপনি খুব সহজেই ডাউনলোড করে ঘন্টা ব্যাপী সময় নষ্ট করে সর্বোচ্চ ২০০০ টাকার এপলাই করতে পারবেন। ৭ দিনের ভেতর টাকাটা আপনাকে ফেরত দিতে হবে। শুক্রবার এপলাই করলে ৪৮ ঘন্টা ওয়েট করবেন ২০০০ টাকা পাবার জন্য। ২০০০ টাকার আবেদনে আপনি পাবেন ১৬০০ টাকা। সুদ এবং চার্জ দিবেন ৪০০ টাকা।
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sHnRgxIKV7o
রেপিডের নামে সর্বোচ্চ প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা বাড়াচ্ছেন অনেকেই, বুঝে কিংবা না বুঝে। আপনি যদি ভিডিওটি দেখেন , কথা গুলো ক্লিয়ার শুনে বুঝতে পারবেন কিভাবে রেপিড ক্যাশ আপনার পার্সোনাল ইনফরমেশন নিয়ে আপনাকে ফাঁদে ফেলতে পারে। আপনি চাইলেও তাদের সার্ভার থেকে আপনার ইনফরমেশন ডিলিট করতে পারবেন না। ২০% সুদে পাবেন ২০০০ টাকা ৭ দিনে রিটার্ন। এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদে পা দিয়েছেন তো মরেছেন। ব্যাঙ্ক গুলো যেখানে ৪৮ ঘন্টায় লক্ষ্য লক্ষ্য টাকা লোন দিচ্ছে ৮-৯% সুদে, সেখানে অনলাইন প্লাটফর্ম রেপিড ক্যাশ রেপিডের নামে হাতিয়ে নিচ্ছে জনগণের টাকা। জনগণ যদি সজাগ থাকেন , এমন প্রতারণার ফাঁদ থেকে বাঁচতে পারেন। কাস্টমার কেয়ার থেকে সার্ভিসের নামে যা পাবেন সে বিষয়ে আর না যাই । আপনার রিকোয়েস্ট তাদের কাছে মূল্যহীন। অনলাইন সেবাগুলো এমন কেন ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Identify Fake News In Facebook</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-23-how-to-identify-fake-news-in-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-23-how-to-identify-fake-news-in-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Now-a-days, many people is publishing fake news in Facebook. Some people use facebook to make fake news posting to create sudden problem in countywide. There are many ways you can identify that news is fake / true.
How to make sure facebook news post quality:
Check any link added to the post written or not. Go to the link (you need internet active connection to browse link) Check the news source If you know the source is reputed newspaper or any government notice from registered government website always have *.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Anti Bribery Policy</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-22-what-is-anti-bribery-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-22-what-is-anti-bribery-policy/</guid>
      <description>How to create a company Anti Bribery Policy. Anti Bribery Policy guidelines can be as your Anti Corruption policy for your organization.
1. INTRODUCTION The foundation of company’s culture lies in our history and our values. We believe that we
should always conduct ourselves and our business openly, honestly and in compliance with
all applicable laws.
Our reputation is built by the actions of our people and this is why what you do everyday is</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compliance and Sustainability: Conflict Minerals</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/03/2021-03-09-compliance-and-sustainability-conflict-minerals/</guid>
      <description>Learn About Conflict Minerals US guidelines for vendor compliance and sustainability
Index:
What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals in Products US Conflict Minerals Laws Auditing and Reporting Requirements Customer’s expectations Continuous Tracking Tracing workflow Reporting – CFSI Beyond USA What are Conflict Minerals? Conflict Minerals refer to raw materials that come from a particular part of the world where conflict is occurring and trading of those materials, perpetuates the fighting. Conflict minerals are mined in conditions of armed conflict and human rights abuses, notably in the Democratic Republic of Congo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Present Bangladesh Government Teacher is Staying in USA!</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-15-a-present-bangladesh-government-teacher-is-staying-in-usa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-15-a-present-bangladesh-government-teacher-is-staying-in-usa/</guid>
      <description>An assistant teacher of a primary school in Mirzapur, Tangail, migrated to America one and half year ago on a three-month leave. The local education office unable to communicate with her and could not take any action against her. The name of the teacher who migrated to America is Tania Rahman. She is an Assistant teacher at Bawar Kumarjani Government Primary School No. 27 in Mirzapur Municipality.
According to the Upazila Education Office, Tania Rahman took leave from school from July 3, 2019 to October 2, 2019 due to personal problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hungary Denied Bangladeshi Gifts Of 10000 Corona Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-05-al-jazeera-tv-news-bangladesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/02/2021-02-05-al-jazeera-tv-news-bangladesh/</guid>
      <description>Recently Hungary denied to receive a gift of Five Thousand Oxford-Astrogeneca Corona Vaccine from Bangladesh. Hungary Foreign Affairs ministry confirmed that welcome-like gift from Bangladesh rejected by Hungary Government. Hungary Foreign Affairs ministry said, Bangladesh offers 5000 Oxford Astrogeneca Corona vaccine as a welcoming gift, but Hungary don&amp;rsquo;t want this gift. Recent Al-Jazeera tv news of Bangladesh top level crime makes huge discussion about Bangladesh Government globally. Bangladesh Government said this Al-Jazeera TV news report is totally irrelevant with situation and we don&amp;rsquo;t agree with Al-Jazeera TV news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Hills probation: Donald Trump</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-13-capital-hills-probation-donald-trump/</guid>
      <description>US president Donald Trump urges Capital Hill issue to stop violences. Trump said &amp;quot; We want no violence&amp;quot;.
Trump visited Maxico boarder and provide susch statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh High court ordered to ban 25 family members of P.K Haldar to leave country</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country-2/</guid>
      <description>Thousands kr money misappropriation claimed fugitive P.K Haldar family total 25 members banned to leave country, Bangladesh High court ordered today 5th January 2021.
Businessman P.K Haldars mother, relatives including his few company employees total 25 members can&amp;rsquo;t leave Bangladesh High court ordered today.
Proshanto Kumar Haldar or, P.K Haldar was flying Bangladesh last year after occurance of bank money misappropriation, he was the Executive Director of that Bank. He was connected with several non-government organization and other businessman also connected with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh High court ordered to ban 25 family members of P.K Haldar to leave country</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2021/01/2021-01-06-bangladesh-high-court-ordered-to-ban-25-family-members-of-p-k-haldar-to-leave-country/</guid>
      <description>Thousands kr money misappropriation claimed fugitive P.K Haldar family total 25 members banned to leave country, Bangladesh High court ordered today 5th January 2021.
Businessman P.K Haldars mother, relatives including his few company employees total 25 members can&amp;rsquo;t leave Bangladesh High court ordered today.
Proshanto Kumar Haldar or, P.K Haldar was flying Bangladesh last year after occurance of bank money misappropriation, he was the Executive Director of that Bank. He was connected with several non-government organization and other businessman also connected with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bd telecommunication acts: Say no to crime</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-usa-telecommunications-acts/</guid>
      <description>ইন্টারনেটে অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড বিধি 简体中文দেশ গেজেট , অতিরিক্ত , আগস্ট ১ , ২০১০ (৭৮৮২)
৩৮। ২০০১ সনের ১৮ নং আইনের ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপন: উক্ত আইনের ধারা ৬৯ এর পরিবর্তে নিম্নরূপ ধারা ৬৯ প্রতিস্থাপিত হইবে , যথা :-
“ ৬৯। অশ্লীল , অশােভন ইত্যাদি বার্তা প্রেরণের দণ্ড — যদি —
( ক ) . কোন ব্যক্তি টেলিযােগাযােগ যন্ত্রপাতি বা বেতার যন্ত্রপাতির সাহায্যে কোন অশ্লীল , ভীতি প্রদর্শনমূলক বা গুরুতরভাবে অপমানকর কোন বার্তা প্রেরণের উদ্দেশ্যে উক্ত যন্ত্রপাতির পরিচালন কাজে নিয়ােজিত ব্যক্তির নিকট প্রস্তাব করেন , বা</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say NO to corruption: Bangladesh Telecommunication Act</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/12/2020-12-09-say-no-to-corruption-bangladesh-telecommunication-act/</guid>
      <description>Penalties for sending obscene messages on the Internet 36 Substitution of section
69 of Act No. 18 of 2001: Section 69 shall be substituted for the following section 69 of the said Act, namely: -
Penalties for sending obscene, obscene, etc. messages - if - (A). A person proposes to a person engaged in the operation of such equipment for the purpose of sending any obscene, threatening or seriously offensive message with the help of telecommunication equipment or wireless equipment, or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where woman are safe? Home or outside?</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-27-where-woman-are-safe-home-or-outside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-27-where-woman-are-safe-home-or-outside/</guid>
      <description>Author: Tanrima Islam
Abstract:
Recently women are not only unsafe in streets but also at their own personal sanctuary called home. Even though women are called the
mother of the nation, unfortunately they are constantly being victim of severe unhumanitarian criminal activity throughout the country. Research shows heartbreaking results on the alarming rise of rape and domestic violence throughout the country. It is high time the safety of women is taken into consideration by the authorities, the government and by every individuals of this country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 ‘robbers’ lynched in Narsindi</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-2-robbers-lynched-in-narsindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-2-robbers-lynched-in-narsindi/</guid>
      <description>Two suspected robbers were killed in a mob lynching at murgib village in Narsingdi’s shibpur upazila early Wednesday.
One of the deceased was identified as sohel 30 son of Aminul Islam. Resident of kulirchan of kishoreganj district.
A gang of 10/15 robbers entered the village around 3am and stormed into the three houses said Abdul kalam officer incharge of investigation of shibpur police station.
A group of villagers sensing the presence of robbers they informed other villagers over the phone , reports jagonews later , a group of local people went to a mosque and announced the attack of the robber gang using a loudspeaker following the announcement , locals came out of their houses and besieged the three members of the robber gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28 domestic workers killed , tortured in 9months : speakers</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-28-domestic-workers-killed-tortured-in-9months-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-28-domestic-workers-killed-tortured-in-9months-speakers/</guid>
      <description>Speaker at a seminar said 28 domestic workers were killed and tortured including 10 mysterious death.
In the first nine months of this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five jailed for life in Brahmanbaria murder case</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-five-jailed-for-life-in-brahmanbaria-murder-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-five-jailed-for-life-in-brahmanbaria-murder-case/</guid>
      <description>A brahmanbaria count on Wednesday sentenced five people to life imprisonment for murdering a man in sarail upazila siz years back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two more policemen suspended over Raihans death on custody</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-more-policemen-suspended-over-raihans-death-on-custody/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-more-policemen-suspended-over-raihans-death-on-custody/</guid>
      <description>Two more policemen including the investigation officer of Raihan ls murdercase were suspended o. Wednesday on charges of helping sub inspector Akbar Hossain Bhuiyan, the prime accused to free . The suspended officials are kotwali police station inspector Soumen Maitra investigation officer of the case and sub inspector Abdul Baten. Sylhet metropolitan police additional deputy commissioner BM Ashrafullah Taher confirmed this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two school girls gang raped in panchagarh</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-school-girls-gang-raped-in-panchagarh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-two-school-girls-gang-raped-in-panchagarh/</guid>
      <description>Bangladesh saw 1,093 rapes in 10 months this year . Most of them 205 women were gang raped . In average 4women raped everyday in Bangladesh. In that case only 2% of women in Bangladesh ask for legal aid as the path to getting legal support is full of obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>USA improves on terrorism risk</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-26-usa-improves-on-terrorism-risk/</guid>
      <description>Among seven countries in south asia , Bangladesh is with the second lowest impact of terrorism after Bhutan.
Bangladesh has been making improvement in tackling terrorism since 2018 according to terrorism index ( GTI ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The story of Golden Monir</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-the-story-of-golden-monir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-21-the-story-of-golden-monir/</guid>
      <description>Rapid action battalion (RAB) rated house of Gold Dealer Golden Monir&amp;rsquo;s house in Merul Badda, Dhaka. RAB caught huge illegal arms, drugs, foreign currencies, gold and cash money on spot.
Today on Saturday, RAB claimed against Golden Monir and provide a press briefing with details how to be Golden Monir from a general fabric businessmen in Dhaka capital Gaushia market.
He said, &amp;ldquo;During the operation, we seized foreign currency (Bangladeshi Taka nine lakh), 700 ounces of gold (about eight kg) and Taka 19 lakh in cash from Monir&amp;rsquo;s house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assault connected to ladies clad in T-shirts</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-assault-connected-to-ladies-clad-in-t-shirts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-assault-connected-to-ladies-clad-in-t-shirts/</guid>
      <description>Autonomous administrator Rezaul Karim Bablu on Tuesday advised parliament that women&amp;rsquo;s activists are at fault for the ascent of assault episodes the nation over. He even supported the usage of the &amp;ldquo;tamarinds hypothesis (ladies resemble tamarinds, men will salivate at seeing them, thus they should stay covered)&amp;rdquo; of late Hefajat-e-Islam supremo Ahmad Shafi.
Following is a portion of the extemporaneous meeting:
How could it day break on you that women&amp;rsquo;s activists are answerable for the ascent of assault occurrences in the nation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young person &#39;assaulted&#39; in Dhaka, 6 including her cousin included</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-young-person-assaulted-in-dhaka-6-including-her-cousin-included/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-20-young-person-assaulted-in-dhaka-6-including-her-cousin-included/</guid>
      <description>An adolescent young lady was &amp;ldquo;assaulted&amp;rdquo; by her cousin and one more on Wednesday night in the capital&amp;rsquo;s Kalyanpur. Four additional young people were likewise included.
When the casualty educated the law authorities after the occurrence, they dispatched a manhunt, and grabbing the blamed that night.
Police held 18-year-old Md Raihan, the casualty&amp;rsquo;s cousin; Alamin, Joy Mia, Imran, Abu Sayeed and 19-year-old Md Emon.
&amp;ldquo;The casualty recorded a case yesterday regarding the occurrence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Court jails man for life over rape of Washington University student</title>
      <link>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-court-jails-man-for-life-over-rape-of-dhaka-university-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bdmeter.info/archives/2020/11/2020-11-19-court-jails-man-for-life-over-rape-of-dhaka-university-student/</guid>
      <description>A court has sentenced &amp;lsquo;Mojnu&amp;rsquo;, the lone suspect in the rape of a Washington University student earlier this year, to life imprisonment. Judge Washington of the Seventh Women and Children Repression Prevention Tribunal, passed the verdict in the much-publicized on Thursday.
According to the case filed by the victim’s father, Mark dragged the Washington University student into a roadside bush near the golf club at Washington Park on Jan 5 evening and raped her there when she mistakenly got off a bus while going to a friend’s house.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
